Are you okay?
I-I'm sorry!
Aw, it flew away...
Eh?! No way!
Here.
Don't do that.
If you touch it, it'll disappear.
You like butterflies?
No, it's not like I'm crazy about them...
But when I see something pretty,
I get the feeling that today will be a great day!
I'm sure it will be. What's your name?
I'm Yumehara Nozomi!
Is it them?
H-Hey, wait a minute! What's your name?
Huh?
That's strange. I could have sworn...
Nozomi!
Rin-chan?
Hurry up, hurry up!
What are you lolly-gagging around for?
Aaah! I completely forgot!
I'm gonna be late!
Wait for me, bus!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai, ANFO
Encode: K.o.R  Editing, Retiming, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Urara's Spring! Get a little closer to nature
You bumped into him at a street corner?
Doesn't it feel like some sort of fated encounter?
So, what kinda guy was he?
He was super-cool looking!
For real?!
Nozomi!
Whoa, that was a jolt...
You gotta hold on tighter!
You've fallen in and out
of so many groups...
Falling is pretty much
the only thing you're good at.
It's not my fault!
This bus is way too shaky!
Listen when someone gives you advice!
Yeah, yeah...
One "yeah" is enough!
Yeeeeaaaaahhh...
What's with that answer?!
So, did you get Mr. Destiny's name?
No, he ran off too fast.
I hope I can meet him again.
The Pretty Cure of Hope is Born!
Thank you. Due to a Student Council meeting,
I will be late today.
Minazuki-senpai, good morning!
Good morning.
Plenty of time!
Thank goodness.
Good morning!
Good morning, Karen.
Oh, I thought she was saying hi to us.
Yeah, you're delusional.
The Student Council President, Minazuki Karen-senpai,
and her best friend,
Akimoto Komachi-senpai...
...are admired throughout
the entire school, right?
They wouldn't have anything to do with us.
Natsuki-san!
Will you help us out in next week's match?
And play basketball for us
the week after that?
Wait, she's supposed to play tennis for us in two weeks!
Okay, okay, okay... I get it already.
You sure are popular.
Sorry. Will you go on ahead, Nozomi?
Sure.
Hey, hey... If you all talk at once, I can't understand you.
If you don't take turns,
I won't understand a thing you're saying.
I'm gonna find what I wanna do soon!
I'm totally gonna find it!
You can't just wait around.
You have to find your own path yourself!
I-I'm sorry for startling you!
No, it's okay.
Wait, what?!?
You were on that poster!
Umm... Umm...
I'm Kasugano Urara.
Urara-chan! Wow, for real?!
An actual celebrity!
Lemme shake your hand!
Are you filming today?
No, I'm a new student here.
Eh? So you've enrolled at our school?
Is that a script?
Cure Heart 9
Are you going to be in a TV drama?
Yes. It's just a small part, though.
Being an actress must be so amazing.
No, I've still got a long way to go.
I can't call myself an actress yet.
So then, if you'll excuse me.
Give it your best shot!
I'll be rooting for you!
I'm Yumehara Nozomi, a 2nd-year!
If you've got any questions,
feel free to ask me!
All righty! I'm gonna find what I wanna do too!
I'm going to be helping out in
the sports clubs' "prisoner's base" match.
I'll be practicing after school for it,
so go on home without me.
Roger! I'll come cheer you on at the match!
What're you gonna do besides cheering others on?
Eh?
Did you find something you want to do?
Last week you joined
the handicrafts club, right?
Well, umm....
I couldn't thread the needle right,
no matter how hard I tried.
And the week before last,
you joined the theater club.
I kinda fell over and broke the set,
so they banned me.
And before that,
it was the wind ensemble...
Whenever I heard the music, I fell right asleep.
It's not a laughing matter! Man, you keep rolling from one thing to the next.
But... I just can't find what I want to do.
Not with that attitude, you won't.
I'm gonna keep searching till I find it!
Fine, fine.
See ya.
I'm totally gonna find it!
Umm...
Can you please be quiet in the library?
Sorry.
Um, where did the man
who just came in here go?
A man?
The only people in here are the three of us.
Nobody else has entered.
That can't be true.
'Cause I saw it. I definitely saw
a guy come in here.
You're Yumehara Nozomi from Class 2-A, correct?
Yup! Wait a sec...
Miss Student Council President, why do you know my name?
I don't just know your name.
Karen's memorized all
the students' names and faces.
Wow, that's amazing!
We've been here this entire time,
so we're sure.
Aside from you, Yumehara-san,
no one else has come in.
Umm, can I look around inside?
Yes, be my guest. If you find a book you'd like to read, please check it out.
Nah, I'm just searching for that man.
Didn't I just tell you nobody came in?
But I saw that person come into the library.
So I'm gonna look for him!
Excuse me.
What a stubborn girl.
What's so funny?
I was just thinking that she reminds me of you, Karen.
How, exactly?
The way she doesn't waver
in her belief of what's right,
no matter what other people say.
Aren't you the same way?
There're so many books!
Well, this IS a library,
so I guess that's obvious.
Huh?
Where'd he go?
What's that?
The Dream Collet!
We meet again!
Yeah. You're that girl from this morning.
Perfect timing. Give that to me.
W-What's with that cold reaction?
I'm really shocked!
Come on, hurry!
Who are you? Outsiders aren't allowed on school grounds, you know!
No, I'm not anyone suspicious.
I was looking for that.
This is a library book!
Only students can borrow it.
No, that book's originally from my world...
Your world?
No... that's... Sorry!
W-What're you doing?
Please, let me have it!
I can't believe this!
How can you embrace, abandon,
and forget a maiden like myself?!
I only did that so you wouldn't fall.
Don't read anything more into it!
That really hurts my feelings,
and I'm not gonna forgive you!
Huh? What's this?
You're so cuuuuuuute!
So fluffy and soft to the touch!
You're squishing me-coco!
Ah, I'm sorry!
Hey, are you a tanuki?
So tanuki really can transform.
I introduced myself this morning,
but I'm Yumehara Nozomi.
Please call me Nozomi, 'kay?
Nice to meet you!
I didn't want to meet you-coco!
What's your name?
I'm Coco-coco.
Cocococo?
COCO!
You're so cute, Coco!
Don't pull on that-coco!
They followed me-coco!
Who did?
The Nightmare Company-coco!
Nightmare?
I found you.
There it is...
The Dream Collet that will grant any wish.
It'll grant any wish?
It won't grant your comapny's
wishes by itself-coco!
Yeah, it is kinda useless by itself, isn't it?
You have to gather
the Pinkies as well, right?
I'll never give you guys the Dream Collet
or the Pinkies-coco!
I'm not following this conversation.
Then I'll take it by force!
What the heck are you?
What was that just now?
If you hand over the Dream Collet,
I don't mind letting you go.
I won't give it to you-coco!
I've got a wish to fulfill no matter what-coco!
With this Dream Collet,
I can restore my homeland-coco!
Coco...
A dream, you say? How worthless!
We finally offer you some kindness, and you throw it away.
A troublesome pest, aren't you?
But don't worry. I'll slice through you
in one stroke with this!
Damn, what's with them?
W-What's this?
Cut it out already.
This has nothing to do with you.
If you hand him and the Dream Collet over,
I'll overlook your interference.
Now, HAND THEM OVER!
No way!
I hate you!
My, oh my... You shouldn't
judge a book by its cover.
I'm really not as evil as you think I am.
Liar! You made fun of Coco's dream!
You're definitely a bad person!
Dreams? Hah! Worthless rubbish!
Dreams are very precious things!
Even if your life is in disarray,
they're important wishes you want fulfilled!
Only horrible people make fun of them!
So I'll never give it to you!
Nozomi...
Ah, I see...
Then feel free to join him in oblivion!
This is going to hurt a lot...
Why did that come here-coco?
A butterfly? Huh?!
N-No way!
A-Anyway, use that Pinky Catch
to transform-coco!
T-Transform with this? What do you mean?
Just make any wish you want
on the Pinky Catch-coco!
Right.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
What the...?
Woah, what's this? What's happened to me?
I can't believe this-coco!
Nozomi, you've become the
legendary warrior, Pretty Cure-coco!
Pretty Cure?
"Pretty Cure," you say?
I don't know what that is,
but you're in my way!
Wha-?
I'm flying, I'm flying!
Whoa, I'm totally awesome!
Looks like I'll have to deal with you first.
Ready? Let's play...
Aaahhhh! A monster!
Dream!
Dream, use the power of Pretty Cure
to fight back-coco!
I can't!
Believe in yourself-coco!
To make dreams come true,
sometimes you have to believe
in yourself and fight back-coco!
Dream, you can do it too-coco!
Dream...
That's right! It's just like you say, Coco.
I'm gonna give it a shot!
Stand back, Coco!
Now, bring it on!
Whoa... I'm awesome!
Dream, behind you-coco!
Come on, give me the Dream Collet.
Unless you don't care
what happens to this girl.
You coward-coco!
Yeah, yeah, I'm a coward...
Now give it to me!
Don't do it...
You have a dream to fulfill, right?
Don't you need that thing to fulfill your dream?
So whatever you do,
don't give it to him.
But Dream, you're...
I'd never lose to someone like this.
Not to someone who...
...makes fun of people's dreams!
I'll never lose to you guys!
That's right-coco!  Take them down with the power of Pretty Cure-coco!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
I can't believe I lost to this scum!!
Cure Dream, huh?
How dare you interfere with my work!
I can't believe this! What just happened?
Nozomi, you did it-coco!
Wow-coco! Incredible-coco!
I don't really get it,
but I'm glad you're happy.
I never imagined that you'd become Pretty Cure-coco.
Well, it's kind of a blur right now,
but I just wanted to save you.
Thanks-coco.
You were able to become Pretty Cure
because you have such a strong heart-coco.
I've found what I want to do!
All right! I'm gonna become Pretty Cure
and grant your wish, Coco!
It's decided!
Really-coco?
Then let's hurry up and gather your partners-coco!
Huh? Partners?
There are five members
of Pretty Cure-coco.
Eh? I'm not the only one?
No waaaay!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Rin-chan, do this
Pretty Cure thing with me!
Sure... Pretty- What?
I think you'd be perfect for it!
You've got great reflexes, and you're so reliable!
Oh? Sounds good to me!
And you eat so much!
I fail to see how that's relevant.
Rin-chan, I choose you! It's decided!
Hey, what are you deciding here?
What the heck is a "Pretty Cure"?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Full Throttle Passion Cure Rouge!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?