I've finally found what I want to do!
I'll become Pretty Cure,
and help grant Coco's wish!
Oh, I just gotta tell Rin-chan right away!
Morning, Nozomi!
Wow, you're early for once!
I had something I couldn't wait to tell you.
Look at this! Ta-da!
A wristwatch. Who bought it for you?
It's pretty cute.
No, no. This is no wristwatch!
Then, what is it?
The truth is, it actually lets you transform...
I... see.
So you go "trans-form!"
And then you transform,
and beat up bad guys and stuff, right?
Exactly! Let's do it together, 'kay?
C'mon.
Just get on the bus.
Hey, wait!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai, ANFO
Encode: K.o.R  Editing, Retiming, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Rin-chan, I'm telling you the truth.
Sure, sure... later, okay?
He's so cool!
Name on board: Cocoda Kouji
I know it's sudden, but I'll be your
interim homeroom teacher as of today.
My name is Cocoda.
Why? Why'd you become our teacher, Coco?
If something were to happen,
I thought it'd be better to be close to you.
Eh? You did it for me?
Coco, do you have feelings for me or some-?
N-No! It's not like that!
That's not what I meant!
Aw, don't be so shy...
You should have just told me-
No! It's for Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure?
Rin-chan! Just the girl I wanted to see!
What are you doing, Nozomi?
Rin-chan, let's do this
Pretty Cure thing together!
Full Throttle Passion, Cure Rouge!
If you have this Dream Collet,
you can make any wish come true.
Really? It can grant any wish?
Yeah.
Can I wish for my homework
to be instantly done?
Just do it yourself!
The Dream Collet isn't complete, so it can't grant any wishes yet.
And we have a bigger problem: Nightmare.
"Nightmare"?
It's true, Bunbee-san!
That was, without a doubt,
the Dream Collet!
That's quite the achievement, Girinma-kun. If it's true.
You might even get promoted.
Promoted? You mean I can finally attend executive meetings?
So, where's the Dream Collet?
Yeah, about that...
What's this? You just said
you found the Dream Collet.
So, why don't you have it?
Of course, I tried to obtain it,
but this thing called
"Pretty Cure" appeared, and...
Stop right there. Excuses are still excuses.
Our project aims to grant
the great Despariah-sama's wishes.
It is for that reason that we exist. And...
...you're not the only employee of Nightmare, either.
There are plenty of other
team members who want to go.
Bunbee-san, I was the one
who found the Dream Collet!
Please let me finish the job!
Please, wake up!!
You'd better get results this time.
Yes, sir!
The Nightmare Corporation will stop at nothing to get what they want.
In their attempt to capture the Dream Collet,
they destroyed my home,
the Palmier Kingdom.
How awful...
We tried to protect the Dream Collet
with all our might.
So, I want to use its power
to revive the Palmier Kingdom!
Got it! I'll do my best
to grant your wish, Coco.
You make it sound so easy.
I've never heard of this "Palmier Kingdom."
Just where is it, anyway?
It's a country that's not located in this world.
What.
So you're saying you're from a different world, Sensei?
Correct! Rin-chan,
you're making this a lot easier!
If Nightmare gets its hands on
the Dream Collet, it'll be disastrous.
We need the power of all five Pretty Cures
to protect it from them.
Okay. Five people, huh?
I'll collect them right away;
just leave it to me!
What's the matter, Rin-chan?
You believe that crazy story?
Yeah... it's true and stuff.
Watch, I'll show you my transformation.
Nozomi, you mustn't transform for no reason!
Are you okay?
What'd you do that for-coco?!
That was too close!
You almost ruined my plans!
Your "plans"?
Yes.
I've decided that my first kiss will be under a Christmas tree
on a snowy Christmas Eve,
with my wonderful boyfriend!
Even though you don't have a boyfriend-coco?
Be quiet, you! That doesn't matter. You've got a dream too, right?
That's a blatant false equivalence-coco!
And what do you mean by that?!
SHUT UP!
O-Okay.
He's the real thing.
Which means... that whole story
was actually true?
Yeah. So, you'll be joining
Pretty Cure! It's decided!
Sorry, but I'll pass.
Why?
I've got other things to do. See ya!
Oh, Rin-chan...
It's no wonder-coco.
It's a lot to take in all at once-coco.
Minazuki-senpai!
Akimoto-senpai!
Is Yumehara Nozomi-san here?
No, she's not. Do you need her
for something?
If she's not here right now,
we'll try again later.
Pardon us.
Why were they here?
All my pondering isn't explaining anything.
The library was in a state of disarray.
But afterwards, it all returned to normal.
As if nothing had happened at all...
If that girl knows something,
I have to force it out of her!
Indeed. I think it'll be fun.
"Fun"?
Something beyond our wildest dreams is happening at our academy.
I get all excited just thinking about it!
You sure are curious.
I prefer "inquisitive."
Owwie!
She just kinda ran off without thinking,
got herself lost, fell down, and started crying.
Even though that kind of stuff always happens to her...
But she seemed so gung-ho
and excited about this.
What should I do?
Worried about something?
Huh? Yeah.
It looks like my friend's
stuck her neck into some weird business.
Oh?
You're saying strange things.
The most important person is yourself.
There's no such thing as friends.
They are illusions.
That's not...
You should just abandon annoying losers.
I can't do that!
What?
Be they friends or not...
I'll erase anyone who gets in my way.
Who the heck... are you?!
I'm here to collect
a little something for my job.
A little something?
The Dream Collet.
One time when we were kids, Rin-chan and I got lost.
Ouchy, ouchy, fly away!
It flew away, so you're okay now.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Okay.
I put one foot in front of the other because Rin-chan was there for me.
Rin-chan is my very best friend,
so I really wanted to be Pretty Cure with her.
I have a best friend, too.
He's the person I get along with the best
and fight with the most.
But we always make up in the end.
Don't worry. If you keep trying,
I'm sure she'll eventually understand.
Because you're best friends.
Yeah, you're right.
What's your best friend doing right now?
He's sleeping in here.
Eh? In there?
My best friend is the guardian of the Dream Collet.
He was badly injured when Nightmare invaded,
and ended up in a deep sleep.
That's why we can't open
the Dream Collet right now.
What can we do?
Is there a way to get it open?
Yes, if we had the power of
all five Pretty Cures.
Okay, I'd better hurry up and collect some partners!
Let's go for it! Yeah!
Thanks, Nozomi.
A Pinky!
A Pinky? What's that?
This way!
That way?
Do you, perhaps, know about the Dream Collet?
No, I don't!
It's so cute~!
That's a Pinky.
To grant a wish, we need to return 55 Pinkies to the Dream Collet.
I see. All righty...
Nozomi!
Rin-chan! You came back after all!
Quit this Pretty Cure thing, right now!
It's impossible for you!
What's wrong, Rin-chan?
It's too dangerous! I met him!
Whom did you meet, exactly?
Watch out!
Coco!
I'll be taking this Pinky, thank you very much.
I'm okay-coco. Saving the Pinky is more important-coco!
Got it!
Don't!
Nozomi, you can't do this! It's too much!
You're always doing these crazy things...
You'll get more than just hurt!
But I've decided.
I decided I that I'm gonna grant Coco's wish, for sure!
Nozomi?
I'll be fine.
Pretty Cure... Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
That's... Pretty Cure?
I don't want to put my friend in danger.
What should I do?
A butterfly?
Nightmare is a results-oriented company.
If I get the Dream Collet,
I'll be set for life.
I'll take it any way I can!
No way!
Huh?
You guys hurt Coco and
destroyed his homeland.
There's no way I'm listening to you!
Nozomi...
I won't give you the Dream Collet!
Pretty Cure!!
Dream, behind you-coco!
Nozomi! Nozomi!!
So you don't want to stand up to such a fearful opponent, eh?
It's for the best. This is what becomes of the fearless and foolhardy!
Of course I'd be scared of
something like this! But...
Scary, scary, fly away!
But, the thing I fear the most...
What really scares me...
...is losing Nozomi!
Hey, how can I transform?
You want to become Pretty Cure-coco?
I don't really want to!
But if I don't do something now, who will?
Please, I want to save Nozomi!
Your strong feelings for your friend
called it here-coco.
Save Nozomi-coco!
Pretty Cure... Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
Rouge...?
There's more than one Pretty Cure?
Dream!
I won't let you interfere!
Move it!
You think you can save her?
If that's all you've got,
you'd be better off running away.
It doesn't matter if I'll be better off!
We've been together since we were kids,
and we've always helped each other,
no matter what!
Rouge...
Is this what they call "friendship"?
Fine, I'll just kill your so-called friend
right before your eyes!
Just lay there and watch closely.
We've always... been together.
And we're going be together from now on!
Don't underestimate friendship!
Rouge, use the power of Pretty Cure-coco!
The powerful flame of a young girl's
pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
Dream, do it now-coco!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams! Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Not again!
Wow, Rin-chan! You were super-cool!
You were like... this, and this!
This Pretty Cure thing is too dangerous to let you do it alone, Nozomi.
So I guess we'll just have to
do it together.
Yeah!
Nozomi, catch the Pinky-coco!
How?
Shake the Catch-coco.
Like this?
Press the button-coco.
Caught it!
Yay! We did it!
All right!
What's with those two?
And what's a "Pretty Cure"?
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yumehara-san, I happened to see it!
Ah, Urara-chan, what did you see?
You can ask me, Yumehara Nozomi-san,
about anything!
Um, what in the world is a "Pretty Cure"?
Ah, that's.... Wha? You saw that?
I didn't transform or anything, really!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Who's that Bubbly Pretty Cure?
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?