Wait! I...
I can't lie about my feelings any longer!
I... really do...
...love you.
Okay, that's enough.
Okay.
Kasugano Urara-chan, you're a 1st-year middle school student, right?
Yes!
That's quite a spirited answer.
Are you having fun at school?
At school?
Urara-chan?
A-Ah, yes, sorry.
Yes, school's always fun,
every single day.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai, ANFO
Encode: K.o.R  Editing, Retiming, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Catch.
Of the five Pretty Cures,
Nozomi is the Pretty Cure of Hope,
and Rin is the Pretty Cure of Passion-coco.
"Hope"?
"Passion"?
That's right-coco.
And the remaining three are
the Pretty Cures of Intelligence,
Tranquility, and Effervescence-coco!
Wait just a second.
I get "Intelligence" and "Tranquility"...
But "Effervescence"? What's that?
What's that?
Who's that Bubbly Pretty Cure?
I'm home!
Nozomi, I'm hungry-coco.
What's this-coco?
It's a cream puff.
Let's try it-coco!
It's sweet and really yummy-coco!
Oh, you're back?
D-Dad, you were here?!
I was sleeping.
Well, it's about time to start making dinner.
Huh? Is Mom gonna be late?
Yeah, it seems her salon
is busier than usual.
You've been up all night, haven't you?
That's not good for you!
There's no rest for a children's book author, you know.
What's this?
I-I-I-I-It's a stuffed animal!
A-A-A-Anyway, look at the TV, Dad!
That girl in the middle is Kasugano-san. She's a 1st-year at my school.
Oh, that's really neat.
D-D-D-Don't you think?
You had one mission, made two trips,
and got zero results.
That will reflect poorly on
your performance evaluation, Girinma-kun.
Evaluation?
I-I truly apologize. You see,
there are now two Pretty Cures, and...
Now there are two of them?
Yes.
Why does that make such a big difference?
Well, that's, um..
Our duty is to grant the great Despariah-sama's wishes.
And for that, we need
to obtain the Dream Collet.
I thought you of all people would understand the importance of this, but...
O-of course I did!
Girinma, why don't you take a little vacation?
I hate falling!
Failures take a fall.
You're up next. I'll leave things in your hands, Gamao-kun.
Yo.
Black tea, please.
Sure, that'll be one million yen.
Har har.
Hmm... "Intelligence" and "Tranquility" I get,
but what is "Effervescence," anyway?
I don't know, but it sounds kinda cool.
"The Pretty Cure of Effervescence"!
For one thing, stop saying
"Pretty Cure" just wherever!
Don't be alarmed, we were just talking about pu-pu...
About pudding!
Yeah, yeah. It was just
a misunderstanding about pudding!
Right, right, just a misunderstanding.
Rin-chan the Passionate just overheated her brain a bit.
That's me, Rin-chan the Pass-
Hey, don't call me that!
Hey, look over there-
Urara-chan!
W-Wait a sec, Nozomi!
Hey, Urara-chan.
You were on TV yesterday, right?
You looked so cute!
Oh, thank you so much for watching it.
Come on, sit down, sit down.
Hold on.
Here you go, thank you very much.
Hmm?
Let me introduce you. This is
my very best friend, Natsuki Rin-chan.
Nice to meet you.
People call her "Rin-chan the Passionate."
Yeah, Rin the Passionate-
Hey, I told you to stop calling me that!
Huh? Why not? It's cool!
I don't want people interpreting "passion" the wrong way!
Those are the two from yesterday.
That's why you shouldn't call me "passionate" in public, okay?
I'm Kasugano Urara.
I have something I want to ask you two.
You two know Urara-chan?
Yeah.
Otaka-san?
Aren't lively lunches like this one nice?
I was worried that you'd always be alone.
Eh, really?
It's fine. I want to rehearse for work during lunch.
Well, if that's what you want to do, okay.
See you later.
So, what was your question?
Oh yeah. You had something you wanted to ask us, right?
Ask me anything and you'll get
a straight answer!
Umm...
What's "Pretty Cure"?
"Pretty Cure"...
T-T-The bell's ringing! Let's go, Nozomi!
Wait, Rin-chan!
We didn't transform or nothin', really!
Get your butt in gear.
Must go faster!
Huh? Yumehara-san?
I forgot my lunch box.
Well, we should be getting back to class now.
Um... is anything wrong?
My mind's made up!
Since you're a 1st-year, you don't know much about this school yet, right?
N-No...
Oh yeah! I'm gonna give you the grand tour right now.
It's decided!
Um, what about class?
Don't sweat it. Let's go.
All right, class is starting.
Huh? Where's Yumehara?
She didn't... come back... after lunch...
I have a... bad feeling... about this...?
Dangit, Nozomi...
Sorry, but please study on your own for a bit.
Ah, I've gotta go to the restroom.
Check them out, Urara-chan!
That friendly spot-billed duck family
is really popular with everyone at school.
Everyone thinks they're cute, but they're paddling frantically under the surface.
Hurry up, Urara-chan!
Please wait for me!
Hey Urara-chan, look at this!
It's really pretty!
No matter how many times I come here,
it never looks any smaller.
It's the Cinq Lumieres Grand Auditorium.
The oldest building in the city, right?
Oh? You knew about it?
Yes, I've admired it since before I transferred to this school.
I will stand on that stage too, someday.
And make many people smile.
That's the kind of actress I want to be.
You're amazing, Urara-chan.
You've had a dream since you were little.
I recently found what I want to do too, but I've still got a long ways to go.
I've still got a long way to go, myself...
My current job is just
a small supporting role,
and it only has one line.
So all that lunchtime script-reading was for that one line?
No. I have to leave for lessons or work
as soon as my classes are over,
So, I haven't been able to get to know
any of my classmates.
Because of that, I've been reading the script by myself.
But that's a necessary sacrifice,
if I want to make my dream come true.
And so, I think I'll just do my best alone.
But you're not alone!
'Cause we're already friends, right?
You've told me all about your feelings,
and we've fooled around so much.
We're totally friends now!
Yumehara-san...
No, call me Nozomi, 'kay?
Sure!
I've got something important
to share with you, Urara-chan.
Tada!
W-What's that?
Yeah, we use these to transform and face off against Nightmare.
"Nightmare"?
That's right. They destroyed a whole country
for their own convenience.
So, my dream is to help restore
that country back to the way it was.
That's your dream?
Yep! And that's why I became Pretty Cure.
Umm... Don't tell Rin-chan, okay? She'll probably get mad.
There you are!!
NO-ZO-MI! What are you doing cutting class?
You're an upperclassman!
How can you corrupt a 1st-year like that!?
Now, now, calm down.
This is no time to be calm!
H-Hold your horses...
I ain't holdin' nothin'.
I wanna get this over with fast.
So, hurry up and get out that Dream Collet.
Urara-chan, run!
Nozomi-san?
Man, what a pain.
Good grief...
What's that?
So, ya know that Dream Collet?
Out with it, NOW!!
Run, Urara-chan!
Come on, this way!
Rin-chan!
I guess we're all out of options.
Nozomi-san!
Hurry up!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
This is... Pretty Cure?
Get 'em, Kowainaa!
Is that coming from the auditorium?
Something's going on at this school.
Karen, we're in the middle of class.
Nozomi-san!
Urara-chan, make a run for it!
But...!
Hurry up, this way!
I ain't gonna let you...
...run away!
Go, save yourself-coco!
Urara-chan, you've got to escape!
But...!!
Stop your whinin' and GO!
You two're killin' me here. Would ya just get that Dream Collet out already?
'Cause if you don't, I ain't gettin' paid
for this part-time job!
We'll never hand it over to you!
We need the Dream Collet
to get Coco's country back to normal.
I made a promise to Coco!
You're so annoying.
If ya don't cough it up,
you're in for a lot more pain.
I've go to hurry... hurry up and call for help, or else...
Nozomi-san!
You're amazing, Urara-chan.
You've had a dream since you were little.
Oh yeah. You had something you wanted to ask us, right?
Hurry up, Urara-chan!
But you're not alone!
'Cause we're already friends, right?
Nozomi-san...
Nozomi-san, Nozomi-san!
Tsch, if ya ain't producin' it,
I got no choice.
Maybe I should ask HIM instead?
What?
W-Wait!
Ya think I'm gonna wait...
just 'cause you told me to!?
Coco!!
Stop it!!!
Huh?
Urara-chan?
Let go of Nozomi-san and Rin-san...
LET THEM GO!!
That...
...can't be!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
Effervescence was... her?!
The Pretty Cure of Effervescence, Cure Lemonade.
Eh? What is this? I don't even...
Nobody ever told me
there was three Pretty Cures!
First things first: I'll finish these two off!
I can't let you do that!
Release my dear friends!
Lemonade...
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
Now's our chance!
G-Get 'em, Kowainaa!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
What the hell? They ain't
payin' me enough for this.
Urara-chan, you did it!
Yeah, about that...
So you're the third Pretty Cure.
Yeah.
I'm Coco-coco.
You became a Pretty Cure because of
your strong effervescent feelings-coco!
Oh, so that's why she's
the Pretty Cure of Effervescence.
You think?
I've got a lot to explaining to do-coco. Right after...
...you and Nozomi serve detention-coco!
Whaaa...?
Of course-coco! That's what you get
for skipping class-coco.
Aww, no way!
Got it. Nozomi-san and I will be together, right?
Why are you so happy about it?
Urara-chan, from now on...
We'll be counting on you!
Right, I'll do my best!
Yes!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Akimoto-senpai, will you be a Pretty Cure with us?
Pretty Cure? What's that?
We transform, and protect the Dream Collet!
Oh my...
You'd be perfect as
the Pretty Cure of tranquility!
Thank you. That sounds like a very interesting story. I'd like to read it too!
No, no, it's not from a book...
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The Tranquil Cure Mint!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?