This one, please.
Sure.
"The Seven School Mysteries - Robert A.H."
Please make sure to return it
within one week.
Thank you very much!
Hey, did you hear that
this library might be cursed?
Cursed?
After sunset, you can hear loud voices and the sounds of a struggle.
No way...
For real! I heard it from
a girl in the class next door.
This is completely hopeless.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai, ANFO
Encode: K.o.R  Editing, Retiming, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Thank you. I'll be going now.
An evil spirit in the auditorium?
And it attacked some students?
I heard it was a monster
on a rampage in the library.
No, it's definitely an evil spirit
in the auditorium!
So scary...
Good morning, Komachi.
Good morning.
Those strange rumors about evil spirits and monsters sure are spreading fast.
Yes, they are. I heard students
talking about them in the library, too.
Would you care to discuss the issue
with me at lunch today?
Where?
You totally need sugar with fried eggs.
If you start your morning with
sweet fried eggs, you'll have energy all day!
I wish I could go go to sleep at night
wrapped in fried eggs!
You mean like a fried egg futon?
Give up on that idea
before you get all sticky.
Can I have them just as a blanket?
Hey, aren't fried eggs supposed to be salty in the first place?
But a salty futon would be scratchy,
and I wouldn't be able to sleep.
Whatever, I can tell this
conversation is a dead end.
So, what do you think of
Nozomi's loony lifestyle?
I like my fried eggs with ketchup!
Um, that's not the question here.
Anyway, I'm still hungry.
I overslept this morning,
so I only finished half of my breakfast.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Now there're three of them.
Kasugano Urara-san, the 1st-year who works in show business.
When did they become such good friends?
The Tranquil Cure Mint!
You called for me?
Yes, I called. You see...
Is this about the Dream Collet?
You're quite well-informed, Arachnea-kun.
The time is at hand for us
to obtain the Dream Collet,
which we need to grant
Despariah-sama's wishes.
I've heard the rumors.
However, Girinma-kun and Gamao-kun have both failed.
In addition to being unable to finish
his mission, Gamao-kun has disappeared.
Just leave this important duty to me,
instead of that irresponsible Gamao.
Not even Girinma is on my level,
let alone Gamao.
Well, I think you should be fine.
However, three individuals
called "Pretty Cure"
are attempting to interfere
with our mission.
Whoever they are, they won't be a problem.
I am an elite among Nightmare's elites.
I expect results.
Just leave it to me.
Okay, that's enough for today.
Finally, lunch time!
Yumehara, Natsuki, will you come to
the guidance counseling room with me?
Oh yeah, can you invite that 1st-year named Kasugano, too?
Urara too?
Excuse us.
I've been waiting for you. Thanks for coming.
So what's up with this?
Why'd you bring us here?
You may always be in your teacher form
while we're at school...
...but isn't this a misuse of your authority?
I can finally relax-coco.
It's so tiring to stay in that shape-coco.
Well, what did you want?
Out with it, already.
A girl's lunch break is short, you know.
Meaning: we want to eat our lunches, and soon.
Let's eat!
What else would I want to talk about-coco?
Listen carefully-coco!
But I'm starvin'!
Ignore us and go on.
You still need to find
two more people-coco.
Two more?
Hurry up and search for the Pretty Cures of Intelligence and Tranquility-coco.
Yeah, I got it.
The Pretty Cure of Hope,
The Pretty Cure of Passion,
and the Pretty Cure of Effervescence.
Three of you are gathered-coco.
That just leaves
Intelligence and Tranquility-coco.
Basically, you need to find the Pretty Cures
who have the traits you're missing-coco.
Yes, we might be lacking
in intelligence and tranquility.
I want to gather all five of you quickly,
so that I can release
my precious friend-coco.
Pardon us.
Oh, it's just you three?
Um, yeah! Kinda...
You can't just take over the guidance
counseling office to eat your lunch.
Did you need something from us?
I have something I want to ask you three.
So in other words, you think
we have something to do with
the disturbances that everyone's been talking about?
According to the
Student Council's investigation,
numerous students have seen you three
near all the scenes of the disturbances.
Ah, maybe...
Nozomi!
Oh, that's...
So you do know something, don't you?
No, not really.
As Student Council President,
it's my duty to find out the truth.
Now, please explain yourselves properly.
Even if we explained...
Karen would just like to find out
if you know something or not.
Would you like to join us?
H-Hey, Nozomi...
Join you?
Minazuki-senpai, Akimoto-senpai...
I think you'd be a perfect fit!
Nozomi, just give it a rest!
Since Minazuki-senpai is
the Student Council President,
she must be crazy intelligent.
And Akimoto-senpai has a...
how to describe it...
You just get this
tranquil feeling from her, right?
I see!
Massive fail.
Umm, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Could you explain it
more simply, perhaps?
Keep this between us,
but the truth is that we're Pretty Cure.
"Pretty Cure"?
We transform to protect
the Dream Collet from Nightmare.
Will you please join us?
Please!
Are you trying to fool me with
some deranged made-up story?!
It ain't made-up!
It really is true!
I can see why you wouldn't believe it,
but it's the truth!
I'm going to be thoroughly investigating you three.
Let's go, Komachi.
That sounds like a very interesting story.
What sort of author wrote it?
Please tell me more
about it next time, okay?
Hey, wait!
Why didn't they believe us?
Because it's too abnormal for normals to believe.
But I won't give up.
I'm gonna attack them again.
It's decided!
Tell them all you want,
but they won't believe you.
Student Council President
Minazuki-senpai is especially...
Especially what?
How should I say it? It's like we live in
completely different worlds, you know?
But don't those two fit "Intelligence" and "Tranquility" perfectly?
Well, I guess so.
But isn't it kinda rude?
She's operating under the preconceived notion that we're the culprits.
Though technically, we are.
What do you think, Urara?
I think lunchtime's over, isn't it?
Oh noes! I didn't get to eat all of my lunch...
Hello.
Good morning!
What are you writing?
"Meeting in Progress"
I think we should move on to the next item.
Kasugano, what are you doing here?
I just wanted to talk with Minazuki-senpai,
the Student Council President,
but it seems she's in a meeting right now.
Where're Nozomi and Rin?
Rin-san's got club practice, and Nozomi went to the library to see Akimoto-senpai.
There's a Pinky somewhere around here-coco!
Hurry up and catch it-coco!
Huh? What's this?
What should I do?
All right-coco! You caught it-coco!
This is a Pinky?
You're trying to become a novelist?
That's awesome, Akimoto-senpai.
I've loved books since I was little,
and I read every day.
So I thought it would be nice
to write some myself.
Wow! I always fall asleep whenever I read a book.
However, there's a big difference between reading books and writing them.
I've sent submissions to contests,
but they've always been rejected.
People laugh at me, and tell me
that I'll never become a novelist.
Lately, I've been thinking it's hopeless, and that I should just give up.
You can't give up!
If you've finally found your dream,
you can't just give up on it so easily!
It doesn't matter if they laugh,
or what they say.
If you believe in yourself and keep at it,
I'm sure your dream will come true someday.
Yumehara-san...
Ah, sorry.
Actually, I've only recently
found out what I want to do.
So, you see... I'll be there to support your dreams, Akimoto-senpai!
It's decided!
Thank you.
I feel somewhat refreshed.
Great! When you're chasing your dreams,
a positive attitude is
the most important thing, right?
Hey, can you continue that story you were telling earlier?
"Earlier"?
That story about transforming into Pretty Cure.
What kind of author wrote a story like that?
But like I said, that's not fiction,
it's non -fiction!
Prepare yourselves, Pretty Cure.
So you're saying that you want to protect that Dream Collet from Nightmare
and make Coco-san's wish come true, Yumehara-san?
Exactly! Do you believe me now?
More or less. But, Karen won't believe such a story so easily.
Owww!
What's going on?
No way, you're...
My name is Arachnea.
I'm an illustrious envoy of Nightmare.
Now, hand over the Dream Collet!
Who's she? What does this mean?
Something's appeared-coco!
Nightmare is on the move again-coco!
What'd you say?
Akimoto-senpai, hurry!
It's futile.
I said to hand it over now!
We'll never give it to you!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
"Pretty Cure"? She was telling the truth?
Interesting.
If you're a match for Girinma and Gamao, just how strong might you be?
Let's play a little bit.
Akimoto-senpai, hurry up and run!
Must go faster-coco!
That goes without saying.
But even if I weren't exhausted from practice,
I wouldn't be able to go any faster!
There wasn't anyone at the library, either.
So where could they have gone?
Stop-coco!
Down there-coco!
A dead end?
What should we do?
Akimoto-senpai, please hold on to me tight!
Like this?
Not bad, not bad...
But this is as far as you go. Hm?
Nozomi!
Akimoto-senpai, you're okay too?
Rin-chan, Urara!
Hurry! Transform and save them-coco!
Transform?
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
I can't believe this.
Now that all three of us are here, it's our turn!
You don't get it, do you?
No matter how many weaklings gather,
they're still nothing but weaklings!
Now, out with that Dream Collet!
No way, never!
I'm not going to give away my dream that easily!
You girls have no right to dream!
Dreams are nothing more than illusions!
I'll make you all descend into the depths of despair!
Illusions?
That's... that's not true!
What are you complaining about?
Those without power cannot even dream.
You should just stay silent
and let others trample over you!
That's... just not right!
Quiet, you.
Akimoto-senpai!
Heh, those who prattle on about dreams
have no real power.
It hurts...
Akimoto-senpai has power!
Huh!?
I've seen it!
She's always writing while she's working at the library!
No matter what anyone else says,
she keeps working on her novel!
Anyone who tries that hard totally has power!
Yumehara-san...
I'll never forgive anyone who
makes fun of Akimoto-senpai's dreams!
Shouldn't you be more worried about yourself?
That's enough of this. Kowainaa!
Be careful, you three!
Yumehara-san listened to
my dream and didn't laugh.
She said she'd support me.
I want to support her dream, too!
That's the spirit-coco!
You have a way with words-coco!
Komachi, your strong feelings
have called the butterfly-coco!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
Cure Mint!
Now there are four Pretty Cures-coco!
It doesn't matter how many of you there are! Get them!
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Awesome, Mint!
I'm next!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
Dream, now!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
You did it-coco!
Tsch, how am I going to report this?
What do we do?
What were they doing underground?
We heard some really loud noises...
And weird voices, too.
So they're the ones causing all the ruckus?
So it WAS you three, eh?
No...
You see...
Finally made it out.
Komachi?
Karen...
What in the world are you doing?
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Haha! We've finally found the fifth!
The Pretty Cure of Intelligence has got to be...
Minazuki-senpai, right?
Didn't I already tell you I wouldn't do it?
Wha? Don't be like that...
You still have all that sweet-bean jelly from that old classic shop, right?
Are you fishing for sweets?
I brought these for Komachi, not for you!
Eh heh, was I that obvious?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The Qualifications of Pretty Cure
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?