It's the Student Council President, Minazuki-senpai!
Student Council Office
Good morning.
Good morning!
I made a schedule for the Student Council entry in the yearbook, but...
Could you please check it for us?
Um, I'm not sure about
everyone's assignments...
Don't fret about it, I'll check it later.
Thank you very much!
I guess if I want something done right,
I have to do it myself.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yummy! How 'bout this one?
You sure do eat a lot, Nozomi.
Is there a problem?
Heck no! You think I'd lose to you?
May I join you, perhaps?
Please, be our guest.
Wow, so extravagant!
My mother makes it for me every day,
but I can never eat it all.
If you'd like to...
Thanks for the food!
Komachi-san, let's eat together every day from now on!
Hey now...
This is no time for a relaxing meal!
Hurry up and find the fifth Pretty Cure-coco!
Someone's gonna find you first, Coco!
Why are you in that form?
I like to take it easy
during lunch break-coco.
So you tell other people to go search,
while you're relaxing?
But still, Coco-san is correct.
We have to find the
fifth person quickly, right?
In order to protect the
Dream Collet from Nightmare,
we need to assemble five Pretty Cures.
Komachi-san, you catch on quick!
Komachi just soaked everything up like a sponge-coco.
There's just no end to my curiosity.
Another Pretty Cure, huh?
Um... I'm Hope.
Passion is Rin-chan.
Effervescence is Urara.
And Tranquility is you, Komachi-san.
That just leaves Intelligence, right?
If you need intelligence, just ask me!
Otaka-san!
I may not look like it,
but I'm a Level 5 abacus user!
Note: Level 10 is the lowest, level 1 is the highest.
I calculate all the bread prices at the shop in my head.
Ahh, I see!
And what do you see, exactly?
Is there something I can help you with?
S-Sorry! You're just a bit too late.
Oh, really?
That's too bad...
Oh, yeah!
You forgot your change,
Nozomi-chan! Here's 2 million yen.
Come again!
And here I thought she'd work out.
You were serious?
By the way, you're not with Minazuki-senpai today?
Karen often has Student Council meetings,
even during lunch break.
It sounds tough.
Karen has a strong sense of responsibility.
If Minazuki-senpai joined us in Pretty Cure,
I think she'd be really reliable.
But she's already turned us down once.
True, Karen has a stubborn side to her.
If she says "no" once, she probably won't
change her mind so easily.
I see.
All righty then! In the meantime,
let's all go to Minazuki-senpai's house!
It's decided!
The Qualifications of Pretty Cure
Arachnea-kun...
How do you plan on explaining this failure?
I was just caught a bit unawares.
I didn't think there would be
four Pretty Cures.
There are four now?
How many of these Pretty Cures are there?
I'm the one who will get yelled at for your mistakes, you know.
Please, give me one more chance!
I will definitely finish this job...
Why don't you... take a short vacation?
Looks like I'll have to
go out there myself.
It's so tough having such worthless subordinates.
M'lady, today is the day
your mother will call. Let us go.
Sure.
President!
What is it?
Um...
If you don't mind, could you come to the yearbook meeting with me?
I'm not sure I can explain the schedule we decided on today to everybody.
I'm sorry, it seems I'll be late today.
Please go home without me.
Yes.
It's true; if I want something done right,
I have to do it myself.
I-Is this a castle?
It's huger than the school!
It seems like no one is home.
Huh? There's no one there?
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
Akimoto-sama, you have quite a number of friends.
Is Karen home?
It seems that m'lady is busy with
Student Council business, as usual.
Please, come and wait inside.
Sure.
He called her "m'lady"!
I'd love to be called that, just once...
Awesome! It's 100 times bigger than the school grounds!
You're way off-base!
It's obviously 98 times bigger!
You two are like peas in a pod.
Yup, we sure are...
Excuse me.
Thank you very much!
Just call me if you need anything, okay?
Sure! Sorry for bothering you!
Goodbye.
Huh?
Minazuki-san, your Student Council meeting has run this late?
Yes.
Must be hard running the Student Council.
But if you try and do everything by yourself,
you'll never have any time to do the things you want to do.
Thank you for the advice.
Now if you'll excuse me...
That girl really needs someone she can talk openly to.
Sakamoto-san, I'm sorry I brought
so many people here without warning.
Oh, no. I'm sure m'lady
will be pleased by it.
I'm home.
Oh, Komachi?
Sorry for intruding.
Hello!
Yumehara-san... Natsuki-san...
And even you, Kasugano-san.
Your house is awesome.
How many hundreds of people live here?
Hey, now...
Right now, the only people living here
are m'lady and myself.
Huh? Just the two of you?
M'lady's mother and father are,
for most of the year,
on tour performing around the entire world.
On tour performing?
Yes. Master plays the piano,
and Madame plays the violin.
They are world-famous musicians.
But it must be lonely to live in
a place like this by yourselves.
I'm not really lonely or anything.
Could this be a picture of your parents?
That's so cool!
They almost look like musicians!
He just told us they were!
And this is your mother, right?
She looks just like you, Minazuki-senpai!
Don't you mean that Senpai looks just like her mother?
Eh? Is that how it works?
Yeah! It's because she's her daughter.
I see...
Oh yes, I brought something.
Bean jelly from my family shop.
Thanks, as always.
I'll go and cut the bean jelly she brought.
Please wait at the gazebo in the garden.
Gazebo?
The arbor. This way, please.
I've been jelly of this mansion.
Yummy!
Eating bean jelly in such
a wonderful garden really feels special.
It really is delicious.
Isn't it? Komachi's family has run a Japanese confectionery shop for more than 100 years.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You shouldn't wolf down food like that.
Got 'em!
Hey, those are mi-
But it seemed like you didn't want them.
Who in the world wouldn't
want food that tasty!?
You ate them...
M'lady.
Yes?
Madame is on the phone from Vienna.
My mother?
Thank you.
Mother?
I'm sorry I couldn't
answer your call earlier.
Yes, I'm doing well.
No, I'm not lonely at all.
Please, don't worry about me, and do your best at your job.
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Thank you, Jiiya.
No problem.
Sorry for making you wait.
Was that your mom?
Yes.
Anyway, why did you come here today?
Surely you had some reason?
Yeah...
U-Um...
Actually, we wanted you to become Pretty Cure, Minazuki-senpai!
That story again?
Didn't I say I had no interest in that?
Well, I realize what I'm trying to tell you is hard to believe,
but it's all true!
The disturbance at the library the other day was our doing!
After that, there were some tremendous sounds coming from underground, right?
That was me!
Why're you playing along with them?
Fine. If you see this, will you believe us?
Your turn.
I was gonna suffocate-coco!
Sorry 'bout that...
Now, do your job.
Man, you should treat me better...
1, 2, 3-coco! 2, 2, 3-coco!
They're really making stuffed animals well these days, aren't they?
I'm not a stuffed animal-coco!
I'm Coco-coco!
Well, it's more normal not to believe it.
We became Pretty Cure
to collect the Pinkies
so that we can restore Coco's homeland.
That's right-coco!
Pretty Cure? Coco? Pinkies?
I don't get any of it!
There's a Pinky near here-coco!
Ah, there it is!
Komachi, catch it-coco!
Okay.
See? If you do this,
the Pinky comes closer.
The Pinky?
What?
No one in my section
could complete such a simple task?
Who is that person?
Give us back the Pinky!
Oh, so this is yours?
You snooze, you lose!
Now, hand over the Dream Collet to me.
No way!
We ain't giving it to you!
Oh? You're courageous
enough to oppose me?
But how long will that courage last?
What's that?
Watch out!
Karen, hurry!
Everyone, transform-coco!
"Transform"?
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of
the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
This is Pretty Cure?
It was true.
I'm on a tight schedule, here.
Can't you just give me
that Dream Collet now?
No way! We'll never let you have it!
You won't give it to me?
Damn you.
Don't make me use
more power than I have to!
Since it doesn't seem like you'll ever give me the Dream Collet,
I guess I'll have to be serious with you for a bit.
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Pretty Cure, watch out-coco!
What's that?
Hurry, hold out your hand-coco!
Transform into Pretty Cure and save them-coco!
Stand up against that monster? I can't do something like that!
Hurry up and save them-coco!
I guess if I want something done right,
I have to do it myself.
No, I'm not lonely at all.
It's always like that.
I guess if I want something done right,
I have to do it myself.
The butterfly disappeared-coco!
Karen...
...couldn't...
...turn into Pretty Cure?
W-What?
Why?
Can't I do anything?
It's coming.
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
Dream, do it now-coco!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Whatever.
I'll just have to settle for this Pinky for today.
What should we do?
He got away with that precious Pinky.
I understand that you were
telling me the truth.
However...
From what you've seen,
can't you tell that I can't help you four?
Do not ask me again.
No, we'll be back.
'Cause I want you to become
a Pretty Cure too, Minazuki-senpai!
I'll keep attacking,
as many times as it takes!
It's decided!
Catch ya later!
H-Hey, Nozomi!
Why... couldn't I... become...
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
You're the only one who can be
the fifth Pretty Cure, Minazuki-senpai!
Didn't you see what happened?
I can't become Pretty Cure...
You can! You totally can!
Along with everyone else...
Yumehara-san... Thank you.
I also... I also want to help all of you!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Pretty Cure 5, All Assembled!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?