Karen, m'lady...
Pardon me.
Is it that plane, perhaps?
Maybe that's the one that Mom and Dad are on.
It might be.
Will they be home soon, I wonder?
Yes?
Oh, never mind.
Hey, isn't it almost tea-time?
Let's have tea!
Right away.
Why?
Why couldn't I save them?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai
Encode: K.o.R  Editing, Retiming, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
I never should have counted on my worthless subordinates.
After all,
I stole this Pinky so easily
when I went out there myself.
Just take a look at this!
Somebody praise me!
Next I'm gonna get
that Dream Collet, you'll see!
And defeat Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure 5! All Assembled!
Ah... We lost...
That Pinky was captured by Nightmare.
Don't worry about it!
We'll be able to save the Pinky
once we have all five Pretty Cures together.
Huh? Five? Are you still trying
to get Minazuki-senpai to join?
'Cause that's what I decided.
I also think that Minazuki-senpai should become Pretty Cure.
I'd thought that Karen would be able to become Pretty Cure, but...
But she couldn't transform.
We should just give up
and search for someone else.
I...
...am totally against that!
Because I've decided that the fifth
Pretty Cure will be Minazuki-senpai!
Huh? Where are you going?
To Minazuki-senpai's place.
Karen is in a Student Council
meeting at the moment.
Jiiya-san!
Student Council Meeting Room
Meeting in Progress
Even the first-years are adjusting to the school.
So students that arrive late are even more noticeable.
Therefore, I think that we should arrange a warning system for tardy students.
I hope that the Student Council can provide its full support!
Ms. President?
Minazuki-san?
I-I'm sorry!
Well, um, uh...
I'm sorry.
Oh, my... Wonderful.
Thank you for treating me to
this delicious tea.
Oh, don't worry about it.
We're all just waiting
for Minazuki-senpai, after all.
I see you've found a way to "fill" the time.
But it's good, and I'm hungry.
Yeah, but anything tastes good when you're hungry.
Will you please become friends with m'lady from now on?
When you girls were with her the other day, she seemed to be truly having fun.
It had been a while since I had seen m'lady enjoy herself that much.
That long?
Yes.
Ever since she was young,
m'lady has held herself back
out of consideration for her parents,
who are often on performance tours.
Yes, Father!
Mother!
I've got Jiiya with me, so I'm fine.
Do your best at your concert, okay?
Everyone was focused on
Master and Madame's performances.
She thought it unacceptable to monopolize their attention for herself.
So m'lady hid her loneliness,
and could not display her own true feelings.
But, when you all were with her,
she truly seemed to be having a good time.
That's what I saw.
Everyone, from now on...
What are you doing?
Minazuki-senpai!
M'lady!
Why are you here, Jiiya?
Well, you see...
Um... We just ran into Jiiya-san when he was waiting to pick you up,
and asked him if he
wanted to wait with us.
It's funner with more people!
Don't make me repeat myself.
I can't be of any help to you!
Just leave me alone.
Did she have to be so rude about it?
You, be quiet.
Karen...
Jiiya, please wait in the car for me.
Of course. If you'll excuse me.
Umm.. One way or another,
we really need your help, Minazuki-senpai!
Please... Become Pretty Cure with us.
I wasn't able to become Pretty Cure.
Didn't you see it?
The butterfly disappeared.
Why is Minazuki-senpai no good?
If you don't truly wish to become Pretty Cure, you can't.
So then, Minazuki-senpai didn't really want to become Pretty Cure.
That's not true!
I wanted to save you all,
from the bottom of my heart!
In the end, if I want something done,
I have to do it myself.
In any case, more visits won't get you more results.
I can't become Pretty Cure. Pardon me.
Karen!
You totally can!
Nozomi...
Minazuki-senpai!
W-Wait just a second!
You shouldn't have any business with me anymore.
I've got plenty of business!
Please.
I want you to become Pretty Cure,
no matter what!
Why? Why me?
That's because...
'Cause I already decided.
The fifth Pretty Cure will be you!
Doesn't the sight you witnessed
affect your decision?
I'm not worried about that at all.
And anyway, we had a lot of fun the other day.
You're so mature and refined, Minazuki-senpai.
You're really dependable.
And like, totally different from me.
But, I also found one thing
we have in common.
What's that?
We both really love our parents.
That's what I thought after
seeing you get that phone call, Senpai.
You told them to take care of themselves,
so that they wouldn't worry about you.
Jiiya-san said the same thing.
That's...
There's no way a person
as caring as you are
can't become Pretty Cure, Minazuki-senpai!
You can do it, for sure!
Yumehara-san, you certainly are
full of mysteries.
Huh?
Let's put my ability to become Pretty Cure aside.
Please, feel free to come over
whenever you'd like.
Sure! I will!
Can I come and play, too?
How about a game of
"Pick Up the Dream Collet"?
Can I come and play, too?
How about a game of
"Pick Up the Dream Collet"?
Give back the Pinky!
The Pinky, huh?
You talking about this thing?
Pinky!
Over here!
There's a Pinky nearby-coco!
But, something's not right-coco!
Watch out!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
Pinky...
Nozomi!
You okay-coco?
Yeah.
How dare you do this to Nozomi!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
You're gonna pay for this!
Wait...
That Kowainaa is a Pinky!
I knew something wasn't right-coco!
You two hide over here.
He's using our own
Pinky against us...
What should we do?
My, oh my... You won't fight when you're up against a Pinky?
I can't waste any more time.
My salary's above the overtime exemption threshold, you see.
I want to get this job over with!
Dream!
You won't last long in the Legendary Warrior business with that kind of productivity!
They're all...
What? Is that all you've got?
And now, for the final blow...
That's enough!
Karen, you can't-coco!
Please, stop this!
Minazuki-senpai?
It's too dangerous!
What's with you?
Please, don't hurt them anymore!
I won't let you lay a finger on those girls!
And what can a powerless person like yourself do about it?
I may not have any powers,
but I want to save my friends all the same!
'Cause I already decided.
And when we're all together, it's really fun.
Even if I can't become Pretty Cure,
I want to be with them!
I want to help everyone!!
Eh? What are you blathering about?
Minazuki-senpai.
Please, stop already.
Karen...
Run away!
A butterfly appeared-coco!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
I transformed... into Pretty Cure!
W-What's this?
There are five Pretty Cures now?
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
I already figured there'd be five of you!
Look at that. If we remove that mask,
the Pinky should return to normal.
Yes, I see!
I'll hold back the Pinky.
Okay, then I'll yank off the mask!
I'll go with Rouge!
I'll hold that guy off to give you all more room to work.
All right, just leave that guy to me and Lemonade.
Let's go!
Yes!
Pretty Cure!!
The effervescent power of
a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
The earth tremors of
a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
There!
The rock-crushing power of
a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
The powerful flame of
a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
Not good enough!
The great potential of
a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Damn you!
What am I supposed to put in my incident report?!
The Pinky!
Thank goodness!
Mint, catch the Pinky-coco!
Thank goodness; we managed to catch the Pinky.
All five of the legendary warriors of Pretty Cure are gathered-coco!
See? It happened
just like I said it would.
Thanks to you.
There's no going against Dream.
I'm really glad.
You finally did it.
Everyone, let's do our best together from now on!
Yes!
Hello? Oh, Mother?
It's not anything too important.
But I was wondering when you'll be able to come back to Japan.
Oh, it's nothing really.
I was just thinking... that I missed you.
Really, it's nothing major.
Good morning.
Good morning. See you later.
Nozomi, use the boost to get through!
Wait for me!
Yumehara-san, you're late.
Hey, cut me some slack here!
No.
Can't you overlook this? Aren't we buddies now?
That and this are completely different matters.
Can't a girl get a little
favoritism around here??
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Finally, all five Pretty Cures are gathered-coco!
Now we can meet the guy in the Dream Collet-coco!
Good for you, Coco.
I've been waiting so long for this-coco...
So, let me introduce him to everyone-coco! This is Nuts-coco!
Whoa, he's not the friendly type.
Is he really your best friend?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The Best Friend, Nuts, Appears!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?