The day has finally arrived-coco.
All five Pretty Cures have been gathered.
And now, we can open
the Dream Collet-coco!
We'll be able to meet
the guy sleeping in here, too.
It's all because of you, Nozomi-coco! Thank you-coco!
And she's still asleep-coco.
Nozomi, wake up-coco!
This calls for drastic measures-coco.
Nozomi?
Nozomi, if you don't hurry, you're going to be-
Good morning.
Um... Since the alarm clock didn't wake her up, I...
I am sorry. She really is a heavy sleeper,
so please, carry on.
Who was that?
Nozomi!!
What're you yellin' about, Mom?
There was just a really cool-looking...
I mean, really suspicious-looking guy
trying to wake you up!
Ehh?!
What're you talking about?
There couldn't be any guys here, right?
But, he said "Good morning" to me.
Maybe you were just dreaming?
You must be seeing things...
Seeing things...
Yeah, that's right, I just saw some things.
Things that weren't there.
Nozomi, what's with that stuffed animal?
Ah... this is...
Ah, Mom, aren't you going to be late for work?
I have appointments this morning!
I already made breakfast for you, so make sure to eat it, okay?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
So Coco's best friend
is in the Dream Collet?
That's right. If we have the power of all five Pretty Cures,
we can release him from the Coll-
Kasugano-san, I saw you on TV yesterday.
Natsuki-san, will you be
a ringer in our next game?
Everyone, thanks for waiting.
Not a problem. Now, with everyone here-
Minazuki-senpai, thank you for
the advice you gave me the other day.
Akimoto-senpai, I read that book
you recommended to me.
It was really, really, good!
Man, we can't talk like this...
Today's Student Council Agenda:
No Chime Day
School Beautification
Volunteer Work
Mental Health Checkups
Today's Student Council Agenda:
No Chime Day
School Beautification
Volunteer Work
Mental Health Checkups
This is the first time I've ever been in the Student Council room!
Someone could come in here at any time,
so let's do this quickly.
And now, without further ado,
let's meet Coco's best friend!
Move the five Pinky Catches close to the Collet-coco.
Nuts!!
The Best Friend, Nuts, Appears!
Nuts!
I've missed you so-
Why'd you do that-coco?
What were you thinking?
You shouldn't open the Dream Collet in front of so many people-nuts!
That's still no reason to hit me-coco!
It seems like they're fighting...
Are they really best friends?
By the way, who are these people-nuts?
They're Pretty Cure-coco!
Pretty Cure? These girls-nuts?
We've failed at recovering the Dream Collet
and at preventing their team from assembling.
I can't report that to the higher-ups!
That would be dereliction of duty, wouldn't it?
Isn't reporting to us part of your job?
Bunbee-san.
It's important that subordinates do their jobs properly.
If something happens in the field,
and the person responsible does not report it to us accurately, it's quite a problem.
K-K-Kawarino-san, you haven't changed a bit...
(= o-kawari no naku)
I-I am truly sorry!
I was late in reporting that we had more delays than we anticipated.
The legendary warriors,
Pretty Cure, correct?
You know of them?
"When the power of despair begins to shroud the world,
Warriors of Light wielding
the power of hope shall appear."
That's how it goes.
"If you knew already,
you should have told me sooner!"
That's what you were thinking just then, right?
No, that thought never crossed my mind!
Well, regardless of the legend,
we must obtain
the Dream Collet for our Despariah-sama with all possible speed.
Do you understand this?
Yes! Loud and clear!
Good luck with that, then!
Kawarino thinks he's hot stuff...
I've been waiting for you to call me.
Girinma-kun...
It's you people's fault that I just got chewed out!
Sorry...
I didn't have any intention of using you again,
but I called in a few favors to let you keep working.
This time, defeat Pretty Cure and get me
that Dream Collet, no matter what!
Yes! Of course!
Student Council Meeting Room
By the way... Who is the leader of Pretty Cure-nuts?
Leader? We haven't really decided on it.
But it's got to be the Student Council President, Karen-san.
But you were the one who
invited me to be Pretty Cure.
Shouldn't you be the leader?
No way... I've never even been a class rep,
let alone a squad leader.
But you were the first person to become Pretty Cure, weren't you?
Without Nozomi-san here, I don't think
any of us would have become Pretty Cure.
Well, it was your idea
in the first place, so...
Just do it, Nozomi.
Oh? Okay, then maybe
I'll take a crack at it?
This isn't some game-nuts!
I can't trust you-nuts!
But Nozomi and the others...
...managed to get the Catches
with their powerful wills-coco.
These girls aren't necessarily our allies-nuts.
They might just be protecting the Dream Collet
so they can grant their own wishes-nuts!
Nuts!
Now look here...
There's no reason to insult us like that.
Nozomi-san would never deceive anyone.
She just wants to help you two.
I don't remember asking
for your help-nuts.
Even if you didn't ask her to,
it was Nozomi who got you
out of the Collet.
Shouldn't you be thanking her first off?
Class is starting.
If we don't go back to the classroom...
Jeez, what's Nuts's problem?
Sorry.
Nuts said some terrible things.
Please forgive him.
He's been through a lot,
and he can't trust anyone anymore.
What all's he been through?
Well...
Nuts is your best friend, right?
Yeah, that's the way he is...
Then I'll try my best to be
his friend too, okay?
Nozomi...
So won't you cheer up, Coco? Bye!
Nozomi is such a good girl...
That's for sure.
Hey! Wait for me, Nozomi!
My mom saw Coco in my room this morning.
For real?
I-Is everything okay?
I think I managed to trick her, but...
Wouldn't it be better if Coco-san stayed at someone else's house tonight?
This is a problem...
Yes, it is. And in the future,
we'll also need a place where we can discuss things privately.
So, we need to make
a Pretty Cure Secret Base, right?!
Stop yelling "Pretty Cure" everywhere!
Oh yeah, what about
your mansion, Karen-san?
You've got lots of rooms, and lots of snacks!
You're only after the snacks.
But it will be a problem if we are constantly interrupted.
I don't particularly mind, but my house is far away from the school, and...
Oh, that's right! There is a warehouse
near here that my family no longer uses.
All right! Let's go there right away!
It's decided!
Man, nothing ever brings you down.
It was originally a factory.
But it's not in use now.
It's so big!
You could have a concert in here.
I think this might be too big for us to use.
Really?
Well, there's a small
storeroom nearby, but...
There's more?
This place might be good.
If we clean it up, we could use it.
But isn't it too small?
It's bigger than my house.
All right. Everybody,
clean your hearts out!
It's decided!
It's so dusty...
Rin-chan, you're covered in dust!
You look dumb, haha!
Now you've done it! Wait right there!
No way!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!!
Wait, wait, wait!!
If we don't hurry, it'll get dark out.
Oooh... Hold it right there!
Oh? How cute.
What?
Look, it's a lizard.
Get away! Don't bring that thing
any closer to me!
But it's so adorable...
How long are you going to pout?
You help out too, Nuts.
Just leave me alone-nuts.
My face is all black.
Hey, don't just leave your Pinky Catch
lying around-nuts!
You have to be careful with it-nuts!
Ah, sorry.
That's right. There's a Pinky in it, too.
Wait, there's a Pinky in the Catch-nuts?
Yeah!
Why didn't you tell me-nuts?
Get that Pinky transferred into the Collet-nuts!
"Transfer"? How?
Point your Catch towards the Collet-nuts.
Like this?
Pinkies... sure are cute.
Nuts.
Nozomi and her friends were able to turn the Pinky back to normal.
Nuts...
Coco!
Coco! Nuts!
Ah, it's been a while.
Today, I will take what I came here for, you see?
N-Nuts!
There's even a Pinky inside of it. Thanks.
Give the Dream Collet back!
Nozomi!
If you want it,
then force me to give it back!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Five of them? Sheesh, they've multiplied...
Nuts!
Wait!!
Nice to see you,
ladies of Pretty Cure!
I bid you welcome.
This is all that you five can muster?
That's not going to cut it.
Nuts, are you okay?
Did you say, "Nuts"?
So you were the one who opened the gate?
The Palmier Kingdom was protected by the Five Lights.
Even with the all the power of Nightmare, we couldn't get inside.
However, when we disguised ourselves as an injured Pinky,
some guy named "Nuts"
opened the gate for us right away.
Nuts...
How dare you trick me-nuts! You're cowards-nuts!
I think it was quite clever, myself.
I have to thank you.
We were able to get into your kingdom
because you opened the gate for us.
Which gave us a chance to obtain the Dream Collet.
If you're going to blame anything,
blame your own stupidity.
It wasn't Nuts's fault!
Nuts didn't do anything wrong!
You took advantage of Nuts's kindness,
so it's all your fault!
Nuts wanted to help that Pinky.
Don't you understand that kindness?
And you're the ones who destroyed Coco's and Nuts's kingdom, right?
Why're you blaming other people for what you did yourselves?
The one who got tricked
is the one at fault.
No, it's obviously the one doing the tricking!
You noisy brats!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
Nuts, what is your dream?
My dream-nuts?
My dream is to restore
the Palmier Kingdom-coco.
Don't you have the same dream-coco?
We'll help you!
Let's grant your wish together.
Pretty Cure...
Your wishes will never be granted.
I'll defeat Pretty Cure,
take the Dream Collet...
...and be promoted to management!
You're in a dead-end job-nuts!
And why is that?
Pretty Cure won't lose, and they'll never give you the Dream Collet-nuts!
Impertinent little...
What?
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
I'll remember this!
Yes!
This is really the storehouse
from yesterday?
Karen, did you renovate the place?
I didn't do anything.
Wow, what's this?
Who in the world...
If we'd only relied on you girls,
who knows when we would've finished cleaning?
So I tidied it up instead.
Ahh, what a hottie...
Rin-chan, is he your type?
N-No way...
Who are you?
That's Nuts.
You cleaned this place up all by yourself?
That's awesome!
Not really.
In any case, please let us live here while we're staying in this world.
Can we?
Of course! No problem, right?
S-Sure...
That's Nuts?
I think he could have
a good career in showbiz.
Yeah, he's wonderful...
But he is Nuts... right?
What're these?
Boxes to hold your Pinky Catches.
When you take off your Catches,
store them in there.
Thank you, Nuts.
We'll take good care of them.
Um, can I look around the store a bit?
Sure, go ahead.
All right!
This one's pretty...
Which one, which one? Ooh, it is pretty!
What?
Let's trust in Pretty Cure, okay?
Yeah, I guess. Nightmare is dangerous, so we'd better be on our guard.
You should act grateful to them.
By the way, I prepared a room
that you can live in here.
What'll you do?
A room? Thanks.
Coco, we're going to restore
the Palmier Kingdom.
Nightmare won't have their way with us.
That's the Nuts I know!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Karen-san sure is strong-willed.
More like hard-headed, you mean.
Everyone looks up to her
as Student Council President.
Well, I don't.
Rin-chan, what's the matter?
Is something up between you and Karen-san?
Not really. We're the BESTEST of friends...
This is NOT a good sign.
Pretty Cure might be in big trouble!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Compatibility: Zero? Rin and Karen.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?