If you wanna decorate a store, then tulips are just the thing!
Oh, Natsuki-san!
I see you've also brought some flowers?
Yeah. You did too, Minazuki-senpai?
Those are Chinese bellflowers, aren't they?
That's right! You sure know a lot.
Well, I know a little, at least.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Tada! I brought green tea!
And I brought black tea!
Excellent. I brought snacks to go with that tea.
Wha, those snacks look yummy.
Isn't this great, Nuts?
They all brought us gifts for the store.
It's not like I asked them to.
They can just do whatever.
You're not fooling anyone.
Look! Aren't the flowers pretty?
I know, right? Red flowers definitely suit this store the best.
Really? Blue flowers also match nicely.
But blue has a kind of gloomy image...
Blue is a color that calms the heart.
It aligns perfectly with
the shop's atmosphere.
Ehh?! But red flowers are better at brightening up the store in a flash!
My family runs a flower shop,
so just trust me on this one.
Now, now... Both kinds of flowers
are lovely, aren't they?
That's right! Blue flowers, red flowers...
They're all beautiful!
So you said your family
runs a flower shop, Rin-san?
That's right. I grew these tulips myself,
with tender loving care.
So if you ever want any flowers,
just ask me.
Sure!
Karen-san's Chinese bellflowers
are pretty too.
These flowers were grown in
the greenhouse at my home.
It allows us to enjoy
summer flowers before their season.
Eh?! That's awesome!
Summer flowers are supposed
to be seen in the summer.
What was that?
Why don't we set that aside and have some tea, okay?
We agree!
Compatibility: Zero? Rin & Karen
The hot water is ready.
Yaaay! Snacks, snacks!
Should we have black tea or green tea?
Hmm, let's go with black.
But shouldn't green tea be served with Japanese snacks?
Black tea works fine too.
But Japanese snacks and
green tea have a long history.
Their flavors are specifically designed to go together, you know.
So green tea is far more appropriate.
That past stuff doesn't matter.
I feel like black tea right now.
But they go better with green tea!
Isn't that right?
I think they go with milk just fine!
It's okay. Don't worry about the snacks. Just drink whichever you feel like.
T-That's it! Let's just mix green tea, black tea, and milk together!
It's decided!
Um, what?
Before you have your tea,
I have a request-coco.
A request?
All of you girls, aside from Nozomi,
still have Pinkies in your Catches-nuts.
Transfer them into the Dream Collet
right away-nuts.
You want us to transfer the Pinkies?
Roger that!
After you, Minazuki-senpai.
Oh, thank you. It's nice that you
call me "senpai" like that all the time.
It's the natural thing to do.
Even though I'm your senpai
in the Pretty Cure department...
Did you say something?
No, nothing at all.
Like this?
You did it-coco!
Rin-chan, Karen-san, hurry up and
transfer yours so we can have tea!
V-Very well.
Better do what Nozomi says, right?
A-After you.
No, after you.
No, no... After YOU.
Please, you go first.
Arachnea-kun! ...is not here yet.
Arachnea-kun?!
Yes?
Welcome back.
Arachnea-kun, did you enjoy your vacation?
If you're referring to the holiday I took
by falling into that hellish basement,
I've had my fill.
Now, give me my assignment!
At least you're motivated.
I wonder if you're the only one I can trust with this job.
Of course I am!
If you let me handle this task,
I will bring you immediate results!
Your track record says otherwise.
Get me the Dream Collet, and do it quick!
If you don't, our superiors
will hold us both responsible!
You don't have to tell me that.
If you understand, then get it done.
Yes, sir.
"Pretty Cure" has gotten in our way,
which has seriously delayed our plans.
I sincerely apologize for my complacence in this matter, Despariah-sama.
The field is an unpredictable place.
Without supervision from above,
the subordinates cannot do their jobs.
I understand, my lady.
I shall remove all obstacles,
and take direct control over the situation.
All we do serves to grant
your great wish, Despariah-sama.
I have but one wish.
To use the power of the Dream Collet
to grant myself eternal life and youth...
...and rule this world with absolute despair.
I take it you understand?
Yes! Thoroughly!
Ehhh? You haven't said a word to
Karen-san since yesterday?
What's the big deal?
We never talked before all this either.
If she ain't gonna speak to me,
I ain't gonna speak to her.
Aww, Rin-chan, you're so stubborn.
So your tastes in flowers are a LITTLE different...
...your tastes in tea
are a LITTLE different...
So you've both got bad timing
when reaching for the Collet. So what?
I think that's plenty.
Yeah, it's pretty awkward.
But it'll be a problem if you don't talk.
Like, when we become Pretty Cure, and-
I keep telling you not to say "Pretty Cure"
when we're out in public!
But you just said it too, Rin-chan!
Only because YOU said it first!
It's strange...
Eh?
Even though you two argue, it's not a big deal.
So why did things between you and Karen-san end up like they did yesterday?
Now that you mention it...
...that's a good question.
It doesn't make
a bit of difference.
I've always felt like Minazuki-senpai and I just don't get along.
It's not that we don't get along.
It's just that you have to be so blunt with people like Natsuki-san.
But still, you don't have
to be so stubborn.
She's the stubborn one!
Don't you know that?
What I was saying was right.
It's not about being right or wrong.
Everyone has their own opinions on these things.
Then I guess she and I have
a fatal difference of opinion.
Wouldn't you call that
"not getting along"?
H-Hey, Rin-chan... Nice weather we're having today, huh?
Hmm? Yeah, it's good weather for sports.
But the weather forecast said that it would rain this evening.
W-What should we do?
L-Let's just keep at it, Nozomi-san...
Right.
Ah, Karen-san, that's a cute
little lunchbox you have there.
Really?
I'm surprised you can survive
on such a meager diet.
Maybe I shouldn't have said that.
Now that you mention it, Karen might not eat fast, but she does eat a lot.
Wow, I didn't know there was anyone who could eat more than me.
Man, this is really becoming a pain-coco.
Neither Rin-chan nor Karen-san are ever going to give in.
What should we do?
Well, I guess it's only natural-coco. You gathered them all, Nozomi,
but most of us are just
new acquaintances-coco.
That's true, yes.
It was unlikely that the five of us would've already known each other well.
It makes sense that Intelligence and Passion would have low compatibility.
But I thought having totally different personalities would make things more fun.
We've got to find something,
anything they have in common-coco!
Something they have in common...
Where are they, anyway?
Well, Karen's at the Student Council,
and I think Rin's at one of her clubs.
They said they'd come to the shop
once they'd finished.
Maybe they'll run across each other
and arrive together!
Something's here-coco!
I've found you, Pretty Cure!
Nightmare?!
There's only three of you?
I'm sure I'd heard there were five.
How convenient for me.
Now, give me the Dream Collet!
No way!
We won't give it...
...to the likes of you!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
Prepare yourselves.
I've got you now!
How pathetic.
Dream, Mint, Lemonade!
Tell the remaining two
to bring me the Dream Collet
if they want to save their friends!
Hrm? Your car isn't here to pick you up today?
I told them I'd be late today,
and thus wouldn't need it.
Done with your activities?
With a little help.
Your weather forecast was wrong,
so we had plenty of time to practice.
Still going to Nuts' shop?
Of course I am.
We've got a big problem-coco!
W-Why'd you startle us like that?!
What happened?
Dream and the others have been captured by Nightmare-coco!
And they said to bring the Dream Collet if you want to save them-coco!
We can't let them have it!
Let's go save them!
Don't have to tell me twice.
What's the matter? Are you scared?
N-No, I'm not scared or anything!
This way!
I can sense them-coco! That way-coco!
We're close-coco! Almost there-coco!
What is this place?
Be careful-coco!
I've been waiting for you!
Where are the others?!
What, you can't see them?!
Take a good look!
Now then, be good little girls
and hand over the Dream Collet!
We ain't gonna give it
to a creep like you!
Nozomi, Komachi and Urara...
We'll save them all!
I wonder if you can?
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
Passion? Intelligence?
What fools! Do you really think you're a match for me?!
What?!
Curse you!
Heh. No staying power, I see.
We aren't...
...through yet!
Dream, are you okay-coco?
Coco?
Dream!
Rouge, Aqua!
Pay more attention!
I am paying attention!
It looks like they're still bickering.
Yes, although they're
quite synchronized.
Even better than usual?
You brats! How can just two of you
be so damn tenacious?!
Isn't it obvious?
Yeah, it's pretty obvious to me.
What's so damn obvious?!
To Aqua...
To Rouge...
...I can't afford to lose!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
You guys!
Rouge, Aqua!
You saved us!
Don't get too cocky!
You're just a random
gathering of strangers!
There's nothing random about us!
Shut up!
We all have different personalities,
and sometimes we clash with each other.
But there's a reason that
we five are here together!
Because the five of us are one team!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
You'd better remember this!
Yes!
Wow, you two were awesome!
Your movements were
lined up perfectly.
I guess you really do
get along with each other.
It was merely a fluke.
Yeah, just a fluke.
But...
I wanted to save you all, so...
You did pretty well... Rin.
You weren't so bad yourself, Karen-san.
Karen-san, is it okay if I visit your greenhouse sometime?
Sure! Can I stop by
your family's flower shop, Rin?
Ahem... "Flower Shop Natsuki" is open 365 days a year. Come anytime!
They've suddenly become
good friends, haven't they?
They might even make a good duo.
Just like me and Nuts-coco!
We're a duo-nuts?
I don't really think so-nuts.
You're really not fooling anyone-coco!
Oh, that's right! I just figured out what those two have in common.
Some common ground-coco?
Yeah, they shouted the same thing
at the same time:
...I can't afford to lose!
Rin-chan and Karen-san really, REALLY don't like to lose.
Ah, hold on, Karen-san!
What the heck are you doing?!
I just moved them there specifically because they'll get more sunlight!
No they won't! The window's facing south,
so they're better off here!
I'm sayin' that isn't any good!
Over here is better!
They're my flowers,
so let me handle it!
I see what you mean.
Right?
I guess those two still have
a long way to go.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
The new edition of the
Cinq Lumieres News is out.
This is pretty in-depth.
Your Student Council meetings, Rin-chan's club matches...
...Urara's television appearances,
and even stuff about Komachi-san!
Impressive reporting, eh?
But there isn't an article about ME!
Write about me, too!
'Cause I'm in Pretty Cure!
Don't tell her that!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Pretty Cure is Discovered!?
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?