Good morning!
Heya!
Ah, it's Cinq Lumieres News!
Yeah. The school newspaper is well-regarded
for being both entertaining
and informative.
Scoop!
An Idol's
Lunch
~A Conclusive Report on Kasugano Urara-chan!~
What's with this article?!
"Urara-chan had spaghetti,
rice pilaf, and a sandwich...
And Natsuki-san from class 2-A had her lunch box plus four sweet buns.
And Yumehara-san wolfed down
two plates of curry
and four doughnuts
with her tongue sticking out."
What the hell?!
It's totally wrong!
I had melon bread, too.
That's not the point...
Ah, good! I think I look
really cute in these pictures!
Hey, you really shouldn't be happy about this!
Sorry to interrupt...
What the people want to know,
I want to know.
I am Cinq Lumieres News's
chief editor, Masuko Mika!
Masukomi is a Japanese abbreviation of the English term "Mass Communications".
But from now on, call me "Masukomi"-ka!
This week, we're doing a close-up interview with Cinq Lumieres'
first showbiz idol,
Kasugano Urara-chan!
Urara-chan, what are your thoughts?
Um, well...
Come on! We don't have time for some photo-op!
Look here, Masuko-san.
Even if it's for the newspaper club,
do you think it's okay to print
these pictures without permission?!
Quickly and efficiently reporting the news students wish to hear...
...and publishing it without censorship or alteration
is the grand mission of
the Cinq Lumieres News!
Cool! She's so professional.
Why are you so impressed by her?
Urara-chan, what did you eat today?
An extra-large hamburger,
some fried shrimp...
H-H-Hey, Urara! You don't have to answer questions like that, you know.
And an extra-large strawberry parfait!
I said you didn't need to answer.
Let's change the subject.
Are you going on any dates
with a boyfriend these days?
Eh?
So? Do you have one?
W-Well, I don't have a boyfriend, but...
I do have someone I admire!
Eh?! Who is it?!
It's... Yumehara Nozomi-san.
M-M-Me?!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Today it's three bean jam rolls and..
Oh, isn't that topic played out?
Otaka-san, please don't surprise me like that.
Readers will get tired of
repetitive stories.
Yes, that's true.
But there's not much else..
Don't be so sure!
You could evaluate my fashion sense~!
Perhaps some other time.
I see.
The Student Council President,
a Library Committee member,
An all-around sports star, a popular idol...
And then there's... Yumehara-san?
Why are those five together, anyway?
Isn't it nice to see friendships that cross class lines?
Well, four of them are well-known throughout the school,
but they hardly have any connections to each other, let alone Yumehara-san.
There must be something to this!
My reporter senses are tingling!
Nozomi, will you get me another plateful?
Why me?
'Cause you're... the leader?
Oh, right.
Say, we're missing a straw.
I'll bring one back for you.
Being the leader sure is hard work!
It's just like being
Student Council President.
You have to answer to and work for all the  students.
I see.
We're counting on you for
that plate and straw, leader!
Yumehara-san is their leader?
How could she lead those four superstars?
Pretty Cure is Exposed!?
Ah, I had so much fun yesterday.
But it's back to the grind today.
Man, my stomach hurts.
So, Kawarino-san dropped by earlier.
What do you think he said?
Who knows?
He said that if we don't get the Dream Collet
from those Pretty Cure losers,
then "every one of you is fired!"
Of course, I understand it's not entirely you guys' fault,
but I fear our window of opportunity
is steadily closing. What do you think?
Bunbee-san, you don't have to
cloud the issue with veiled threats;
I will get you that Dream Collet,
without fail!
Headline: "Extra Edition Scoop!
These five girls' suspicious relationship!?"
Looks like we're in the news again...
What does she mean by, "The suspicious relationship between these five"?
The Student Council President, Minazuki Karen,
and her best friend, Akimoto Komachi.
All-round sports girl, Natsuki Rin, and
the up-and-coming idol, Kasugano Urara.
Why has a relative nobody,
Yumehara Nozomi, suddenly gotten so close to those four school-wide celebrities?
My source will reveal all!
That's so obviously Otaka-san.
According to my source,
you five have lunch together almost every day.
And in my interview,
she said that you got together right after
the mysterious poltergeist disturbance.
There must be some kind of connection between these two events!
She's on the right track.
More like almost right on the money!
Don't say any more! We'll be ruined!
Ms. President,
please give me a clear answer.
What is the connection between you five?
Well, you see..
Oh, Ms. President? What happened to that sharp tongue of yours?
Please give a more direct answer
to my question.
For the sake of truth,
no matter what authority we go up against,
we will investigate thoroughly!
That's our motto here at the Cinq Lumieres News!
If you refuse to answer,
I'll try asking someone else.
You were called the "leader,"
so what exactly are you the leader of?
That's of, um... the Allies of Justice!
Hey, hey...
Answer me seriously!
Nowadays, Allies of Justice, are like...
...such an antiquated expression.
Cocoda-sensei is with them?
Eh? Sensei disappeared!?
Are you sure you should transform back to normal out here?
It's tiring to stay in that form-coco!
That voice... Who are they talking to?
There's a Pinky near here-coco!
Nozomi, catch it-coco!
Dang it, I can barely see anything.
Is this a store?
Hey, they moved!
Are they dolls? Pets?
Ah, I can't take this any longer!
Masuko-san?
Sorry to interrupt...
What are you all doing in here?
W-What are you saying?
We're not doing anything unusual.
We're just browsing in this shop.
All five of you?
Well, that's... just a coincidence, right?
Uh, yeah, what she said.
That sounds good enough, right?
Nozomi!
But it is unnatural that all five of us
would happen to meet here.
Urara...!
Something's not right here.
What kind of store is this?
It sells jewelry, accessories,
and other fashionable little trinkets.
Do you like those sorts of things, Masuko-san?
Well, they are pretty cute,
but just now I thought I saw
these dolls moving.
Ah, umm... these things?
They're really well-made, yeah.
If you do this, they move... See?
H-Huh?
Do it-coco...
See? They're automatic talking, fighting dolls! Pretty cool, huh?
They're amazing! Amazing toys!
So where are the store's employees?
Eh? Gee, it looks like they're not here right now.
Not here?
What kind of store lets customers walk around unsupervised?
Don't that strike you as strange?
That store is majorly sketchy!
U-Um, excuse me.
I'm from the Cinq Lumieres News.
Do you, perhaps, work at that store?
Are you an acquaintance of those girls?
Uh, yeah... sort of?
Hmm... Well, isn't that convenient?
Masuko-san?!
Hey, what're you... I'm against violence!
Masuko-san!
She's in there-nuts!
This place gives me the creeps.
If you don't hand over
the Dream Collet peacefully,
this girl will pay the price!
Masuko-san...
Who is this woman? What does she mean by "Dream Collet"? What is it?
Be quiet.
All right, you girls!
Give me the Dream Collet, now!
Hurry up and save her-coco!
Right!
No! We can't do that
in front of Masuko-san!
But at this rate, Masuko-san will...
What should we do?!
I said fork it over, now!
I might not get a chance like this again...
Don't try to interfere!
Ah, my camera!
Is it really that important to you?
How about THIS?!
Now's your chance-coco!
Now's your chance-nuts!
Right!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...And the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Today, I will finally get my hands
on the Dream Collet!
W-Who are those those girls?
Crap, Masuko-san saw us!
We've got more pressing matters on our hands!
But it might be a problem...
Mint!
Now, stop resisting and give me the Dream Collet. If you don't...
What's this? It hurts...
Masuko-san has nothing to do with this!
Then hurry up and bring out
the Dream Collet!
No way!
Are you sure about that?
Masuko-san!
It's no good. We can't fight back!
She's going to pay for holding Masuko-san as a hostage!
Aqua, you and I will take her on.
I'll do what I can.
I'll support you two.
Leave the Kowainaa to me.
I'll go with Rouge!
What?
Come and get us!
Curse you!
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Lousy Pretty Cure foiled my plans again...
Here.
Ah, thank you very much for saving me.
U-Umm...
Who are you? What are your names?
U-Um, our names aren't worth mentioning, per sé...
We're called "Pretty Cure," though.
Don't tell her that!
Sorry, no pictures.
Eh?!
Okay, let's go.
Something is definitely going on in this town.
And who were those girls?
This is gonna be a huge scoop!
My reporter senses are tingling like crazy!
U-Umm...
Did five girls just go by here?
I don't know. I didn't see them.
Did you need something?
Whoa, he's beautiful...
Is something the matter?
No. There was just a really
scary monster over there...
And those five girls drove it away.
They were truly incredible,
so I wanted to do a report on them.
Five amazing girls?
Driving away a scary monster?
Miss,
Yes?
there are some things in this world you're better off not knowing.
Shouldn't you just forget about it?
O-Okay!
Yesterday's events are gonna be
all over the news.
You know what they say:
pics or it didn't happen!
It's still bad news for us.
Let's check out the damage...
Is there a scoop about Pretty Cure?
Apparently not.
Huh?!
"Super Hottie Found in the Town!!"
That's Nuts.
It's Nuts all right.
I didn't know we had
such a hot guy in this town!
The Cinq Lumieres News will be reporting on this man from now on!
We'll be counting on everyone's support!
So she couldn't care less about us?
I'm kind of upset now.
But isn't this for the best?
Oh my...
Huh?!
Five girls...
...drove off a suspicious person?
Wow, what a tiny article.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
This is so bad! I've never seen anybody but us shopping at Nuts House!
Now that you mention it,
you're right...
Which means it's time to start our Nuts House advertising campaign!
My, that's an excellent idea!
So, what will this campaign consist of?
U-Umm... we'll make it up
as we go along!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Save Nuts from Starvation!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?!