I wonder what snacks
she's brought today...
I'm back!
Good afternoon!
Hiya!
Good afternoon! Greetings.
Oh, it's you guys.
What's with the attitude?
Is this how you treat all your visitors?
No, I just thought
you might be customers...
Nuts!
Nuts!!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
It's delicious-nuts!
You were just hungry?!
I was worried you were sick-coco!
Coco, you live with him,
but you didn't even notice?
Two days! Nuts hasn't eaten anything
in two whole days!
I'd throw a fit if I just missed one meal.
So that's just... cruel!
I tried to make him eat, but Nuts...!
These mamedaifuku are just so yummy-nuts!
Go ahead.
A-All right...
I can't pay you for them right now. But once I get the money,
I'll be sure to pay you back-nuts!
Don't worry about paying me.
I brought them here for everyone to enjoy.
I'll definitely pay you back-nuts!
There's no reason for you to treat me-nuts!
See-coco? That's what he said
every time he refused
to eat the cream puffs
I offered him-coco.
But why haven't you eaten for two days?
Maybe he was so busy
he didn't have time to eat?
I'm guessing not.
What is it?
I've... never seen any.
Any what?
I've never seen anyone
in this shop, except for us.
Yeah, now that you mention it,
customers don't come in here-coco.
Does that mean...
...this store...
...hasn't had a single customer?!
Save Nuts from Starvation!
I have reviewed your report.
I'll just go and get us some tea-
All of your previous paperwork confirms
our expectations of you, Bunbee-san.
What?
These reports contain nothing but failures.
I envy how you're able to sit here and relax
without a care in the world.
I kind of have to sit here...
Well, if it were me,
I'd have run away in shame long ago.
Ah, speaking of running away.
Who was that again... Gamao-san?
I haven't seen him lately.
According to your report, he was defeated by Pretty Cure, and has yet to return.
Shall I assume he's quit?
Well, I'm sure he's some where-
Well, we can't have that!
If you don't properly manage your subordinates, then...
I am very... sorry.
It's all Pretty Cure's fault!
What?!
If they hadn't interfered...
I woulda gotten the Dream Collet,
and gotten paid!
I coulda stuffed myself
with all the food I wanted!
Pretty Cure, I'll never forgive ya!
Damn it!
You sell such cute accessories, too.
Then why don't you get any customers?
Don't worry-coco!
Good merchandise like this
will eventually fly off the shelves-coco!
At this rate, your projected sales
for the foreseeable future are zero!
It doesn't matter how good the product is
unless you get the word out!
If you want success,
you need advertising, promotions,
and sales techniques!
Looks like somebody's gone and flipped Urara's personality switch.
That's an up-and-coming idol for you.
Her words pack a punch.
Quite persuasive.
But how should we advertise-coco?
Hmm... How about we show
this stuff to people at school?
I bet they'd love it!
Alrighty, let's all do some advertising!
It's decided!
Okay, I'll recommend this one along with this one-coco!
This one too!
However.
You can't bring accessories onto school grounds.
I was... going to warn them about that as one of their teachers-coco.
Okay.
But if we only bring a few...
I suppose we can't.
But then how can we advertise?
You can still advertise
without the actual product.
How?
Well, we just, umm...
Word of mouth, and the mass media.
Word of mouth...
...and the mass media?
Yeah! I was, like, totally surprised!
I saw it too!
I told you!
Seriously?
And then do you know what he said?
What, what?
Good morning!
I can't really say...
Don't hold back, just tell us already!
Hrm, should I or shouldn't I~?
Good morning...?
Ah, good morning!
Good morning!
Now, go on, go on...
Fine, if you insist.
So what happened next?!
Well, you see...
Hm? Akimoto-san, did you want something?
Huh? Well, umm...
I wanted to ask...
do you girls like accessories?
He actually said that?!
I totally heard it, really!
Yup!
Wow, I never could have believed it.
I wish he'd said that to me.
But now that I think about it,
it would never work...
I'm kinda jealous you thought that up!
Komachi...
You're not being forceful enough!
Student Council Meeting Room
So it's my belief that we should take quick, effective action to improve the situation.
Then, shall we each individually consider
the merits of Komachi's proposal,
from the perspective of our roles?
Yes.
No objections.
Then, this concludes our special Student Council meeting.
But I'd like to add one thing.
Huh?
I found this shop that sells
the most beautiful accessories!
I highly recommend it!
Why don't we all go visit it?
Okay?!
Karen, I think that's a bit too forceful.
Huh?
No good?
No way!
But it's a really great accessory shop!
Can't you use the power of the press
to help us, Masuko-san?
No, no, and no!
The Cinq Lumieres News will not print publicity for some random business!
I don't think it's a problem.
Sensei?
Don't newspapers normally
have advertisements in them?
Mine doesn't!
The Cinq Lumieres News practices fair-and-balanced journalism!
We cover current events and provide social commentary.
I'll never, ever, ever, EVER
allow advertising!!
I guess nobody's going to come.
Looks like we screwed up our advertising.
That's not... No, you're right.
I'll... pay you for these five when I pay for yesterday's,
I promise.
Don't worry about it.
It's too early to give up!
Huh?
Because we still have Urara to fall back on!
Oh!
That's right!
Indeed.
Yes!
What are you watching?
Urara-san's going to be appearing on this live TV show.
And she's wearing
one of your necklaces, Nuts.
Why a necklace?
Whenever a celebrity wears some accessory on TV,
lots of people rush out to get the same one.
That's right! It's perfect publicity for you!
But she hasn't appeared at all yet.
Hi! Greetings!
Here she comes!
Where's Urara?! Show us Urara!
Thanks for that rumor report. It was great, wasn't it?
But what store has the best selection at the lowest prices?
She's tiny!
Urara-san's in there somewhere?
Where is she, again?
There she is! In the middle row...
One, two... five people from the left!
Ah, there she is! There!
You can barely even see Urara,
let alone the necklace.
We're almost there! I'm sure they'll do
a close-up on her necklace!
A close-up...
That's all, folks!
Next week on this segment...
What you've been waiting for!
The tour of high-class hot spring resorts!
Look forward to it!!
Next week on this segment...
What you've been waiting for!
The tour of high-class hot spring resorts!
Look forward to it!!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors:
Sorry, I wasn't any help at all.
No, you did the best you could, Urara!
But what should we do now?
Just forget it.
We're bound to get some customers,
sooner or later.
I hope.
Why don't we hand out some fliers?
Fliers?
We could make promotional fliers, and then distribute them in town.
Back when my grandfather
was running our shop,
our customer counts suffered a decline.
Really? I thought you were a respected, long-standing confectionery.
That "respected" status
made him complacent.
He thought that that alone would bring in customers.
"Complacent"?
That's right. If you're running a shop,
you not only have to have good products,
...but you also have to work to make sure
that people know about it.
My grandfather realized this,
and they started handing out fliers.
And then the customers
started flooding back!
Even those delicious mamedaifuku...
need publicity?
You're just as brilliant as ever, Komachi.
Yeah!
Okay, let's make fliers! It's decided!
Nuts House - Filled with cute accessories!!
It's done!
It's hard to hand out fliers  when we only have one.
I have to draw this many?
Right.
You want to help?
Wow, that's amazing!
Awesome! It copied them all
in no time flat!
The Pinky Clearkuman's specialty is calling in customers.
That includes making fliers.
Thank you so much, Clearkuman!
Please take one, it's for Nuts House! It's a cute accessory shop!
Please take one!
It's a lovely shop, so please come visit!
We're from Nuts House!
Please come visit us, okay?
Excuse me!
Thank you very much!
They're all working so hard for us.
For you, Nuts.
They're just a bunch of busybodies.
Please, drop by our shop!
Please.
Sure...
Nuts House! Thanks!
It's okay to window-shop, just visit us once!
Hm? Hey, you over there...
Why not buy a nice accessory for your girlfriend?
Whachoo talkin' about?
I don't got any money!
And it's all your fault
that I ain't been paid.
If I had the cash to spare...
...I'd rather blow it on food instead!
Eh?! You're...!
Nozomi!
There ya are, Pretty Cure!
Hey, they're multiplyin' again!
You're that guy from before.
Hah! So we meet again!
Who was he, again?
Don't remember.
Ya don't remember me?!
Ah, screw this! You're all goin' down!
Ow...
Rin-chan?!
Wha-?! Ah, Nozomi!
Are you okay, Rin-chan?
I'm okay, but... Where the heck are we?!
Pretty Cure!
It's all you girls' fault,
'cause you done me wrong!
Huh?
What?
I'll show you what it feels like...
...when you're forced to go hungry!
Gobble them all up!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Sorry 'bout that!
It's okay.
When you see everyone else eating,
it only makes you hungrier-nuts.
I can understand how he feels-nuts.
There's no time for sympathy-coco!
Dream!
Are you okay?
Yeah... Thanks.
All this mess is yer fault!
Huh?!
If it weren't fer you, I'da got my pay...
...and I wouldn't be so damn hungry!
I'll never forgive ya, Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
Damn it!
It's all your fault...
...that I'm this freakin' hungry!
All this time, you've just been blaming other people for your problems!
Nuts was starving too.
But he's been handing out fliers,
and working his hardest to change things!
Hmph! Who cares about that?!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
You are...
...such a creep!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Oh sh-!
Damn you, Pretty Cure!
I'll get you next time! Next time!
Please take one!
Ah, here you go!
Please take a flier.
Thank you!
Please take one~!
Here you are!
Here you go.
Would you please take a flier for our accessory shop?
Please take one!
Thank you very much.
Help yourself to one of our fliers!
Okay, thanks very much!
Ah!
It's YOU!
The mysterious super-hottie!! I know your identity!
His name is Nuts!!
He's the manager of
the accessory shop, Nuts House!
It's Nuts.
Nuts again... seriously?
Thank you very much!
Um, everyone...
Don't push!
Yumehara-san, Natsuki-san!
Ah, Masuko-san?
Thank you so much! So you changed your mind about advertising for us?
What're you talking about?
This was a scoop.
A scoop?
This is the kind of journalism that the
Cinq Lumieres News was born to execute!
You understand now?
You're just fangirling.
Ah, don't push,
we're well-stocked with accessories.
Come on, there's no need to rush!
Thank you very much, miss.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Nozomi, there's no reason
to feel so down.
I don't care anymore!
I've got no athletic or academic talent.
It's always been like this. I just get left behind.
You're an amazing girl, Nozomi.
You just need to take things slowly,
and harness your potential little by little.
Will I fly one day, like that balloon?
You will. I promise!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Nozomi and Coco's Hot-Air Balloon
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?