I don't wanna! Lemme go, Rin-chan!
Stop struggling already!
Ooh, Rin-chan, you're such a meanie!
No more than you deserve!
What's going on with those two?
Oh, nothing's the matter with "us."
Nozomi, show them your math quiz.
Okay...
18%?
W-Well...
What a cute number.
Hard test, wasn't it?
Not at ALL! The average score was 80%.
Do you even have an excuse for this?
I don't care if
I'm useless at studying!
Nozomi, can't you be serious about this?
Nozomi-chan, studying isn't everything. But you have to make some effort.
This school's motto is to have fun playing and have fun studying.
Eh? But studying isn't fun at all!
Is this stuff ever gonna be useful for me?
Yes, it will! Curry: 380 yen;
milk: 120 yen; anpan: 110 yen...
...and the total: 6,100,000 yen!
See? I can work it out in a flash!
What's with all
the extra zeroes?!
Nozomi-san, our midterm exams
are coming up. Will you be okay?
Hmmm...
I'll handle it somehow or anothers.
No, you won't! Not if you don't study.
Why don't we all get together to study?
Good idea!
Starting today, we'll all study together after school every day.
Ehhhh?!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai, Aesir
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
I wonder if I'll be able
to remember all these kanji.
Every kanji has its own meaning.
If you remember the meaning alongside
the character, it'll stay in your mind better.
Every line in a script
has its own meaning, correct?
Ah, I see!
I should memorize them the way I'd remember lines in a script.
Karen-san, you aren't going to study?
No.
Karen remembers everything
that's taught in class.
That's why she's always ranked first.
It all comes down to concentration.
Anyone can do it if they remove
their emotions from the situation.
You make it sound so easy...
Try imagining it in terms of the sports you play, Rin.
Isn't this problem easier to understand
if you think of X as your teammates
and Y as your opponents?
I see! This might work out after all!
Whoa, it's a hot-air balloon!
I wish I could ride off
on it to somewhere...
Are you finished already, Nozomi?
Eh?! Ah-
Is there some part
you don't understand?
Hmmm...
I don't know what part
I don't understand!
It's 3:00-nuts!
Time for snacks-coco!
At last!
Stop!
Solve all these problems first.
Ehhhh?!
No way...
Why is Nozomi so against this-nuts?
She's not too good at studying-coco.
Nozomi and Coco's Hot-Air Balloon
This is a progress graph
for this month, Arachnea-kun.
Shocking, isn't it? What's your take?
It appears we've been growing quite impressively.
I presume my promotion is imminent?
What are you talking about?
That's Pretty Cure's part of the graph!
They get stronger
every time we face them.
This  is your team's graph!
I cannot believe this!
Believe it!
Any graph would take a nosedive after all your repeated failures!
And yet you still have the nerve to stroll in here and face me.
Tell me, what's your secret?
I've been exerting
my best efforts, but...!
Your "efforts" don't make
a bit of difference.
Your excuses are nothing BUT excuses.
Let me make this clear:
excuses are excuses, results are results!
Yessir!
Okay, all done!
I'm finished!
Thanks for the...
...food!
So tasty!
You haven't made any progress.
And those are 1st-year problems.
Whatevers. I'll just get Cocoda-sensei to tell me what'll be on the test!
No, you won't!
Nozomi-san, cheating is wrong.
I won't overlook
academic misconduct.
That's something a bad guy would do!
If this were soccer,
you'd get ejected with a red card.
I was only kidding.
I don't think you have
the time to be Pretty Cure.
Perhaps you should take a break from
being Pretty Cure, and focus on studying.
H-Hold on...
If you can't handle your studies,
surely being Pretty Cure is beyond you?
That's not true!
You might be motivated, but your Catch might stop playing along and ditch you.
The four of us can find
a way to handle Nightmare.
Yes, we'll be Pretty Cure 4!
Yeah, that'd be good!
4 has a cool ring to it!
I know, right?
I am gonna be Pretty Cure!
Nozomi, you haven't
solved these problems yet.
Nozomi!
Leave me alone!
Nozomi...
Nozomi-
Shouldn't we go after her?
She'll come running back once she's cooled off.
Perhaps we went too far?
If we weren't that harsh with her,
it wouldn't do her any good.
You really think this'll do her good?
I don't think this will
motivate Nozomi at all.
But if she doesn't study for her tests...
You can't just force someone to study something they don't want to learn.
They'll just resent it.
So what should we do?
Go and search for her?
Coco already went after her.
He did?
Can he reach her?
If anyone can do it, he can.
Back in the Palmier Kingdom,
Coco was beloved by all the people, and held in high esteem.
He'd teach the children,
and counsel those who had worries.
Not just anyone can do it.
He's truly amazing.
What?
That's the first time I've heard you
praise anyone else, Nuts.
Don't tell him I said that.
Anyway, just leave Nozomi to Coco.
Stop following me!
Why?
You're just gonna tell me
I have to study, right?
Leave me alone already!
Where're you going?
Wherever I feel like!
How about over there?
That's called a balloon, right?
Just how far up can it go?
I dunno...
Let's find out!
H-Hey, wait a second, Coco!
Let's go ballooning!!
Wow, it's huge!
It's pretty impressive from up close.
What's he doing?
He's filling the balloon
with air to inflate it.
It floats because of the air?!
It works because hot air
is lighter than colder air.
Heating the air inside with a flame will cause the balloon to rise.
That's so cool!
How high can it fly?!
Want to see?
Yes!
Whoa, what a view!
Hey, there's the school!
The people on the ground
look like specks.
And Nuts House is over there... Ah-
Worried about them?
Not really! They're all focused on
their own studies, right?
I doubt it.
They're worried about you, Nozomi.
They wanted to get you motivated to study;
that's why they acted so harsh.
Well, I know I should be studying, but...
I've never been any good at it.
It took me twice as long to memorize multiplication tables and kanji.
Things that were easy for them
were so hard for me.
I just have no talent.
Question:
Why does this hot-air balloon rise?
Yumehara?
Eh? Let's see...
It floats because the air is warmed up?
Correct!
You got that one right.
Eh?!
You'll naturally remember things you find interesting or emotionally moving.
It's not a matter of "talent."
Oh, really?
Yeah, really!
But I'm not interested in
what's on the tests.
And I always run away from studying.
I guess your balloon is still on the ground, being filled up with air, Nozomi.
My balloon?
The balloon of your potential.
There's so many things for you
to see, hear, and feel...
...and as you learn about them,
that balloon will inflate.
Studying for your tests is just one way
of filling up that balloon...
...so that when you find
a dream of your own, it'll begin to rise.
Will my balloon... really fly?
That's up to you, Nozomi.
I know that a wonderful
future awaits you.
On par with this view.
If I start studying now,
will I be able to pass the tests?
Of course!
But it'll take me a really long time.
It doesn't matter how long it takes,
or how much you get distracted.
And you have lots of great friends to help you along the way, right?
That's right.
Nozomi-san's still not back.
Ah, it's no use! I'm too worried
about Nozomi to concentrate!
Even the snacks aren't as tasty
without Nozomi-san here...
I suppose Nozomi was trying,
in her own unique way.
Perhaps we were too strict with her.
It's not like we don't trust Coco-san, but...
...something just doesn't feel right without Nozomi-san here, so we...
...should go find her?
I'm sure she'll be happy to see you too.
Somehow, I feel like I can do it now.
Coco, you're amazing!
You're the amazing one here, Nozomi.
Eh? I am?
Do you remember the day we met?
All right! I'm gonna become Pretty Cure
and grant your wish, Coco!
It's decided!
Most people wouldn't go that far for someone they'd just met.
Aw, what're you talking about?
I was on the hunt for
something I could do.
And granting your wish is still my number one goal, Coco.
You're very kind...
The wind's getting too strong to continue the ride.
Okay.
Please wait until
I've secured the basket.
Okay!
U-Umm...
I really am grateful to you
from the bottom of my heart.
But you know...
Your own future should be
the most important thing to you.
Your future has infinite possibilities.
So if you find something
you want to do, you should...
...prioritize that over granting my wish.
My progress graph's
about to resemble a hockey stick!
W-What's going on?!
It can't be...!
Did you find her?
No, no luck that way either.
Where the heck did Nozomi go?
Wha-?
What's with that cloud?
It's not normal.
A balloon?
Someone's on it! Nozomi?!
Coco, are you okay?
I'm all right-coco.
You'll soon be "all wrong"!
Nightmare!
You people really are
such a thorn in my side.
...but today, I'll pluck you out for good!
If you hand over the Dream Collet now,
you can spare yourselves a world of pain!
How many times do we have to say it?!
We'll never give it to you!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
Dream!
Merely taking you down should
start my scores trending upward!
Coco, you'll be safer
somewhere that's not here!
Up there!
Nozomi!!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of
the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
What now?
Coco, it's too dangerous! Go and hide!
It's useless! You're far too weak
to break my web!
I'm so sorry-coco!
You're stuck like this
because I'm powerless-coco.
Don't worry.
I dunno how the future's gonna turn out.
But right now,
I want to grant your wish, Coco!
I don't care if it's painful.
As long as I have that dream,
I can keep going!
Not so fast!
Time to end this!
Dream!
Farewell, Cure Dream!
Dream!!
Dream!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
What?!
Rouge!
Take this!
Hah! Now you can't move
your arms or legs.
Rouge!
You annoying pests keep on showing up!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
The great potential of
a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
Hey, Leader!
It sure is boring around here
without you, Leader!
We're sorry for being
so hard on you!
We saved you some snacks, Nozomi-san!
We'll be waiting for you at Nuts House!
Thanks! We'll be back soon!
I'm... so glad I became Pretty Cure.
I'm not just doing this
for your sake, Coco...
It's for me, too.
For yourself?
That's right!
I think I'll be more self-confident
if I can make your dream come true.
And then, I'm sure a fabulous future will open up in front of me.
So...
...I'm going to
see this through with you.
Question:
Which four-kanji compound means
"wordless expression of
one's feelings to another"?
Umm...
Ah, I know that one!
Or I just remembered!
Ishindenshin (communion of minds)!
Ta-da!
These are the results of
a week's worth of studying?
But look, I didn't fail any of them!
Good job there.
You sure tried hard, Nozomi!
Karen-san, thanks for
teaching me all this stuff!
S-Sure...
And afterwards, I read this book.
"Let's Play with Balloons!"
While you were supposed to be studying?
Yeah! I read the whole thing without even falling asleep!
Komachi-san, thanks for lending me
such an interesting book.
It was my pleasure.
Why did you let her borrow that?
Because I'm a librarian, of course.
So you finally figured out
how to make learning fun, huh?
And that was
the end of the matter.
You really think this is over?
Are these scores satisfying?
Now, now...
Karen-san, Nozomi's not going to
become a genius overnight.
Please consider the long term.
I suppose that's true.
There's always next time, right?
Nozomi, your next goal is to score at or above the average!
Okay!
Next time, I'll aim to be average!
It's decided!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Nozomi-san, I'm debuting as a host in an amusement park stage show!
Awesome! We'll all be there
to cheer you on.
Thank you very much!
But I'm getting all nervous and anxious...
Don't worry! If things get bad, we'll join you on stage and transform into Pretty Cure!
When did becoming Pretty Cure become
the solution to everything?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Protect Urara's Stage!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?