Urara, your appetite is even more impressive than usual today.
Actually, I have a job later today,
so I need to build up my strength.
What kind of job?
I'm glad you asked!
Kasugano Urara...
...will make her hosting debut!
Hosting debut?
Yes! This Sunday, I'm going to be the host for an amusement park stage show.
Kasugano Urara will do her best!
All you kids out there...
...I'll pick up your hearts!
Who're you talking to?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Urara!
Sorry to make you wait!
Good luck on today's show.
Thanks.
That's the spirit-coco!
Coco and Nuts, you came too?
Good question; why are you here?
Because you never know when or where a Pinky might appear-coco.
See what I mean-coco?
Nozomi, catch it-nuts!
I'm on it!
Catch.
Urara-chaaaan!
Manager!
Manager?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
What's in those bags?
Things we need for today.
It's still a bit cold for an outdoor stage show,
so I brought gloves and hand-warmers.
A stomach wrap,
a hot water bag, and, and...
Lucky charms! Lucky charms! And more lucky charms!
Thank you for always
thinking of everything.
Safe travel, academic improvement,
and... safe childbirth?!
Ah! You're friends of hers
from school, right?
Thank you for always
taking care of my Urara.
I am Kasugano Urara's manager, Washio!
Eagle Productions Management Team
Pleased to meet you!
Wow!
She has her own manager!
It's like she's in show business or something!
Um, she IS in show business.
Politics, economics,
sports, entertainment...
Someone keeps abreast
of all those topics!
Good morning! What the people want to know, I want to know.
I am Cinq Lumieres News'
chief editor, Masuko Mika!
But if you read it as one word, it's "Masukomi"-ka!
She's back for more.
Thanks for the exclusive interview special
on your stage show today, Urara-chan!
She already knew about it.
News travels fast.
I am Kasugano Urara's manager, Washio!
Please do write
a lengthy article about her!
"Manager"?
Of course! It'll be the cover story!
Thank you so much! I'm sure that
this stage show will be a great success!
And then someday,
photo shoots, commercials...
TV dramas, movies...!
Right! And then
our final goal is, of course...
Hollywood!
It's decided!
And then... lucrative endorsements,
the Best Actress Oscar, the sky's the limit!
Please keep the exclusive interviews coming my way!
They're counting unhatched chickens.
Protect Urara's Stage!
Girinma-kun... Girinma-kun!
Ahh, Girinma-kun.
This might be your last
appearance on stage, you know.
And what might you
mean by that, exactly?
The defeated are fated
to leave the stage,
and quietly live out
their lives in a far-off place.
Aren't you due for some R&R?
Bunbee-san...!
I have no plans to retire yet.
Mark my words; next time,
I WILL bring back the Dream Collet.
I'm counting on you.
Without fail...
So you'll do it here!? Wow!
Huh? Urara...
What a cute stage outfit!
She looks like
a "big-sister" type of host.
Yeah!
Okay, let's begin rehearsal!
Okay!
Hello, boys and girls!
Good afternoon!
The Forest Animals show is about to start!
Let's all have lots of fun today, okay?
Sure!
Nozomi, quit upstaging her.
Okay everyone,
let's call out the animals!
Hey!
Good afternoon! I'm Kerokero!
I'm Moomoo!
And I'm Torao!
The three of us are...
...the Friendly Trio!
You all must get along well.
That's right!
Yeah, that's a good expression.
So cool.
Yeah. Urara's always shining brightest when she's on stage.
I wanna try it too...
Weren't you banned from
the Drama Club after three days?
Don't remind me!
Say what?!
The girl who plays the rabbit
had an emergency, and can't make it?
This is a problem.
We can't put on the show without the rabbit!
What should we do?
We may have to cancel today's show.
No way!
Director, please!
This is my Urara's first stage appearance!
Is there no other option?
I-I know you're upset,
but the rabbit is a main part.
N-No...
I'll do it!
Wait, you'll do what?
I'll play that part!
N-Nozomi!
B-But you didn't even last three days
in the Drama Club!
I'm sure I can wing it!
You have to memorize your lines.
Why don't we ask if they can take out some of the lines?
We'll support you from off-stage.
Even so...
Rin-chan, it'll be fine!
With everyone's help, I'll get by somehow or another! Let's make it a success!
It's Urara's first
stage appearance, after all!
There's just no stopping you.
All right, let's do this thing!
Rin-chan!
Yes, let's.
The show must go on.
Komachi-san, Karen-san!
We'll all cooperate and make this work!
I can't say I'm reassured.
Let's do it. We still have time.
We've been preparing this for a long time.
Very well, the show will go on!
For everyone who's been waiting for it!
All right, I'll psyche myself up
to play this rabbit!
It's decided!
Everyone...
Okay, there's not much time!
Continue the rehearsal!
Right! I'll do my best!
Okay, start rehearsal!
Right!
Okay then, let's all
call our friend, Usako-chan!
Usako-chan!
You're walking weird.
We're totally screwed.
So much for my article.
What should I do, Rin-chan?
You've got to get this
straightened out before the show!
Got it! Straightened out!
Will she actually be okay?
What'll happen-nuts?
I have no idea-coco.
Hey, a fun animal show will be
starting shortly on the outdoor stage.
It'll be a terrific spectacle,
the kind you don't see every day! Bye-bye!
A show time... of terror.
The Forest Animals show will now begin
at the outdoor stage near
this amusement park's playground area.
Nozomi-san.
You don't have to be perfect;
you just have to have fun.
Thanks, I'll try to do that!
All right! Kasugano Urara's going to dazzle the stage!
Hello, boys and girls!
Good afternoon!
Urara-chan...
So far, so good.
That's the way.
The Forest Animals show is about to start!
Let's all have lots of fun today, okay?
Okay!
Okay, let's all call out the forest animals!
Hey!
Good afternoon! I'm Kerokero!
I'm Moomoo!
It's almost time for your rabbit to go on.
And I'm Torao.
R-Right!
The three of us are...
...the Friendly Trio!
And now, for our idol:
Usako-chan!
Massive fail.
Oh, right. Nozomi!
I'm Usako
Good afternoon
Your lines, your lines!
I'm so nervous...
Let's get this show on the road.
Something's appeared-coco!
H-Hey!
What the-?!
What the heck is that?
It can't be...
What's that?
No way!
What?
That's their story angle?
Nozomi!!
Coco, Nuts!
Nozomi!
Rin-chan, and everyone else!
Hurry-nuts!
Protect the crowd-coco!
That's one tall order.
If we transform here, then...
That's right.
We're in front of so many people...
Hey everybody, we've got trouble!
There's a monster in the forest!
Ah! Look up there!
Turn on the audience spotlights, please!
Now!
Right!
Pretty Cure...
...Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of
the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
What's that?
We've gone and done it.
We transformed...
Yes~!
Quiet, you!
W-What's going on? Huh?
Where's Urara-chan?
I've seen those girls before.
This is my chance.
Pretty Cure, I won't show you
any mercy today!
That's our line!
How dare you interfere with Urara's stage show?!
You think I care?
Where's Urara-chan?
One thing's for sure,
this is no ordinary show! It's a scoop!
Urara-chaaan! Where are you, Urara-chan?!
Mister, I can't see!
S-Sorry.
Pretty Cure!
It's your fault! You're the ones who ruined Urara's first stage appearance!
Who cares about
your dinky little stage show?!
It's curtains for you,
so hand over that Dream Collet already!
R-Rouge...
It's not dinky!
This is an important first step for Urara!
Dream, Rouge...
In that case...
Maybe I should ask for their feedback.
This is going to hurt a LOT.
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Onee-chan, you rock!
Awesome! This is a major incident!
Who the hell are you?
You think you're so smart?!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
T-Thanks.
Masuko-san, it's dangerous,
so keep away!
S-Sure!
Huh? How does she know my name?
It's just one thing after another...
Hey, you!
Making fun of people's dreams...
Getting innocent bystanders involved...
We'll never, ever forgive you!
Shut up!!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Not this again!
Yes!
Urara-chan, where are you?
Gotcha! I've captured those
five mysterious girls in action!
Story of the year, right here!
She got us good.
What should we do?
This time, she'll surely...
No kidding. We might not be
so lucky this time-coco.
Time to hurry back
and write that article!
You're...?
Ah, it IS you.
Funny meeting you here.
N-Nuts-sama!
Ahhh! I KNEW it!
This time it's totally
an exposé on Pretty Cure.
That's for sure.
Let me see too!
"Scoop! Destined Reunion!"
"The two of us are linked with
the red thread of fate"?!
What's with this?
Where's the article about US?
Talk about burying the lead!
And that picture's meaningless filler.
Please let me see too!
Well, at least it gives
the show rave reviews.
Karen-san, Komachi-san.
All's well that ends well... I guess?
Too bad your spotlight got stolen.
Yes. But if I get another chance,
I won't squander it!
Right. That's Urara for ya.
Urara-chaaan!
Washio-san!
Why're you running yourself ragged?
I've got big news, Urara-chan! Your show yesterday was extremely well-received!
The amusement park wants you to put on
another show like the one from yesterday!
So, Urara-chan, can you host
the show like you did yesterday?
If you do, I'm sure
those people will come again!
Ain't gonna happen.  Not going to happen.
Come on, ask them to come again!
Get ready Hollywood,
'cause here we come!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Volleyball, basketball, futsal...
Ah, what should I do?
What's the matter, Rin-chan?
They're all on the same day during the big sports meet.
I said I'd play for all of them!
What are you going to do?
Is there any way for me to...
What if I disguise myself as you
and take your place?
Is there any good way for me to...
Hey, are you listening?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Rin-chan Decides on a Club!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?