Show some hustle!
Here I go!
Goal!
Nice one.
Kaori-san and Rin-san are just too amazing together.
There's no way we could stop them.
Aki, you and Miho haven't been
paying attention to the flow of the game.
You have to stick to your marks,
and predict your opponent's next move.
Ah! Captain Konno, I have to get going.
Oh right, you had to go home early today.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Sorry I'm always leaving halfway through.
It's okay. You really saved the day
by coming to play with us.
You'll play with us
in the next tournament, right?
Sure! I'm doing stuff with other clubs too,
but I'll definitely play futsal.
All right! Let's do our best in our first match, with all five of us playing together!
Yeah!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Yes!
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Pretty Cure!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
Go!
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Yes!
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
I'm home!
It's Onee-chan!
Welcome home!
Hey... Yuu, Ai, stop that!
Welcome home, welcome home!
You know you shouldn't be
running around in front of the shop!
Hey, wait!
Give me back my cookie!
No way!
Ehh?! Why you...
Give it back already!
Cut it out!
Nozomi-neechan tripped.
She tripped, she tripped!
Why are you two
so incapable of behaving?
Oh, Rin, welcome home.
Ah, I'm back.
What's all the fuss about?
I asked Nozomi-chan
to look after Yuu and Ai.
I'm sorry, Nozomi-chan. It must be rough,
with these two refusing to obey you.
There's no problem on my end.
I'm an adult, after all.
No, you're not.
Rin, your dad's out on a delivery right now,
and I have to step out, too.
Take care of Yuu and Ai for me.
Nozomi-chan, take it easy.
Sure! I'll just help out a bit more.
You've done more than enough.
Lend us the futsal ball!
Hey, can we borrow it?
Every time I lend something to you two,
it always gets lost right away.
We won't lose it!
Let us borrow it!
Give it here.
Onee-chan, you meanie!
Fine, but that's an important ball.
Do NOT lose it, okay?
Hey, Rin-chan! What's futsal, a warm monkey?
Note: "Saru" = monkey, and Nozomi is confusing "futto saru" with "hotto saru."
Not "hot"-saru, "fut"-sal.
It's a five on five mini-soccer game.
I didn't know that club existed.
It doesn't have enough members
to be an official club.
That's why we practice in the park. But we're gonna have a match!
Good afternoon.
Ah, come on in, Karen-san.
You were going
to show me some flowers?
Karen-san!
Will you cheer for Rin-chan with me?
She's gonna play hotsaru!
Futsal!
Among other things, that is.
Didn't you know? Playing multiple sports probably won't be possible.
At the Student Council,
I heard that all the teams will...
...be playing simultaneously
during this year's sports meet.
Rin-chan Decides on a Club!
You can't play on more than one team?
That's a problem.
What are you gonna do?
If I may have a word?
I'm Masuko Mika, from everyone's favorite newspaper: The Cinq Lumieres News.
Read it as one word,
and it's... Masukomi-ka!
What do you want?
With you on their side,
victory is assured.
The one they call the "sure-winner-ringer": Natsuki Rin-san.
But with all the matches on
the same day in this year's sports meet,
which club will she choose?
Word travels fast.
A reporter, through and through.
Don't be impressed by her!
Please give a clear answer
to the question on everybody's mind!
A "clear answer"? But...
Natsuki-san!
You'll play on the
volleyball team this time, right?
Quit trying to poach her. We need Natsuki-san to be the anchor for the relay!
We'll be in trouble
if you don't play for us!
H-Hey! I'm in the middle of an exclusive interview here. Don't interrupt!
Shut up!
She'll be on the Judo team!
Don't delude yourself;
it'll be basketball!
Say what?!
She's all about volleyball!
Yup, it's true. This is the mother of all time conflicts.
I know it'd be hard to run them
straight from morning to afternoon.
I guess I just can't
play more than one.
It's too bad. You really
ruled the scene last year, Rin-chan.
I really wanted
to go all-out this year, too.
Here you go. Yakisoba bread and 30 yen in change.
Ah, thanks.
Is just one enough?
Are you feeling all right?
Rin-chan is worried because she can't play on more than one sports team.
Oh, is that so?
Well, it's nice to do various things,
but it's also good to
completely focus on one single thing.
Just one thing?
Wouldn't this be a good opportunity to decide which sport you like best?
That's right. You should join a club.
But my family runs a flower shop.
When I see how busy my parents are,
I feel like I have to help as much as I can.
I'll only end up being a burden to whichever club I join.
And that's why I've just been
"playing the field."
Then let me help!
I'll look after
Yuu-chan and Ai-chan for you!
That's not happening.
Well, I'll think it over
while I'm out on my run.
Otaka-san, one more
yakisoba bread, please!
Coming right up!
Handing out fliers, putting up posters,
window washing...
Ahh! It hurts just to read them!
But I can't eat nothing
without any money.
No fightin' it.
Maybe I'll do this?
Natsuki-san!
Help us Natsuki-san, you're our only hope!
But you said you would!
Please!
Sorry! I've got another practice,
so give me some more time to decide!
An off-campus practice?
Very sketchy.
Rin-san... hasn't shown up.
We shouldn't get our hopes up
for the match.
She wouldn't come to
a no-name non-club like ours.
We didn't even compete for her attention.
And we were so close to meeting
the tournament's five-person minimum, too.
We shouldn't force the issue! Rin should decide
which club she wants to play for.
But if Rin-san joins,
we could be an official club.
We all got together because
we wanted to play futsal, right?
Matches aren't everything.
Let's just show Rin how happy we are that she practices with us once in a while, okay?
Okay.
They all...
I'm back.
Onee-chan, welcome home!
Yuu, Ai! Don't run in front of the shop!
Stop right there!
I'm gonna get'cha!
Give them back!
No way!
This one is so soft and fluffy!
This one is velvety and streeetchy!
Don't pull on him!
That hurts, you know?
Cut it out!!
Oh, you're back early.
We all came to help.
Rin, welcome home.
Having these girls here
has really been a great help.
You'd better be sure to thank them, Rin.
I've got a delivery to make,
so you can take it from here.
"Take it from here"?
Nozomi... You were the one
who brought them here, weren't you?
Teehee~
Don't "teehee" me!
C'mon, give them back to us!
No!
We want 'em!
Give us a break already-nuts.
I-It talked!
It didn't talk, it didn't!
Yeah, yeah!
Nice shot!
Whatever, just give them back already!
I see. This Konno-san
sounds like a good captain.
Same goes for the teammates.
Yeah. It really was a coincidence.
I just happened to come across them on my way back from shopping.
They were all having fun
playing futsal together.
The team was a great bunch of girls. But...
You had to help out at your family's shop,
and you were always worried about your younger siblings.
I don't know what those troublemakers would do if I left them alone.
If I'm not there for them...
You really are a good big sister.
I wouldn't say that.
So what are you going to do?
Refuse to step in for
everyone except the futsal team?
I don't think that'll work.
Half-hearted measures like that just end up hurting everyone.
Excuse me!
Can you kick that over here?
The ball!
Man, what a pain.
Perfect timing.
If you want this back, give me the Collet!
No way!
What you say?! Hand it over already!
If you don't...
Don't do it!
Onee-chan is always cleaning that ball!
She really cares about it!
You two...
Give it back!
Shuddap already!
If you really want it, I'll give it to ya!!
Rin-chan!
Onee-chan!
Yuu, Ai, everything's all right now.
I need to have a "discussion"
with this person.
Play over there
for a little bit, okay?
But...
Just get going.
Onee-chan...
Go to that other field.
Don't come back here
until you hear me call.
Hurry!
Just a second, you.
What, there's five of you again?
What were you trying to do
to my little brother and sister?
Give it a rest, will ya?
I was just givin' them back their ball.
Even I'm gonna get angry if you keep droning on about that.
I'm the angry one here!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of
the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
And the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
If you still won't hand over the Collet,
maybe this will persuade you.
A Pinky-coco!
When did he catch that-nuts?
I nabbed it while I was cleaning.
You know what will happen
if I use this on it, don't you?
Calm down. We've dealt
with this before, remember?
We need to pull the mask off the Pinky!
First, we have to slow him down.
I've got this!
Got it. Rouge, it's all you.
We ready to go?
Yes!
Damn you! You no-good, lousy...!
I'll take that line...
and throw it right back at you!
Dammit!
Aw, c'mon! What're you so mad about?
You tried to bring Yuu and Ai into this.
Those kids are
my precious younger siblings!
That's right! Yuu-chan and Ai-chan...
...are still so little.
You were about to be
unspeakably cruel to them...
...and we'll never
forgive you for that!
Shut up already! You think I came here
to get lectured by you?
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Going somewhere?
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
Eeyouch!! Looks like my paycheck's just gone up in smoke!
We did it-coco!
Thank goodness the Pinky was safe-nuts!
Coco, Nuts, are you okay?
Those kids really dragged you around.
Now that you mention it,
my neck is killing me-coco.
I hope I never meet them again-nuts.
Sorry about that.
Those two're always so unpredictable.
But they're your darling kid siblings.
Didn't you say so?
Well, yeah, I guess.
I can't take my eyes
off them for a second.
I feel bad for the futsal players,
but I'll have to turn them down.
Why?
But you wanted to do it!
Don't you like futsal, Onee-chan?
We'll be good.
We'll do what Mom says at home.
So play futsal!
You two...!
Sorry for interrupting.
Masuko Mika?
Is this story really true?
Have you really decided to join
the futsal team, Natsuki Rin-san?
Uh, well...
Yeah! Onee-chan's gonna be in the match!
She'll win for sure!
Key testimony from the subject's siblings!
And I've got it all on the record!
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got an article to bang out!
And she's gone.
Now we know tomorrow's headline, today.
You can do it, Onee-chan!
We'll cheer you on!
Now look, you two...
Since you're so insistent,
I guess I'll try this futsal thing.
It's decided!
And when the time comes,
I'll be the one to look after you two!
That's not happening.
Hey! Don't you all say that at the same time...
Breaking News! A Decision to Play on the Futsal Team!!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Are budget shortfalls
really so devastating?
It's a difficult situation.
Isn't there anything I can do?
Can't you just increase the budgets
with sheer willpower?
That's impossible.
Then you can beg and plead with someone...
That won't work, either.
Then, then, then...
I told you I can't...
But I haven't even said anything yet!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The Worrying Student
Council President, Karen
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?