Cream puffs after class are just wonderful-coco!
Don't you think you should be
more careful about being discovered?
What would we do if someone saw you?
No problem-coco! I'd use my fancy footwork
to hide in a jiffy-coco!
Rin-chan!
Oh, it's Rin-coco.
But don't pick up the teacup if I'm hiding behind it-coco.
Huh? You were trying to hide behind that?
Your tail was sticking out
for anyone to see.
I was plenty hidden-coco!
Karen-san, can I have a moment?
Look at these balls!
They've clearly seen a lot of use.
Shouldn't they be reinflated?
They're so worn down that
they have holes in them!
We need new balls to practice with,
but our budget isn't enough to buy more.
"Budget"? But your club only gained official status just recently.
It's completely inadequate!
We already buy tons of stuff ourselves.
If we don't get our budget raised, we can't practice seriously at all!
Put in a word for us
at the Student Council.
What the heck?
Miss Student Council President, we can't buy more cloth with the Sewing Club's budget!
How can we pump ourselves up
if we can't afford dumbbells?
All of the clubs' budgets
have already been allocated!
But...
They were decided using
this year's budget estimates,
so please make do
with what you all have.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Bunbee-san.
Yes?
I see you've placed
your nose to the grindstone.
Despariah-sama is quite surprised...
...that your many attempts to obtain
the Dream Collet have cost so very much.
Well, you know,
travel expenses aren't cheap...
Since you're here, Kawarino-san, how about a cup of tea?
Frankly, I don't care how much it costs.
Your budget is quite generous.
I see.
However, there's no need to expend
the entire budget simply because it's there.
It shouldn't be wasted on worthless departments... or worthless employees.
We're "worthless," Kawarino-san?
Oh, no, I never said you
were worthless, Bunbee-san.
Not yet, anyway.
"Not yet"?!
At any rate, please do your best, Bunbee-san.
Breaking the table would invoke
yet another pointless expenditure.
What are you looking at?!
The budget, huh?
The Worrying Student Council President, Karen
Here's your change: 2 million yen.
Urara, your fried egg looks super-tasty!
Hey, will you trade me for my octopus wieners?
Sure, no problem.
Yay! Yummy!
Ketchup goes pretty well with them too.
These are good!
Hey, Karen-san,
you're the Student Council President...
Can't you increase the clubs' budgets?
The annual budget involves
more than the student clubs.
It also includes the Student Council and all school functions.
If I increase a club's budget,
I have to decrease something else.
But...
Rin-chan, are budget shortfalls really so bad?
Yes, they are!
For example, if your boxed lunch
were leaving you hungry,
you'd think about buying
some yakisoba bread, right?
Oh, of course!
What if you didn't have enough allowance to buy yakisoba bread?
Ah! That's not good at all!
That's the reality of budget shortfalls.
Even if our club needs
to buy something, we can't.
No way! Not having enough spending money to buy yakisoba bread is way harsh!
I'd have to get my mom
to increase my allowance.
It was just hypothetical!
Then what type of bread was it?
It wasn't about bread to begin with!
Vice Principal's Office
Eh? That's impossible.
The club budgets were based on the annual budget proposal.
I understand that.
However, all the clubs need larger budgets.
Please!
Well, I can see why you're
bowing your head like that.
I'll inform the Principal of
the Student Council's request.
Even so, I wouldn't get your hopes up.
You did it.
I wonder if Karen-san was successful.
How did it go?
Komachi.
The outlook doesn't look good.
I see.
I hadn't wanted to do it,
but maybe I should ask my father
if he can financially support the clubs.
But that wouldn't solve anything, would it?
I know that. I was just joking.
I wish I could do something for all those clubs...
"Wish I could do something"...
That reminds me of a certain someone.
In the past, you would've merely said,
"There is no alternative,"
and that would've been final.
Really?
Yes. Perhaps attempting to do what's best for everyone
has inspired you to kick reason
to the curb and go beyond the rules?
That might be true.
Meeting Nozomi-san
and the others has changed us.
Quite a bit of their influence
has rubbed off on you and me.
Surely there is an alternative to austerity.
Let's put all our heads together and think!
Yeah.
Principal's Office
So you see, they wish to raise all the clubs' budgets.
I tried to tell them it wasn't possible,
but she insisted that I ask you, Principal.
If increasing their budgets
were truly necessary, I would do so.
However...
I believe that there are still
many actions that can be taken.
It's hopeless!
I can't think of any good ideas!
But I'm still hungry!
So am I.
Miss Student Council President, we can't take this anymore!
Unless you increase our budget...
Your initial budgets should've been able to handle contingencies and continue operations!
Please make do with what you have!
The budgets were already bare-bones to begin with!
Hey now, everyone... hey, wait!
Aren't you the Student Council President?
Do something!
I guess I have no choice...
Everyone... What madness is this?
Komachi?
Isn't it normal...
...for you to solve
internal club problems internally?
Shouldn't you try to find solutions on your own...
before asking the Student Council President to fix everything?
Everyone was involved with
the club budget discussions.
So it's wrong to solely
blame Karen for the results!
But still...
Komachi-san's right, you know.
Rin-chan!
It's true that we've been leaning on the Student Council President...
...instead of trying to resolve this stuff ourselves.
Sorry, Karen-san.
Okay everyone, line up!
Tell us what you want, one at a time!
Nozomi-san?
Do you have some kind of plan?
Not at all!
But if we all put our heads together,
I'm sure we'll come across a good idea.
Like how everyone can have tasty lunches if we trade for what we want!
Ideas and side dishes
come from different places!
But Nozomi might be on to something.
I know, right?
Yeah, I guess we wont know
until we ask them all.
You think?
Okay everyone, tell me
what you want, one at a time.
Ready? The line starts here!
Ah, please stop there.
650 yen, please.
May I have a receipt?
Here.
Thank you.
Due to personnel budget cuts,
I have to take the field myself.
However, my arrival on the scene means game over for Pretty Cure!
Drama Club
So, the Drama Club's budget isn't enough to buy costumes for your next play.
That's right. We're seeing
massive cost overruns.
We wanted to do the Tale of Genji,
but we've only managed to make one costume.
The Tale of Genji? That features a multitude of princesses...
Why not do a more budget-friendly play?
I know one! How about Kintarou?
The costumes would be cheaper to make, and could be re-used for other bear roles!
No! Not aprons and axes!
And we've already started rehearsal!
That's right! I'm sure the Sewing Club...
Sewing Club
...said that they couldn't afford to rent space to display their work.
The Drama Club's costumes can showcase the Sewing Club's creations!
So if their actors wear our costumes,
we won't need a separate showroom,
and we can split the cost of materials with the Drama Club!
Besides, the Sewing Club
can make much better costumes
than we can, so I have no complaints.
You'll really give these
to the Art Club?
Sure. They're so worn-down that we can't use them anymore.
This heavily-weathered material and dented surface...
It's just the objet d'art we've been searching for! Thank you very much!
No problem...
So was there something, other than balls,
that the Futsal Club needed?
Yeah! We need strength-training equipment, like dumbbells.
Dumbbells?
The Judo Club just got brand new strength-training equipment, right?
Yeah, we bought heavier dumbbells.
The old ones were too light to do us any good.
In that case,
can the Futsal Club have them?
Sure, no problem.
Take whatever you want.
All right!
Don't mind if I do...
Don't... mind... if...
All right! Now we can free up enough budget for new balls.
Thanks, Nozomi, Karen-san.
Good for you, Rin...-chan-!
That's so cute!
The Sewing Club patched up our practice gis for us.
They used the leftovers from the Drama Club's costumes.
Doesn't it look like some
really cool applique work?
Okay then... Next... club...
Leave it to our Student Council President to pull off the greatest trade agreement ever.
Though I'm not sure how it followed from Nozomi's idea.
Huh? Why not? That's what I had in mind from the start, ya know.
As if.
But it seems like we'll pull through
this budget crisis.
Ah, I'm starving.
You and me both.
Looks like we're all
in the throes of budget woes.
Yeah, no kidding.
I-It's you!
So, are you ready to relinquish the Dream Collet?
You'd better transform too, Pretty Cure 5.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of
the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
And the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
That brings up my turn, right?
I'm facing you myself to avoid wasting my budget on useless subordinates.
Time to see if I'll be running a surplus, or a deficit!
It looks just like all the others.
It's totally different!
It's shinier over here...
I'm surrounded by amateurs.
I'll drill the difference straight into you!
Now, Kowainaa, make yourself worth the expense!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
That ain't gonna work!
Aqua!
Aqua, Lemonade!
Rouge, behind you!
How absurd. This is the true power of the legendary warriors, Pretty Cure?
Maybe I'm just too strong to tangle with?
I've proven myself to be
a true fiscal conservative, Kawarino-san.
Instead of trusting
my worthless subordinates,
I should have done
everything myself from the start!
Hehehe...
"Hehehe"?
I used to feel the same way.
But if we were to adopt that mindset...
...there's no way we'd ever win!
What did you say?
Everyone! Fried eggs and octopus wieners!
C'mon, remember what happened today!
Yes!
What the hell are you talking about?!
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Didn't I tell you that wouldn't work!?
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
What?
You see, our individual powers
may be weak...
But if we put our heads together...
...and combine our strength,
we can do anything!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
That's right. Because we aren't strong, we support one another...
Doing the best we can to make each other stronger is the key to victory!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
This wasn't a waste of budget! Sometimes, you have to spend money to make money!
The budget crisis was averted,
and everyone lived happily ever after.
Thanks for all your help, girls.
Thank goodness-coco.
But that time Komachi-san got angry at everyone sure was impressive.
Yes. It seems like Komachi-san always follows one step behind Karen-san, but...
Isn't it more like Karen-san is following Komachi-san's lead?
Does that mean Komachi-san is stronger than Karen-san?
You're the worst hider ever!
And there ya go...
You've all made a spectacular effort.
So here's some provisions:
my special experimental bread!
I was really moved when the Principal told me about all this.
The Principal told you?
You used intelligence and cooperated to resolve the issues,
rather than relying on external aid.
That was the most important thing.
According to the Principal, anyway!
So you know the Principal, Otaka-san?
At this point, what difference does it make? Just enjoy.
Don't have to tell me twice!
That's bread from Otaka-san, isn't it?
There's no mistaking it!
H-Hey, whaaaaaat is going on here?!?
Hold it! That yakisoba bread
is off-limits!
I already called dibs on that cream bread!
Now, now, everybody, don't rush. There's plenty for everyone.
All my bread is gone!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
My mom's got a fever!
I have to take care of her!
Will you be okay-coco?
Leave it to me.
I'm making rice porridge.
Rice, water... Water, and... sugar?
Sugar-coco?
A spoonful of sugar
helps the medicine go down... right?
Now my temperature's rising-coco.
Then I'll nurse you as well!
Somebody save me-coco!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Hustle - Nozomi Helps Out!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?