Good morning!
Good morning.
Megumi-chan, what's the matter?
Just a little headache.
But I'm fine.
Rin-chan, you're helping out
at the shop on the weekends?
Yeah. Take a look at
these flowers I selected.
They're very nice.
You're looking more and more like your mother every day.
You think?
Yes. That's the spit and image
of your mom's flower arranging.
When Kazu-chan was about your age,
she'd always bring nice flower
arrangements into our classroom.
When she was about my age?
Wow, so you've been arranging flowers since, like, a LONG time ago...
Rin, it wasn't THAT long ago.
To me, it was pretty much yesterday.
Oh, right, where's Nozomi today?
Ah, about now she's probably...
I'll take this giant cream bread...
AND EAT IT!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Go!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
I'm back.
Welcome home.
You're home early today.
I'm feeling out of it.
I had somebody cover the shop,
and headed home.
Are you okay, Mom?
Oh, no! You've got a bad fever!
I'll be fine.
It'll clear up with a bit of rest.
No, you need some real rest,
as in "bed rest."
But your father has a late meeting with the publishers,
and I've got to make dinner...
Let it go. Just leave
the housework and dinner to me.
Relax and go to sleep.
Will you be okay, Nozomi?
Yeah!
Hustle! Nozomi Helps Out!
Wake up!!!
What part of working the register involves napping?!
Shut up, I'm tired...
You're tired? From what,
holding down the floor?
Well, I don't know how
to work this damn thing.
Fine, I'll take over the register.
You put out those products for display.
What a pain...
What happened?
I thought I'd bring a cold towel to cool your head, Mom.
You'd better change
before you catch a cold.
Wait, why're you worrying about ME catching a cold?
I'll be right back with a towel,
so lie down.
No way!
Nozomi, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
So please, just go back
to bed, okay? Okay?
What is it this time?
Ehhh? What should I do?
Nozomi?
C'mon, Mom, didn't I tell you
to go to sleep?
Wow! The laundry's done already?
Modern washing machines
sure do work fast!
It stopped because you overloaded it.
I... see.
Tadah! I caught a Pinky!
We did it-coco!
Get it transferred it to the Collet.
Okay!
Hey, where're Nozomi
and Rin today-coco?
Rin-san said that she'd be
helping out at her shop,
but that doesn't account for Nozomi-san.
I'm expecting her any minute now.
Oh, this is so bad!
Rin-san...
What's so bad?
I heard that Nozomi's mom caught a cold!
She left her store and went home!
That is a pity.
But...
That's no reason for you to get upset.
Oh, isn't it?
Nozomi's dad is going to be home late from work, too.
So what-coco?
Which means Nozomi-san is the only one
up and about at home.
Right. And knowing Nozomi,
she'll try to take care of her mom
and do the housework.
Nozomi's playing caretaker?
And doing housework-coco?
One time, I asked Nozomi to carry notes from the Student Council meeting, and...
...she tripped and dumped them
all over the floor.
Nozomi once said she'd look over my homework...
But instead, I ended up
teaching HER the whole time.
When she tried to help
sort books at the library...
...merely reading the books' titles
was enough to put Nozomi-san to sleep.
When I let her help clean the shop,
she spilled water all over the place.
That's right-coco.
I had to clean it all up myself later-coco.
See what I mean?
And I've known her
long enough to know...
Nozomi's mom is in danger!
Rin-san, will your store be okay without you?
Yeah. My dad finished the deliveries,
so everything's fine.
More importantly...
We have to save Nozomi-san-
I mean, Nozomi-san's mom!
That's right.
My "cleanup" just resulted in
an even larger mess.
I burned the porridge!
Coming!
Oh, Rin-chan's mom!
Good afternoon.
You sure did a number on the kitchen.
I couldn't get it quite right.
I made some dinner for your family.
Dinner?
Your mom seemed under the weather,
so I thought she could use some help.
Now, let's get this place cleaned up.
Why don't we make
something warm for your mother?
Right!
Wow,you got it all cleaned up so fast!
It's like magic, only real.
No matter what I try,
I can't do anything right.
I just make Mom worry even more.
I only hope she doesn't wind up getting worse.
You were doing her best
to make her feel better, right?
Yes...
I think that would've
made your mother very happy.
Eh? You really think so?
Of course!
I'm sure she'd be glad...
...to see you working
so hard for her sake.
That ought to improve her condition.
All right, let's make your mother's favorite egg porridge together
and bring her back to health.
Sure!
Except, we're out of eggs.
I'll go buy some!
Eggs... Where are the eggs?
What a pain. Talk about labor abuse.
Wasn't that one of them Pretty Cure girls?
I'm sorry. Wasn't your shop busy?
It's fine. I've got people there.
Is Nozomi giving you trouble?
No, not at all.
Nozomi-chan really was trying her best.
Yeah. That girl always puts
her whole heart into everything.
She's a kind and caring girl who always keeps her mother's best interests in mind.
Never fails to impress me.
But of course!
She is my daughter, after all.
Yes, she certainly is your daughter.
Seeing Nozomi-chan do all those things
brought back memories.
She's just like you
used to be, Megumi-chan.
Oh, not that again.
Though actually,
Nozomi-chan's better in some ways.
At least she didn't put dirty dishes in the clothes washing machine.
My mind was blown.
Please, please keep that a secret from Nozomi, okay?
Okay, okay...
Eggs, eggs...
There they are!
Medium Eggs - 188 yen
Nozomi!
You guys!
We heard about your mother.
Is everything okay?
Oh, you were worried.
Man, doing the housework
and taking care of Mom
all by myself sure was tough.
Housework-coco?
Taking care of her-coco?
We're too late-nuts.
I guess we should've gone to
Nozomi-san's place first, not to the store.
Huh? To my place?
How's your mom doing now?
S-She's sleeping, I think.
But Rin-chan's mom
came over a little while ago.
Thank goodness my mom showed up.
Let's finish our shopping
and head over to Nozomi's house.
Huh? Why're you going to my house?
Dear customers, would you please return the Dream Collet?
I can flip it to Bunbee-san
for a nice profit.
He's with Nightmare-coco!
What a lousy exchange policy!
We were just about to head home.
Don't get in our way!
If you don't take your baskets
to a checkout lane before you leave,
you'll be in big trouble, dear customers!
I've got to get back to my mom
as soon as possible!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Rouge!
Take that!
Why you...!
I'll let you go if you give me
the Dream Collet.
I'll never hand it over!
Dream!
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
I have to hurry home!
Like I said, gimme the Dream Collet and you'll be on your way!
I gotta hurry home, because I need to make Mom's favorite egg rice porridge!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
We're gonna finish this shopping and get back to Nozomi-san's!
I keep tellin' ya - you can do all that once you give me the Dream Collet!
This isn't a barter economy!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
Nozomi's mom is waiting for us!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Looks like I'm not getting paid again!
Good afternoon.
Thanks for looking out
for Nozomi all the time.
They came over when they heard you were sick, Mom.
Well, we weren't as worried about her mother's health...
...as we were about Nozomi's treatment regimen.
Hey, I can hear you!
How are you feeling?
Oh, I feel much better,
thanks to all of you.
It must be a bother to have so many people over.
No, it's not. Thank you.
Okay, just leave the house to us.
We'll handle things from here.
Mrs. Natsuki, you rest too.
Wait, is this really okay?
I told you, we got this!
So...
Should we trust them, then?
Yeah!
Nozomi.
Thank you.
Those two really get along well.
Yeah, they do.
Well, they've been together
for a long time.
I hope that we can be good friends just as long as they have.
Yeah! All righty,
let's make my mom's favorite egg rice porridge.
It's decided!
All things considered,
they're good kids.
Yeah, I'm sure they'll be together for a good long time. Just like us.
Are you okay?
Sorry! I've never actually done much around the house.
Hey, you got pieces of shell in it.
Oh, a few bits won't matter.
That's right. They contain calcium, which should do a body good.
You've got to be kidding me.
Why are you slicing bean jelly?
I figured sweets were just the thing to improve a condition gone sour.
Why don't we add some
to the rice porridge?
This isn't an experiment!
I smell something burning-coco!
The porridge is turning black-nuts!
"Coco"?
"Nuts"? What's that?
I can't help but worry!
There's nothing to worry about!
Don't be concerned.
Nozomi, the porridge
is roasted to a crisp!
I'll be there in a second!
Everything's fine, okay?
Hey, Nozomi!
Adding water won't
unburn burnt porridge!
Kazu-chan, I think I'm going to take a little nap...
It's still good, it's still good!
Me too. I think I'm getting a headache.
All righty! One delicious rice porridge
coming right up!
As if!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Okay, we're starting
an adventure novel!
I'm glad you're interested
in my novel, but...
Komachi-san, what's wrong?
Nuts-san said it wasn't worth reading.
That's not true!
Nuts is so cruel!
He'll have to answer to me!
No, it's okay.
I'll just give up on my dream.
WHAAAT??
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Komachi Abandons Being a Novelist!?
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?