The ship was battered by the raging waves from the fierce storm it had encountered,
and was on the verge of capsizing.
As if adding insult to injury,
a pirate ship appeared.
The despondent passengers
all screamed out,
"Please, save us!!" "It's all over!"
However, one soul had not fallen into despair.
A young boy, eyes filled with the sparkle of hope, stood up boldly and declared:
"It's not over yet!"
"Pirate Hurricane" was highly compelling.
I didn't expect you to write
an adventure novel like this, Komachi-san.
Is there more? What happens next?
Huh? Umm... It's still a work in progress.
I can't wait to read it!
Komachi-san, you're amazing.
Writing that many sentences...
That's what impresses you?
You should have Nuts read it too-coco.
Nuts was the biggest reader
in the Palmier Kingdom-coco.
Would you like to read it, Nuts-san?
I'd appreciate hearing your opinion.
No problem.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Oh, yes. I really enjoyed your father's latest children's book.
Especially the heroine.
I felt just like that when I was little.
I could really empathize with her.
Really? My dad'll be
really happy to hear that.
I want to write stories
that'll move people the same way
I'm sure you can do it, Komachi.
That's right.
Pirate Hurricane by Akimoto Komachi
Huh?! You're done already?
Yes.
That was fast!
How was it?
I don't know what
you're trying to say.
I just don't understand what you want to get at with this story.
Um, well...
If the author has to explain a story,
there's no point in reading it.
It's worthless as a book.
Hey, Nuts!
What're you saying?
What? I'm giving my opinion.
I thought it was fun to read.
Yes, it was really exciting!
You're just biased because it was written by a friend of yours.
Speaking objectively,
I can't say that it's any good.
Komachi...
That's true. It's not that easy to write a truly good story.
Komachi-san...
I'm going home for today.
Sorry, everyone...
Komachi, wait!
Nuts!
What'd I do?
Komachi Abandons Being a Novelist!?
Their dream is to resurrect the Palmier Kingdom.
We are to work day
and night to stop them,
and to present the
Dream Collet to Despariah-sama.
Do not worry; everything is proceeding according to our scenario.
Isn't that right, Arachnea-kun?
Yes, we are of one mind on this matter.
I see.
However, your efforts are irrelevant to the progression of the scenario.
The real question is,
"When will we see results?"
When, pray tell?
Well... I'll delegate answering that to Arachnea-kun.
Huh?! M-Me?
Why can they still dream?
D-Despariah-sama!
The Palmier Kingdom has been destroyed,
leaving them in despair.
And yet, why do they dream?
B-B-Because... They have the Dream Collet?
Without hope, one holds no dreams.
Where is hope born from?
From a thin paycheck?
There are people protecting the Dream Collet,
which is the source of the hope.
They are known as the
legendary warriors, Pretty Cure!
Let them dream no longer!
Defeat Pretty Cure, and crush their hope!
And then plunge the world into despair!
Yes!
Nuts, don't you think that was cruel?
Why did you have to talk like that?
She asked for my opinion,
and I gave it to her. That's all.
Komachi-san put her heart into writing it.
And you shot her down!
Would you rather I'd lied?
Couldn't you have
sugarcoated things a little?
Komachi-san might not come tomorrow.
The mamedaifuku train
might not stop here anymore.
This conversation's over.
Hey, Nuts!
I was just telling the truth
about what I felt.
I didn't say anything, did I?
Your face says you wanted to.
Do you think I was wrong?
Not really.
I thought it was very "you," Nuts.
Very "me"?
An awkward person who's honest to a fault,
never uttering a compliment...
Someone who gets angry at himself for hurting Komachi, right?
So what?
What should I do?
Admit that you're powerless on your own?
Although if you INSIST,
I suppose I could lend you a hand.
I don't need your help!
I'll do something about it myself!
Good luck.
Now look, everyone has different tastes.
That story just wasn't something that Nuts would've enjoyed.
So don't worry yourself about it.
I liked "Pirate Hurricane."
It was really exciting,
and it's holding me in suspense.
Karen, don't worry about me.
I'll... be fine.
Really?
Isn't it time you went home?
You shouldn't keep Sakamoto-san waiting.
I'm going home, too.
Okay. You can call me any time.
Sure, thank you.
The scent of despair is in the air.
Dang it.
I thought books had
the answers to everything.
Should I apologize?
No. I can understand apologizing
if I'd told a lie.
But why should I apologize for telling her the truth?
A female biker?
Pretty cool...
Hey, that noise is too loud.
But I'm a customer.
Customer or not, you're being a nuisance.
Hey, Nuts!
This is not quality customer service!
There's no need to be polite with someone who keeps their face hidden like that!
Oh, I see.
It's just as you said.
I apologize for acting rude.
Sorry about that.
K-Komachi-san?!
No way!
You said you had
stuff to do at home!
Wait, are you really Komachi-san?
Madoka-san, correct?
Long time no see, Karen-chan.
Thanks for looking out
for my little sister.
"Little sister"?
I'm Komachi's older sister,
Akimoto Madoka.
Nice to meetcha!
Why did you come here?
Just running a little errand.
Who is it that loves
our shop's mamedaifuku?
Here. Komachi sent these.
Komachi-san is so kind!
How adult of her.
You should follow her example, Nuts!
There's no point giving out dishonest opinions.
It won't do anyone any good.
So you don't mind hurting people,
as long as you're telling the truth?
You should go apologize right now.
So that's the deal.
Nuts-san, don't worry about it.
She's weak enough to get all sulky
after getting her feelings hurt a little.
That's not...!
If she can't take this much criticism,
it's impossible for her to be a novelist.
It's not impossible!
Komachi-san is always writing
when she's working at the library!
If she's able to work that hard,
she must have amazing talent!
It's like improving at sports through motivation and practice.
If she tries her best at writing, she'll improve!
Like that boy in her story who never lets his troubles get him down,
I'm trying my best to be
an actress no matter what!
The writer's feelings are paramount,
more so in writing than in art.
Komachi can become a great author,
because her feelings are just that strong!
We're all...
...supporting Komachi-san!
Thank you.
I'll be sure to pass
your encouragement on to Komachi.
Thanks for the tea. See you later.
Please, wait.
I have a favor to ask.
Komachi, I'm coming in.
Onee-chan?
You have a guest.
Take it easy now.
Have you been working on your novel?
I've got... writer's block.
What about your dream of becoming an author?
I put everything I had into
writing "Pirate Hurricane."
I'm embarrassed that I ever
felt proud about it.
If it's no good, then...
Then I'm simply devoid of talent.
Is that all there is?
You're going to up and quit,
just like that?
Are your dreams so worthless
that you'd sell them away for nothing?!
Nuts!
Didn't you come here to cheer her up?!
Yeah! What's with the scolding?
Please consider Komachi-san's feelings!
Um, um... Let's all calm down, okay?
E-Everyone...?
I'm not mad, I'm just...
C'mon, you guys...
Something's appeared-coco!
Be careful!
Hey, keep it down!
You'll bother the neighbors!
Where are we?
Is this a dream?
Ow, ow, ow! That hurts!
Guess it's not a dream.
Rin-chan, pinch yourself!
Where in the world are we?
The sea.
It's salty.
The real ocean?
That ship...
Inconceivable!
We're all inside the story you created.
Does it suit your interests?
Nightmare!
I'll take you all down for good,
right here and now!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Dream!
Why you...!
Dream, Aqua!
"Everyone on board scored
a 1-way ticket to Davy Jones's locker."
That's the ending of this story!
Mint...
Oh, no need to thank me.
This novel you wrote gave me
enough inspiration to complete my job.
I'm sorry...
It's all because of my novel that everyone is...
Why're you apologizing-nuts?
Mint, did you do anything wrong-nuts?
Aren't you upset at the
loss of authorial control here?
Aren't you angry that you're being used-nuts?!
But...
If you just blame yourself and get depressed, nothing will change-nuts.
Nobody's born a great writer-nuts!
Everyone makes mistakes, repeats those mistakes...
And even so...
If you screw up,
you should try again and fix it!
You'll overcome the challenge somehow!
If you keep writing,
you'll keep getting better-nuts!
If you don't give up, you'll surely...
So... So...
Don't give up on your dream-nuts!
Nuts-san...
I found the Dream Collet!
W-Why?
Hand over the Dream Collet.
N-No-nuts!
Give it to me!
This story is not a tragedy!
No matter what happens,
the protagonist never gives up!
Even when he's in despair, he has
the courage to stand up and fight again!
Sounds like a trite
and lame plotline to me!
Time to put it out of its misery.
This is my story!
And you don't get
to meddle with the ending!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Do it now, girls!
Let's go!
Yes!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
You'd better think twice about
trampling all over Mint's precious story!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
What?
This story's lamer than lame! One star!
Nuts-san.
Hang on a sec.
There's lots of room for improvement.
But the main character isn't bad.
And the idea of combining a hurricane with pirates is all right, too.
If you keep polishing it,
you can bring out its potential.
Nuts...
You really suck at compliments.
Quiet, you... Here.
I... I'll rewrite it.
Although it might take me a while.
Will you read the next draft?
Yeah.
Nuts, aren't you glad the
mamedaifuku train's up and running again?
That's not what he's glad about!
Huh? When'd they all get back?
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Nozomi, am I acting weird?
Huh? You're not weird at all.
How's my hair?
Do my clothes match?
Wait, is something special going on?
Huh? It's nothing. NOTHING.
Your blushing face says otherwise!
No way! But what am I to do?
That person is coming!
"That person"?
Ah, well...
Rin-chan, could you be in lo-?
You don't have to spell it out!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Love Story of a Pure-Hearted Maiden
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?