You sold out of everything?
That's amazing.
What are you going to do about the shop?
We can't just leave it like this
and go on vacation.
No.
Today, Nuts and I
planned on preparing...
...some new merchandise
for the shop, but Rin...
Rin-chan, what're you doing?
Rin-chan, what's going on?
She's been completely
unresponsive this whole time.
Rin-chan, you're making accessories?
But you hardly ever wear accessories, Rin-chan!
What are you making?
I'm finished.
Aha, it's so cute!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
"That's a lovely bracelet you have there.
Did you make it?"
"Oh, this? Yes, I made it myself."
"Amazing. Not only are you
great at sports,
but your handicrafts are utterly adorable."
"Oh, my! What are you saying?"
"I'm not that..."
Umm...
Rin-chan, you're scaring me.
Uh... I'm not acting scary at all, am I?
Seems like you're having fun.
No, I wouldn't exactly say I am...
I'm sure you're tired.
You must be busy with club activities and helping out at home.
We'll provide assistance
whenever you need it.
W-What's up with you guys?
I'm just the same as usual.
Nice and normal.
I just feel like making a bracelet or something once in awhile.
Ah, Nuts... I think this one'll work.
The beads are high-quality.
You're right. It should fit into our lineup.
Yeah! Let's run with it!
Ah, it's already this late? Sorry...
Mom's taking Yuu and Ai out,
so I have to watch the store.
Oh yeah, there was another time when Rin-chan acted like this.
Back then, if I recall...
Huh?
Rin-san forgot her bag?
Our Rin-san...
How could she forget her sports bag
and all her equipment?
Something's not right here.
Love Story of a Pure-Hearted Maiden
Ah, my shoulders hurt...
They've really gotten stiff.
How unfortunate.
Wait, what's this document?
Staff reassignment?
It's got to be a promotion!
I'll get to attend
Management meetings!
Oh, that?
Sign it, Girinma-kun.
Yes, sir! Bunbee-san,
I'm very grateful for this opportunity.
I wouldn't be, if I were you.
No, no. I'm extremely thankful that you recognize
and value my contributions so highly.
Enough of this pointless blabber. Just sign it...
Okay!
...to confirm your resignation
from Nightmare.
I'm being... FIRED?!?
Tell me, why does it take all six
of us to deliver one bag?
We're on a scouting trip for new product ideas-coco.
Or we're all just curious about Rin-san.
Thank you very much. We will deliver them
to your residence later.
Oh, I feel bad for making you go out there all the time.
I should be able to carry
a small potted plant home myself.
You shouldn't trouble yourself.
I'm a lot stronger than I look.
Sure. I guess I should be thankful.
Yes.
See you later!
Thank you very much!
Rin-chan!
W-Why are you all here?!
Here.
Thanks for bringing it all this way.
But why did all of you come?
Everyone was worried about you, Rin-chan!
Until now, no one's ever
seen you wear an accessory like this one, have they?
The only time I've ever seen you wear flashy accessories
was that one time
when you had a crush-
No need to remember that!
Mmmokaysuremmm...
You don't have to hide it from us-coco.
That's right-nuts.
No, I'm not exactly hiding anything...
He was pretty handsome.
And seemed nice.
I'm not really sure,
but he didn't look like a bad person.
Oh, sheesh-nuts.
It was that customer who was disrupting our business-nuts.
N-No way!
You're all getting it wrong;
I wasn't...
Oh yeah! Didn't you say you'd deliver that flower to him?
W-Why bring that up now?
I will be going (later),
but only because it's my job.
Just go now.
Let us handle things here.
All righty, we're all watching the store!
It's decided!
There's no need to!
I don't want to inconvenience you...
That delivery's not urgent,
so it can wait.
It's all good.
But...
You don't have to hold back.
Um, why did I have to change clothes just to run a delivery?
Why not? You look a whole lot
cuter this way!
It's the best!
It's very nice.
It's nice to dress in clothes like that sometimes.
They really look good on you.
I'm really just gonna drop it off,
so I'll be right back.
We'll take care of the shop, so you can take your time.
Take this with you.
It's a matching set.
I bet you're thinking,
"Why not give one to him?", Nuts.
Thanks, Captain Obvious.
You're so thoughtful, Nuts-san.
Here.
Thanks!
See you later!
Okay, I'll hurry back!
I'm curious...
I just wonder what Rin-chan's up to.
You mustn't! Don't even
think about spying on her.
Let's just wait patiently.
But, but... I have to know!
Sure, I'm curious too, but...
I know, right?
Isn't Rin-chan like,
a totally different person now?
Her sense of judgment's gone
out the window, and so have her words.
I'm worried.
That is cause for concern.
That tomboy Rin...
...is a maiden at heart?
What should we do? If she can't talk,
that guy won't like her!
Still, isn't this something
she should solve on her own?
Sure it is, but...
I've just gotta
back Rin-chan up on this!
I'm gonna go check on her!
Wait-coco!
The others are right-coco!
At times like this,
we should just leave her alone-coco.
Maybe I'll go too.
As the Student Council President,
I suppose it's okay to assist the students.
If Rin-san can't think of anything to say,
I can make up lines for her.
As for me, I'll act as Rin-san's stunt double anytime!
I don't think that'll work.
It seems like we're all worried-nuts.
But what about the shop-coco?
You'll take care of it, won't you?
"This is a present for you.
Please take it."
No, I can't just spring that on him...
"Here, have a freebie!"
That sounds like I'm
giving it to everyone...
What should I do?
Foolish girl.
Go ahead and hope for the best.
But it's just when
your hopes are highest,
that betrayal brings you down the most.
Screw it, I'll do it live!
Just push the button...
Rin-chan, you got this!
It's no use. I can't push it.
She's still hesitating!
She's definitely not her usual self.
I never thought she could be this timid.
Hey, you're here pretty early.
Um, I'm delivering your flowers.
Sorry about yelling through your window.
I'll go to the door.
Oh, here's fine.
Sorry you had to make the trip.
Don't be. I'll do it anytime.
Okay, I'll count on you again.
Sure! And thanks again for your business, as well.
Um...
What?
W-Well...
This is a...
Who's out there?
The person from the flower shop?
That's right.
Ah, they're so pretty!
Thanks for the wonderful flowers.
Ah, sure...
I buy all these flowers from your shop
to make my girlfriend's face
light up like this.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Oh yeah, just a second.
Rin-chan...
Here, these are presents for you.
For us?
They're thank-you gifts for
always buying flowers from us.
And I thought they might
look good on you.
Pretty good designs, aren't they?
They're so lovely.
Thanks. But why are you
giving one to her, too?
Just a girl's intuition, that's all.
Okay, I'll be waiting for
your next order!
Thank you! I'll take good care of them!
Rin-chan!
We should leave her alone for awhile.
Karen-san...
I must've looked... so stupid.
I've gone and done it again.
Pitiful, aren't you?
Nightmare!
Hey, please don't push!
Everyone, please calm down!
Something's appeared!
Great, just who I wanted to see...
I don't know what pathetic dream you were so worked up about,
but it's all pointless now, isn't it?
It's not pointless!
Sorry, Rin-chan. We were worried,
so we followed you.
Nozomi?
So all five of you are here, Pretty Cure.
It's not pointless!
Feelings dedicated to another person
are a very precious thing!
They're not pointless at all!
Let's go!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
I'll take you all on at once.
Rouge!
Now he's really getting huge!
Can you taste the harsh reality?
Nothing lines up the way you hope it will!
Abandon all hope, Pretty Cure!
We're not abandoning anything!
Even if I mistakenly get my hopes up,
and wind up disappointed...
I want to live my life looking forward,
in spite of everything!
It's not hopeless at all!
Rouge...
That's right.
Yes, that's the Rouge...
...we know!
You girls just don't know when to quit.
Now you can't use the water anymore-coco!
And you can't get bigger-nuts!
You dare interfere with ME?!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
Don't make a maiden angry.
You won't like us when we're angry!
Yeah, what she said!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
This is bad... I'm all washed up!
You did it-nuts!
You did it-coco!
Rin-chan, there's a new all-you-can-eat
cake shop in front of the train station.
Let's go check it out.
How about a movie?
There's a new one starting today!
Won't you come over to my house? I have some delicious tea...
After eating cake and coming back from the movie to Karen's house,
why not have some of my shop's sweets along with your tea?
Agreed!
Sounds like a plan-coco.
I want to eat choux a la creme
as well-coco!
And I'll eat mamedaifuku-nuts.
You know, that all-you-can-eat place is closed today.
The movie that's premiering is a horror flick, so I'll pass.
And having tea and sweets after all-you-can-eat cake?
I'd never be able to eat all that.
Okay, okay... Then let's go somewhere you want to go, Rin-chan.
What'll it be?
You don't need to worry about me so... huh?
What is it?
If we're all here, then...
Who's at the shop?
Nobody!
What were you thinking?
Well, Coco and Nuts were supposed to be watching the shop, and...
Sorry...
Well, that really simplifies things.
C'mon, step on it.
Right.
Wait for us, Rin-chaaaan!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Karen-san is getting interviewed at home!
"And we've already discovered a priceless vase!"
It won't be like that.
"This huge painting's just gotta be expensive!"
We don't have anything like that.
"And this sculpture is a really nice piece."
I'm telling you, that won't happen.
"Wow! You have a tree that attacks people!"
We definitely don't have one of th-!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Charge In! Karen's Private Life.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?