Please take a look at these,
President Minazuki.
They're ALL letters from students who want to know
about the everyday life
of their Student Council President.
Eh? That many?
You sure are popular.
I'm so envious!
And so, we at the Cinq Lumieres News
shall do a complete and thorough
special report!
An interview with the beloved
Student Council President, Minazuki Karen!
The veil on her mega-rich,
super-cool life of luxury will finally be lifted!
And who will write this?
What the people want to know, I want to know.
The Chief Editor of
the Cinq Lumieres News-
Masukomi-ka!
Don't you say it!
So, I was hoping I could interview you
at your house this Sunday.
Eh? Surely an interview here at school
would be sufficient.
The people want my article to dig deeper than that.
It has to be at your house. Please?
Hmm, maybe I should do a tell-all...
...about the secrets of the Student Council President.
Huh?
What kind of secrets?
Nozomi...
Don't tell me, Otaka-san.
My interview won't be fair-and-balanced if I don't get my subject's permission.
Ah, doing things by the book, I see.
Well, I suppose that's for the best.
I request a close-up interview, please!
Please!
Everyone seems to be hoping for it,
so why don't you accept?
Treat it as if you're
fulfilling a request.
I guess I have no choice.
Thank you very much!
Also, I have one request...
...regarding the format of the interview.
Eh?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
There's one request I'd like to make.
Eh?
I'm not too concerned,
but the people upstairs...
...are starting to get impatient.
What'll happen if we keep
dragging our feet?
I'm already well-aware.
Oh, so you do know!
"It's all Pretty Cure's fault,
it's not my fault at all." Isn't that right?
I assume I should use
the full extent of my power?
Surely you jest.
Your best efforts
have not produced results.
No, you've got to be kidding me.
I can't believe this! That's crazier than crazy.
I have my own methodology.
Today, I will defeat Pretty Cure,
without a doubt!
Whoa... Her house is so big,
I can't even see it from the gate!
Thank you for waiting. Please, come in.
Ah, okay!
Good morning! Thanks for having me!
Good morning.
Welcome.
Please come inside.
Sure.
Wow, you look great in casual clothes,
President Minazuki.
Thank you.
Umm, Miss President, about today...
I understand. You were hoping to do...
...a leisurely interview
without interruptions, correct?
Right.
You needn't worry about a thing.
I'll keep my promise.
Follow me.
Thanks. I'm counting on you.
I don't know how relevant this interview will be.
My life at home isn't much different from anyone else's.
Something tells me that's not the case.
Not by a long shot.
Attack! Karen's Private Life
No surprises here.
This room, this furniture...
It's all so rich and elegant!
Can I take a picture?
Sure, take as many you want.
Okay.
Oh, I've seen these in a magazine.
Master and Mistress are constantly touring the globe, performing.
During their travels, they purchase
various items and have them sent here.
Over time, the souvenirs have
accumulated dramatically.
Wow... Stuff from
all over the world, huh?
By the way, will you be the only
interviewer today, Masuko-sama?
What of the other reporters?
Um, I am alone.
The Cinq Lumieres News...
has a lot on its plate, you know?
I see, so you're by yourself.
Let's have a nice chat outside.
Okay.
We're having nice weather today, so...
Whoa, what a nice terrace!
I can't help envying those
who live in places like this.
Really? It's pretty difficult to maintain.
Is that so?
Yes. We have to be
especially careful with the gardens.
But if you do a good job,
it's quite rewarding to see the plants grow.
Please, sit.
Of course.
Okay, let's begin the interview.
Sure, ask me anything.
First, to start off with...
M'ladies, your tea.
T-Thanks.
Enjoy...
So the first thing you do when you get home...
Sugar and milk, for your pleasure.
Miss President?
What was that? What about my house?
Once you're finished with Student Council business,
when do you feel most relaxed?
How about some sweets?
Oh, those look yummy.
S-So where were we:
the time when I kick off my shoes?
Well, if that's when you feel most relaxed,
then yes, that's where we were.
Miss President?
R-Right! Of course we had
more than three servants.
Allow me to step away
for a moment.
What in the world
are you all doing here?
C'mon, we were worried about you!
Yeah, right. You're just here for your own amusement!
She's on to us.
No, we thought you'd be too honest and blab about Pretty Cure.
Of course I wouldn't!
I just wanted to see what an interview was like.
Haven't you been interviewed a lot more than me?
And you even came in costume?
We borrowed them from the Drama Club!
Pretty fun, aren't they?
I'm not having any fun here!
Keep your voice down-coco!
You're too noisy-nuts!
Even you two?
Now listen up. This is just one of
my Student Council President duties.
Please stay out of the way!
Um, what is it?
M-Miss President?
Ahh, Masuko-san! The terrace is nice and all,
but why don't we go to the garden?
I think it'll work better.
Far, far better!
Wow, what a lovely greenhouse!
Can I take a look?
Go ahead.
There is a hot spring on the grounds, and we make use of the heat here.
Whoa, you sure have lots of plant varieties in here.
Do you like flowers, Miss President?
I'm over here.
Yes, I do. When I look at
all these exotic plants,
they inspire me to try my hardest
to keep them all watered and healthy.
If I didn't care for them,
they wouldn't be able to survive.
That's the President we know.
You like to take care of things, don't you?
It's not exactly like that.
I wish I didn't have to take care of them.
But if I didn't, who would?
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, it's nothing. Just forget about it.
Miss President?
Wait a moment, Miss President.
What's the matter?
I said it was nothing.
L-Let's get out of here.
Dammit!
Miss President!
Our President is surprisingly discomposed.
Please don't leave me behind!
This time, I will defeat Pretty Cure.
And I shall use
any means available to do so.
I think I can finally relax now.
You're sweating a lot, Miss President.
So then, once you've finished with Student Council business,
when do you feel most relaxed?
Feeling relaxed?
Yeah.
Fight!
Keep Calm!
Fabulous~!
I'm hungry~
Maybe I manage to relax...
...when I'm finally ALONE.
Miss President,
are you angry about something?
M'lady, I've brought some Celeb House cream puffs.
Celeb House cream puffs?
It must be hard to get these,
since the quantities are so limited.
Well...
I am very particular about them,
so I obtained them directly from Kobe.
Everyone else, please have some too.
These are dewicious!
How creamy!
You girls?
Thanks for the food!
That hit the spot!
Please Sir, can I have some more?
Hook me up, Jiiya-san!
More will be on the way.
Please come back tomorrow.
Oh yeah!
I'll be dropping by tomorrow!
You don't have to come!
It looks like someone's made Karen-san mad again, Nozomi.
Not just someone!
Uh, oh... Once Karen flies into a rage, she won't come down any time soon.
That's an alternative fact!
Getting angry once in a while is a good stress reliever.
No, it's not!
And it helps keep your skin smooth.
No, it doesn't!
Didn't I tell you over and over
to stop interfering? You nosy little...
But Karen-san, you're so interesting.
What part of me is so "interesting"?
You're so cute when you're angry, Karen-san.
Simultaneously dignified and frightening...
The president has suddenly become so lively, vibrant, and angry.
How can anyone keep their dignity
in this situation?
You just don't want to admit you've lost at anything.
It's quite a different image.
That's completely irrelevant!
Just give me a break!
Okay, okay... we'll go home.
No. I'm escorting you to the gate.
It's like she doesn't trust us at all.
I wanted to eat the cream puffs-coco.
You can come back for more tomorrow.
No "tomorrows" for you!
Masuko-sama...
Please wait a moment.
M'lady will be returning shortly.
I'm a little surprised.
That wasn't what I'd call "presidential."
M'lady has changed ever since
those girls began visiting her.
She's really brightened up.
Um, would you mind going into more detail about that?
Not at all.
Man, you're always so strict, Karen-san.
Oh, no... Karen is very gentle by nature.
Huh? You mean she's only
this strict with us?
Really?
Only because you're all
such troublemakers!
Now that Karen-san hates me,
I can't go on living...
There's no way
you really think that.
No, I'm being serious!
There's a Pinky near here-coco!
Hurry up and catch it-nuts!
Everyone, hurry!
Yes!
So that's how it is.
President Minazuki has always felt sad and lonely.
She can be honest
with her own feelings around them:
a stark departure from the past.
It's all because of the friends she's made. I'm really glad.
"Friends"? I'm kind of jealous.
What could that have been?
Here it comes!
Oh yeah, epic win for us!
Okay, let's go. Masuko-san is waiting.
Masuko-san?
It came from the greenhouse!
This is the greenhouse, right?
Was Karen-san's greenhouse always this creepy?
I didn't make it like this!
Welcome to the jungle!
MY jungle, that is!
You again?
How dare you defile Karen's
precious greenhouse like this?!
It's more authentic this way!
H-Help me!
Masuko-san!
Hey now, Masuko-san
has nothing to do with this!
This is my personal methodology!
You can't transform now-nuts!
You'll be discovered-nuts!
Masuko-san's in danger!
We can't worry about
blowing our cover!
Right!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
It's fast!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
You think that attack will work?
What?
I did it!
Damn you!
I won't let you!
Are you okay?
Who are you guys?
Don't worry about it.
We're here to protect you.
Sure.
Girls!
Mint!
I can't move!
I already told you:
this jungle is my home turf!
You guys!
Everyone...
Run!
Run that way! As fast as you can!
O-Okay!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
You're all...
Aqua...
Thanks, Aqua!
Enough already!
Whaaat?
What do you think you're doing to my dear friends!?
They may carelessly impose on people,
and sometimes they're a real pain.
But they're my irreplaceable companions!
I will NEVER let you harm them!
"Companions"?
Unless we slow it down,
we'll never be able to hit it!
What?
I can read your "methodology" like an open book!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
It's your turn next.
Curse you all!
Here.
Thank you very much.
And you girls are...?
Huh?
What are we going to do? It's really bad this time.
She even got us on camera.
Maybe we'll be in tomorrow's Cinq Lumieres News!
We're finally headline news!
It's nothing to celebrate!
Why not? We've already been caught.
No, it's embarrassing. And anyway...
It'll be highly
chaotic and inconvenient.
And I don't want to worry my family.
But it's not like we're doing
anything wrong.
Yeah.
It'll be hard to stay here
if we're discovered-coco.
That's right-nuts.
We'll handle it
somehow or anothers!
Right, Karen-san?
You look awfully happy, Chief Editor!
I've landed the scoop
of the century!
Mysterious super-heroines!
They're really strong and cool!
Is that what's popular these days?
And did you get
their consent to print it?
W-Well...
You didn't?
No.
I know you're excited and all, but you ought to
keep your subjects' feelings in mind.
I-I see.
Huh? "A Close-Up Interview with the Student Council President."
"During the interview, her friends came over
to her house and made a big fuss."
"The camera caught a shocked expression on the Student Council President's face!"
"According to a source,
'M'lady has really brightened up.'"
Jiiya, what did you tell her?
Look down here.
"The Chief Editor Speaks Out."
"The Chief Editor requests
an official interview with Pretty Cure 5."
"What is the identity of
these wonderful friends?"
An interview request?
When, when? Tell me when!
What should I wear?
What are you getting so excited about?
Don't worry, I'll let you borrow some clothes, Rin-chan.
That's not what I meant!
I can't hardly wait!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Oh no! Two suspicious characters are tailing you, Urara!
Could they be, perhaps...
...a mysterious organization, investigating the secrets of actress Kasugano Urara?!
There's no way that's true.
They're my dad and grandpa.
Eh? Then why are
they following you, Urara?
That's... a secret.
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Seek Out Urara's Secret!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?