Sorry to jet, but I'm in a hurry.
Do you have another lesson today?
No, today's more of a...
Look out, we've got some creepers outside the store!
I saw them too-coco!
They sure are creepy.
More like annoying.
Nuts-san...
I got this.
Hey, you two!
Are you just window-shopping
at our store?
Um, we're...
Just a couple of passersby.
Dad! Grandpa!
O-Oh hey there...
Urara...
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
I'm Urara's father, Michel!
It's nice to meet you all.
M-Michel-san?
Um, ah... Gouda moaning!
Sankyuu Berry Mucchi?
That's not a greeting.
And anyway, Michel-san was speaking Japanese.
Your Japanese is very good.
Thank you. I've been in Japan for 20 years now.
It's such a fabulous place.
I love it no less than my own dear France.
And I'm Urara's grandfather, Heizou.
I'm so glad I've gotten to meet all of you wonderful ladies.
If I were 50 years younger,
I'd be on the attack for sure!
"Attack"?
He's quite a...
"special" grandfather, isn't he?
Okay, now that we've dispensed
with the pleasantries, we really...
...must be going, you see.
Huh? But I was just
about to serve tea.
What she said! You just got here,
so why not relax for a bit?
No, I think we'll be taking our leave.
See you again!
Hold it!
What are you guys up to?
And don't try to fool me.
W-Well...
We just happened to pass through here.
Yeah, sure  you were!
Hello, Urara-chan!
I've got your new job right here!
W-Washio-san!
Here's the script.
You've got a lot more lines this time.
Memorize them fast,
and then knock 'em dead!
I'm sure your father and grandfather-
We wouldn't miss it for the world.
Indubitably.
Michel-san, Heizou-san,
why are you here?
That's...
We were just passing by, and...
Same excuse as before.
You came to check on Urara-chan, right?
I can't say I blame you.
But if you tell us that Urara's acting strange, then...
There's no way we wouldn't worry.
Didn't I tell you it wasn't a big deal,
as I'd be watching her from the shadows?
Um, we can hear you.
I'm not acting strange.
T-That's right.
You're the same old Urara-chan.
I have to get back to the office.
In that case,
we'll be heading home, too.
You get home safely now, Urara!
Sheesh...
Seek Out Urara's Secret!
Girinma-kun... That's you, right?
W-What's this about, Sir?
It's just that I've worried myself sick over you.
You've experienced
a monumental string of setbacks.
Have you been eating properly? You seem really nervous lately.
I've been thinking you might be
getting depressed.
Well...
I've been looking out for you
this whole time.
I'd drop everything to help you out.
NOBODY'S more concerned about you than me.
If you're that concerned,
handle things yourself.
You say something?
No, sir! I will let nothing deter me
from executing my duties!
Please, worry not.
I'm sorry about all that chaos.
My dad and grandpa are always like that.
On headbands: "Urara"
Urara, we're here for you!
Urara, Fight
Go for it, go for it, Urara!
They really love you, don't they?
Yes, to the point of embarrassment.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Yes, they seem like good parents.
Hey, did they come see you at the amusement park?
Neither of them could make it.
They seemed really broken up about it.
They really wanted to see
your debut as an emcee-coco.
There's always next time-nuts.
Speaking of which, where's your mother? Doesn't she watch your work?
I guess... I never told you all about it.
My mom passed away
from an illness when I was little.
I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
No, don't worry about it.
I was kind of too young to remember it.
And I have Dad and Grandpa.
And my manager, Washio-san,
is practically family.
It's always been like that,
so I'm not lonely at all.
Things've been
almost TOO lively...
I suppose it is hard to feel lonely with
a father and grandfather like them around.
Yes.
That's right.
Well, I've got things to do
and places to be.
Goodbye.
Urara!
Good luck with work tomorrow!
Right!
I never knew Urara went through all that.
I'm impressed that she doesn't let it weigh her spirit down.
What is it, Nozomi?
Urara's dad and grandpa said she's been acting strange, and I have to agree.
You've noticed it too?
Isn't there anything we can do for her?
Looks like we weren't
the only ones who caught on.
Um...
So, you girls also sensed something amiss?
On some level, yes.
Looks like everyday shopping to me.
Why would she even
need to hide this?
Ah, but look at her face...
At her job, she was unusually fidgety,
laughing to herself,
and generally acting off-kilter.
But that expression on Urara-chan's face is one of utmost concentration!
There's more to this shopping than meets the eye!
Way to go, Washio-kun.
You have an eye for "Urara-chan details."
You're just as reliable
as a manager should be.
Oh, you're too kind!
I've still got a long, long way to go...
Found~you.
Urara hasn't taken her eyes
off that notebook for an instant.
Yeah.
Is that notebook...
what I think it is?
Something's appeared-coco!
Hey there, little lady...
What?
Where's Urara?
Urara!
Urara-chan!
This is... Urara's bag!
Urara had just bought these.
Nozomi, Nozomi!
We've got trouble-coco!
It's that way-nuts!
Let's split up and look for her.
Hurry-coco!
Looking for someone?
Urara!
Nozomi-san!
Welcome, young ladies of Pretty Cure.
Let Urara go!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
I trust you know
what'll happen to her...
...if you don't hand over
the Dream Collet!
Coward!
So what if I'm a coward?
I'll do anything and everything
it takes to get the Dream Collet!
That's...
Until you feel like giving me the Collet...
...I'll give you a lesson on
"progressive pain!"
S-Stop it!
Stop it!
That notebook is... That notebook is...
A precious notebook
that my mom gave to me!
It holds so many
memories of my mother...
Everyone, please, don't hurt it!
Holds so many...
...memories...
...of her mother...
An invaluable notebook...
How worthless! Who needs memories?
You'll pay for this!
First, let's save Urara-san!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Two of them disappeared?
Urara!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
If it's SO important, you won't be able to attack it, now will you?
Lemonade!
Just leave it to us.
Dream...
It'll be fine, Lemonade!
There's no way that we'd...
...harm your mother's precious notebook!
We'll get it back, for sure!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
I'll never...
...EVER forgive you!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
But I'm really glad that your notebook is safe.
Yeah.
Urara!
Dad, Grandpa, even Washio-san...
Urara, where did you go?
We were worried...
I'm sorry.
Urara-chan!
Y-Yes?
You understand how much you've been worrying them, don't you?
It doesn't seem like she's hurt.
Just let it go.
Urara-chan, both Heizou-san and Michel-san
were really sad after your mother died.
But because you were there for them,
they cheered up,
and put all their efforts into raising you.
And you've had enough success in the workplace
that you're virtually
an adult already.
But if you're making your cherished family members worry this much,
then you're still a child.
I'm so sorry.
As long as you're happy now, it's all right.
Urara, that notebook...?
It's yummy!
That's right, it IS yummy!
It's your mother's special curry!
It happened when I was very young...
...so I hardly have any
memories of my mother.
But I clearly remember the first time
we all had curry together.
The curry we all ate
was incredibly tasty.
I recall the shining looks on Mom's and everyone else's faces.
I only wanted to make you smile
with my cooking, just like Mom did.
If I could just bring Dad and Grandpa
a little happiness...
Urara...
So I decided I'd make
Mom's special curry today!
But I didn't tell anyone,
and I made you worry...
I'm really, really sorry.
Urara, thank you.
You've really grown up.
You're such a good girl.
So that was it.
I apologize for going too far.
No, I should be apologizing.
Shall we head home?
I'm getting hungry, you know.
I really want to try your curry, Urara.
Okay!
S-Sorry...
Nozomi.
Okay, go ahead!
How is it?
It's delicious!
It's got such a kind flavor.
I never thought curry could be so joyous!
Urara, your dad
will never forget this taste!
Thank you so much!
Thank goodness.
Seconds, please!
Me, too!
I'd like a lot more, please.
Have you ever
heard of moderation?
...says Karen-san,
as she holds out her plate.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Put your hands in the air!
Urara's debuting as a singer!
It's getting me all fired too, too!
Whatever...
What's the matter?
You seem down, Urara.
I have to write the lyrics
for my debut song, but I've hit a wall.
It'll work out somehow or anothers!
We can all join you on stage!
Somehow, I don't see that helping.
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Pretty Cure 5's Singing Debut!?
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?