Note: This is the first half of a classic vocal exercise which goes through the Japanese alphabet.
(Water striders sure are red.)
Amenbo akaina. A, I, U, E, O.
(Baby shrimp are swimming in the floating seaweed, too.)
Ukimo ni koebi mo oyoideru.
(Persimmon tree, chestnut tree.)
Kaki no ki kuri no ki. KA, KI, KU, KE, KO.
(Woodpecker tapping tapping, into the dead wood.)
Kitsutsuki kotsukotsu, karekeyaki.
(Black-eyed peas with vinegar.)
Sasage ni su wo kake. SA, SHI, SU, SE, SO.
(Speared that fish there in the shallows.)
Sono uo asase de sashimashita.
(Let's stand up and blast it out.)
Tachimashou rappa de. TA, CHI, TSU, TE, TO.
(With a toot and a tap we took to our feet.)
Totetote tatta to tobitatta.
(Slug slides slowly.)
Namekuji noronoro. NA, NI, NU, NE, NO.
(Something slimy in the closet, sticking to the floor...)
Nando ni numette, naninebaru...
Something like that.
Wow!
Way to twist that tongue.
It's all part of the acting biz.
Amenbo, akyaina, aeueo...
Ukimyoni, kyoebi mo, oyoideru...
Kakinoki, kurinoki, kyoki kyokyo fuu...
There's a reason you got kicked out of the Drama Club after three days.
Didn't I tell you
not to mention that?
My bad...
Rin-chan, you meanie!
Urara-chan!
What's the matter, Washio-san?
We've got a situation, Urara-chan!
Remember that show
you emceed awhile back?
Yes, I do...
Apparently, a producer from
a record company was watching it.
He really took an interest
in you, Urara-chan!
And... he asked if you wanted to debut as a singer!
Jinkies!
A singing... debut?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Arienai
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!! Yes!!
The number of times
I've turned away a smile are increasing
Not at all, not at all
Not enough
Lemon scent
Is debuting as a singer really...
right for me?
I should be working to refine my acting.
I don't have the time to be
taking on side projects.
They want me to write a song,
but I can't think up any lyrics.
Urara! Are you here, Urara?
What are you yelling about?
We brought the goods!
It's pretty cool.
What is that?
This is...
You'll see.
Pretty Cure 5's Singing Debut!?
Congratulations on your singing debut!
Congrats on your debut!
Kasugano Urara ♥
Um... "Singing"?
Y-Yeah.
We made this banner
to help cheer for you, Urara.
What do you think?
It's not our opinions that matter.
It's out of the question.
Don't you agree, Rin?
I guess it's not...
...big enough, not by a long shot!
What? You're questioning...
...the size?!
The design is perfect, though.
You bet!
Pretty lively up there.
My passion cannot be contained by a banner this small!
Double it!
Triple it!
Any less, and it wouldn't be enough.
But wouldn't we need a really...
...spacious workplace
to make one THAT big?
Eh?! My house?
Karen-san!
No, Minazuki-senpai!
We want to cheer on Urara
at her singing debut, no matter what!
Please!
Fine with me...
Yay!
In return, you'll let me do the design.
Yes! You can do!
Karen?
Um...
Actually...
Howdy!
What the people want to know,
I want to know!
Chief Editor of the
Cinq Lumieres News, Masuko Mika!
String that together,
and you get Masukomi-ka!
Huh? What?
It's you again.
Um, where'd everybody go?
Hey! You came at just the right time!
Congratulations on your singing debut!
So, where is your debut event
going to be held?
U-Um...
Can Urara-chan debut
on a stage like this one?
Urara-chan, we'll pull out every last stop...
...to pack the audience in the aisles
AND up to the rafters!
Wow! It's like the
sacred realm of idol debuts!
"Sacred realm of idols"?
Incredible.
And now, to start the presses on an extra edition.
I should publish the location
of her debut as soon as possible.
We're counting on you!
By the way... I've been wondering about something.
What is that?
I made this banner
to help cheer for her!
Cheer for her? Aren't these for sports?
No, it's for Urara's event, duh!
How lame.
Saywha?!
She didn't know much
about the event,
so she didn't know the best way to cheer for her.
I have lots of experience
covering these sorts of events,
so just leave it to
the illustrious Masukomi-ka!
One, two, three, four!
L!
O!
V...
E.
Wrong!
This is the key cheer for when she takes the stage!
Don't be embarrassed, just do it!
We'll do our best.
Is this what... cheering is like?
Beats me.
Ready, set!
L! O! V! E!
Love! Love! U-RA-RA!
I love!
Y-You love!
You love!
I love! You love!
Urara-chaaan!
That's pretty tough.
You like that? Ain't it awesome?
S-Sure.
Um, Nozomi-san, the truth is...
Hey, if we're all cheering for her,
we should come up with matching outfits!
Nozomi, that's a great idea!
But... who will make them?
Well... I didn't think about that.
Next, we should practice what to shout when she's singing her song.
That'd be a good thing to practice,
but we can't until we know the song.
Ah, you're right.
So, Urara... Can you sing the song for us?
Huh? Actually,
I haven't written the lyrics yet.
Huh?
You "haven't written them"?
So you're your own lyricist?
Yes.
How impressive!
Lyrics must be tough to write.
Tsk, tsk, tsk...
I'm sure Urara will have no problems.
She could write
a great song in no time flat.
Urara?
Don't act like it's simple!
Urara!
Urara...
I never said I was going to accept the offer to debut as a singer.
Nonetheless, you all tried to force that decision on me.
Eh? But, aren't you going to debut?
Nozomi-san, you know I want to be an actress, right?
Yeah.
I'm at a loss.
Should someone who's aiming to be an actress be debuting as a singer?
Don't worry about it, just try it out!
Why do you want to be an actress?
That's because... I want to spread my dreams to the audience.
Well, I think actresses and singers both accomplish that.
Those two jobs are connected to people's dreams.
So, if you try your best at either one,
I'm sure you'll be able
to reach everyone.
Nozomi-san...
I'm sorry for yelling at you before.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
I'm sorry I couldn't
understand your feelings.
Um...
Urara, we're also...
...really sorry.
The very best~
admiration
Because everyone's with me
get stronger
Come in.
Making any progress?
Think you can write
some great lyrics?
Of course!
It feels so chaotic.
Y-Yeah.
It'll be hard to salvage good pictures from such a chaotic concert atmosphere.
Cheh, what a pain this is.
No one cares about
all these stupid events.
They ain't gonna draw a crowd.
Right now, Kasugano Urara is
going to have her debut event!
Please take one!
Ain't they Pretty Cure?
Here!
Hope to see you there.
It's Kasugano Urara's debut event!
How's it going?
Don't worry! We're gonna have to
start turning 'em away!
We'll do our best for Urara!
Thank you!
Urara-chan's friends are all
such caring souls.
How's Kasugano-san doing?
It seems she's a bit nervous.
Will she be okay?
Please go and see her.
Masuko-san and I
will hand out the flyers.
Right! Just leave Urara to us.
The very best~
Admiration, bursting
Because everyone's with me
I can be strong
Face in the mirror / Morning
Totally studied, but
It'll be fine if I...
Urara!
So, you nervous?
My heart's already pounding.
Let's see...
Amazing, eh?
But this is the first step
toward your dream.
You can do it!
You have my support.
Stay strong.
Sure.
It's time to get ready.
Please bring your costume and follow me.
Okay.
Um, wasn't the dressing room
over that way?
Ah, there's been a last-minute
change of plans.
I'm supposed to don my outfit here?
Your costume doesn't make
a bit of difference.
No one's gonna come and
listen to you sing anyway.
Instead...
Nightmare!
Can I interest you in...
giving me the Dream Collet?
Girls!
Give it back!
Is this outfit really so important?
Urara, are you okay?
Nozomi-san!
My costume...
What did you do?
So, Pretty Cure is all here?
That means less work for me!
We won't let you trample Urara's dreams
without paying the price!
Her dreams?
She just wants to soak up
that sweet celebrity fame.
You're wrong!
I'd never sing for a reason like that!
Color me doubtful.
Either way, this dream
of yours is HISTORY!!
Urara wants to sing so that she can
spread her dreams to the audience.
And we're going to make
that desire flourish, no matter what!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Fire!
Let me try.
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
You'll never hit it
at this rate-nuts!
You guys!
It's time to give up the ghost,
and the Dream Collet along with it!
Dream!
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
Mint! Rouge!
If our attacks aren't connecting...
we'll have to slow it down!
Do it now!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Ain't nobody wants to
listen to your lousy song!
I'll show everyone my feelings!
Good luck; you're gonna need it!
The costume's... done for.
I fear it's too late to get a new one.
Here, take these.
You wanted to wear
matching outfits, right?
This whole time, I've been wondering...
...why I'm standing on this stage to sing.
I wasn't able to answer that question.
But my best friends were able to tell me.
I pray that my song...
...and my feelings will reach your hearts.
The very best!
Tobikiri~
Admiration, bursting forth
hajikeru akogare
Let's go!
Because everyone's with me,
minna ga iru kara
Get you!
...I can be strong enough to pass through...
tsuyoku naru
Hi!
...the door of courage!
yuuki no doa
Facing down the face in the mirror...
kagami no kao ni batsu
...on the morning of a test...
tesuto no asa no koto
Why, oh why?
doushita no
I totally studied, but...
benkyou wo shita no ni
...I'm still scared.
yappari kowainda
Can't stand it!
harahara
It'll be fine if I do my best...
daijoubu yo ganbarete iru koe
Do my best...
ganbare
My friends...
nakamatachi ga
...are all here...
senaka oshite
The very best!
Tobikiri~
...to push me along!
kureru
Shining bright, yes!
Kirakira Yes!
The very best!
Tobikiri~
A mysterious power appears...
Fushigi na chikara ga
Let's go!
...when I set my sights high.
mezameru shunkan
Get you!
Walking forward under a lemon glow...
Lemoniro no hikari wo susumou
The very best!
Tobikiri~
Admiration, bursting forth...
hajikeru akogare
Because everyone's with me...
minna ga iru kara
...I can open up...
hiraite yuku
Hi!
...the door of courage!
yuuki no doa
Thank you very much!
Kasugano Urara is going to do her best from now on!
Let's go!
Get you!
Yes! Go! Go!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Check this out, Rin-chan!
Ain't it cute?
What kind of doll IS this, and did it just move?!?
You're seeing things.
Hey, you ate my fried eggs!
It wasn't me;
that "doll" just scarfed them down!
You won't hide your fried-egg cravings from me that easily, Rin-chan!
You're totally wrong!
That doll is evil, I tells ya!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The Apprentice Caregiver Milk
Makes Her Appearance!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?