Note: Original Aesir subs are in subtitle track 3.
Ah... I'm so hungry-mil...
I think she'll do nicely-mil...
What's that?
Is this...
...a plushie?
Wow, it's so fluffy and cuddly~!
You're really cute, you know!
Huh?
I wonder what happened to your owner?
Nozomi!
Rin-chan?
Get a move on already!
Why're you just standing around?!
Ah, I'd totally forgotten! I'm gonna be late!
Hehehe...-mil.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Eggplant, Aesir
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Girinma-kun? Hey, Girinma-kun! He's vanished again...
Ah, there you are.
The two of us go way back, don't we?
Remember how we used to talk the night away at your place?
Yes...
Now let's see. Your accomplishments
during the attack on the Palmier Kingdom
were very impressive.
They were a real eye-opener.
Ah, yes! I gave that job everything I-!
You did...
Since then, your performance has been rather poor.
At this rate, it might even spell an end
to our relationship with you.
Is there nothing I can do?
Well, we do  go way back.
So I'll give you one bit of good advice.
Oh, thank you, sir!
Don't try to fight Pretty Cure.
Set your sights on the refugees from the Palmier Kingdom.
Any way you slice it,
you're no match for Pretty Cure.
T-That's not true!
But look...
You managed some outstanding
achievements in the attack on Palmier.
You should stand a chance against the Kingdom's residents, right?
But sir!
I can't rest knowing that Pretty Cure have gotten the best of me!
Please... Please let me destroy them myself!
This is an order.
Your reply?
The Apprentice Caregiver Milk
Makes Her Appearance!
I wish lunchtime would get here soon...
My lunchbox has a ton of fried eggs in it today!
Fluffy, sweet, fried eggs~
It's still first period, you know.
All right, everyone, pay attention please.
Consider the passage,
"The road grumbled to itself with a rattle."
This is a grammatical device called personification...
That voice...
The Wind Sings
...which ascribes human traits to inanimate objects.
This device is integral in "When the Wind Sings".
Personification is used to give
a deeper sense of personality to a world...
It sounds just like his  voice-mil...
Cinq Lumieres News
Kasugano Urara: Debut of a Singer
Look, look! She's written this huge article about you!
Huh, even Masuko Mika can write an honest article once in a while.
Your father and grandpa were pleased too, weren't they?
Yes, very much so!
They've got my CD on constant replay at home.
So the hard work was worth it?
Thank you very much!
Really, I owe it all to you guys!
Yeah, it's like they say:
when there's a happy event...
...it makes your lunch taste even better!
By the way you wolf things down,
everything must always taste great.
Mmm... Fluffy, sweet, fried eggs!
Huh? What's wrong?
M-My lunchbox... is empty!
She's right. It's empty.
Nozomi-san?
She's petrified with shock.
I'm so happy-mil...
But that's so weird. How could her lunchbox suddenly have become empty?
I'm starving!
I'm done for...
I'm surprised you lasted through afternoon classes.
Are you hungry?
If you want some mamedaifuku,
we've got some upstairs.
Really?!
Wow, they look yummy!
Ah, Nozomi!
Yeah, Rin-chan?
Here, take this. I know you'll start choking
if you eat too fast.
Here you go!
Thanks, Rin-chan!
Give me back my mamedaifuku!
They were delicious-mil.
It spoke!
Nozomi?!
Nozomi-san?
W-W-We've got trouble, big trouble!
What's wrong?
This plushie...
No, t-this this plushie-like thing...
ate my mamedaifuku and then talked to me!
A plushie-like thing...
...that eats mamedaifuku...
...and talks?
Isn't that normal?
Right?
What's up, guys-coco?
See, here's another one.
Why would you still be surprised?
No, no! I mean THIS plushie-like thing!
Ah, Coco-sama, Nuts-sama!
You're from the Palmier Kingdom!
Yes...
I'm so glad to find you both well-mil.
Coco-sama, Nuts-sama, I am Milk,
your apprentice caregiver-mil.
"Milk"?
Bow your head-mil!
Just who do you think these people are-mil?!
These are the princes of the Palmier Kingdom, Prince Coco and Prince Nuts-mil!
P-Princes?!
That's enough-coco.
You can stop bowing now-nuts.
Go on, don't hold back, eat your fill-coco!
These mamedaifuku are delicious-nuts!
These two are... princes?!
Unbelievable...
I'd never have guessed...
On top of their duties as princes,
they taught Milk and her fellow apprentices the joys of studying and reading-mil.
They are wonderful princes-mil!
This is the first I've heard
about their being princes...
I didn't think it was worth mentioning-nuts.
Eh, is that so?
Ouch!
These are being served by Milk-mil!
Don't help yourself to them-mil!
Why not?! You ate my mamedaifuku, and now you want more?!
By the way, Milk... have you been alone all this time-coco?
Yes, I have-mil.
I barely got away with the belongings I could stuff into this suitcase-mil.
Coco-sama, Nuts-sama... what happened to everyone else from the kingdom-mil?
The King entrusted the Dream Collet to us.
It was all we could do to protect it-nuts.
Milk, cheer up-coco!
If we gather the Pinkies in the Dream Collet, the Palmier Kingdom will be restored-coco!
R-Really-mil?!
But what if those guys come after us again?
Pretty Cure will save us-coco!
Pretty Cure?! You mean the
legendary warriors, Pretty Cure-mil?!
That's right! Leave it all to us!
We're discussing Pretty Cure, not you-mil!
What should we "leave to you"-mil?
I'm telling  you...
Milk, these girls are...
Excuse me!
I think this would really suit you.
Wow, it's gorgeous!
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama are truly amazing.
They're able to transform into inhabitants of this world-mil.
Can't you take human form too?
Then how have you gotten by?
At times, I pretended to be a puppy...
Sometimes, a kitten...
And other times, I just pretended I was a cute little plushie...
So you've survived from people
being kind enough to take you in...
They were all such suckers-mil.
Wait, are you saying that
one of those "suckers"... was me?!
Calm down, Nozomi!
Thank you for visiting us!
Did they just say
"thank you for visiting us"?
Yeah. Nuts is  the manager of this shop.
Nuts-sama is... engaged in commerce?!
How wretched-mil!
You can rest easy now-mil!
Now that Milk is here, the two of you
won't have to suffer such inconveniences!
It doesn't bother us that much-coco...
First of all, I need to prepare your dinner-mil!
Meals are the foundation for everything else-mil.
Just look at this girl-mil.
She lacks energy because unlike Milk,
she isn't eating properly-mil!
Milk had yet another hearty lunch today-mil.
A lunchbox full of sweet, fluffy fried eggs-mil...
A lunchbox?
Well, it would've been more to Milk's liking if it had been a little less sweet-mil.
So does that mean that
the one who ate my lunch...
...was you?!?
Let me go-mil! Don't keep me from looking after the princes-mil!
You guys are just interfering with my work-mil!
Let Milk handle the rest. Get lost-mil!
Shall we go home for today?
Ehh?! We still haven't settled
the case of the missing lunchbox!
Come on, let's just let it drop for today, okay?
Ehhh? But...
Just forget about it, okay?
All right, I will now go and buy the ingredients for dinner-mil!
Wait-coco! It's dangerous to go alone-coco!
Huh?! Where'd she go?!
Sheesh, she's supposed to be our apprentice caregiver...
...but she's making us
take care of her!
Why is that fluffball such a pain in the-?!
Settle down, Nozomi.
There's no way I can settle down!
My stomach sure isn't settled.
But I guess Milk was telling the truth...
...about being forced to survive on her own all this time.
Being alone must have been
very disheartening for her...
She managed to stay hidden and travel all this way in an unfamiliar world.
Nozomi-san, couldn't you forgive her?
Yeah.
Well... I guess you're right.
She's been alone all this time, after all.
I'm sure it must have been tough for Milk.
Huh?
Hm? What's the matter?
I just saw Nuts...
And Coco, too...
Do you think something's happened?
Hrm? Are you two also looking for someone?
Coincidentally, I happened to be searching for some people myself...
For you, in fact.
Hand over the Dream Collet!
You think I'll let you escape?!
Tch! Stop scurrying about!
Still, the absence of Pretty Cure
means that something is lacking.
Stop it-mil!
Why you little-!
Milk, are you all right-coco?!
Milk, are you all right-nuts?!
Oh, I didn't know this little miss was with you.
Milk is Coco-sama and Nuts-sama's apprentice caregiver-mil!
It's Milk's job is to protect them-mil!
It's too dangerous-coco!
Stand back-nuts!
I will not stand back-mil!
We can't have you two missing
when the Palmier Kingdom gets revived-mil!
That's terribly gallant of you,
but what can you hope to achieve
when you're trembling that much, little girl?
Let me spell it out for you.
The Palmier Kingdom was destroyed.
It can never  be brought back.
You'd be better off not clinging to
dreams that won't come true!
That's not true!
If you believe, your dreams will come true!
We'll revive the Palmier Kingdom, no matter what!
It'll be all right now.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cure...
Is that so?
Now that you've shown up,
I guess I have no choice.
Change of plans!
Pretty Cure, it's on!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
Leave us handle things here!
Those girls... are Pretty Cure-mil?
Yeah-nuts!
They're going to make our dream of reviving the Palmier Kingdom come true-coco!
It's over, Pretty Cure!
What?!
Why you...
We won't let someone like you
get between Milk and her dreams!
She's survived all on her own for so long...
She finally got to meet Coco and Nuts again!
She strained her courage to the limit...
...and gave her all to protect Coco and Nuts!
I won't allow you to cause Milk any more sadness!
Will you can it already?!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Are you okay, Milk?
Thank you-mil!
To think that you girls were Pretty Cure...!
Pretty Cure is so...
...unreliable-mil!
I thought the legendary warriors would be
more upstanding people-mil.
Not some...
...rude little kids who don't even know their manners-mil.
Hey! You've got no right to complain about us while you're thanking us!
Now now, Nozomi.
Quit taking her side, Rin-chan!
Nozomi-san, shh.
Look.
She's asleep?!
She must have been relieved.
She'd been putting up a strong front, but...
...she pushed herself too hard, huh?
Milk tried to protect me and Nuts-coco.
She did the best she could,
in the only way she knew how.
Yeah.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Please listen to me, Komachi-san!
That darned Milk ate all  my mamedaifuku!
There, there. I'll get you some more, okay?
I swear she won't get away with this!
Where'd you go, Milk?!
Huh? Now you mention it, where did  she go?...
I haven't seen her around at all.
Eh? Wha-?! Milk? Milk?!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Milk Runs Away and Causes Mass Chaos!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?