Good morning!
We came by to help out!
Thanks.
We don't need your help-mil!
Milk!
We three will be quite enough to look after
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama-mil!
What do you mean?
Now that she knows that
you girls are Pretty Cure,
Milk has to be more reliable-mil!
A klutzy girl like Nozomi becoming Pretty Cure
is the shock of the century-mil!
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?!
Yeah, whatever...
You're in my way-mil!
Ah, so busy-mil!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Whoa...
Amazing... They're already queuing up outside.
Ah, I'll do that-mil!
No, that's okay. Don't worry,
I'll handle this.
I can do that-mil!
Are you okay?
I'm perfectly fine-mil!
I'm pretty much done here.
You're done-mil?
On second thought,
let's put this over here.
Coco-sama, Nuts-sama!
Princes like you shouldn't have to transport such heavy objects-mil!
You're not exactly lightening the load, Milk.
Milk's just trying to help out-mil!
Hey now, are you all right?
Where should this go?
Over in that corner, please.
Okay!
This is so frustrating-mil!
Milk.
Hm? What is it-mil?
The customers will start coming in soon,
so you'd better go upstairs and rest.
Why's that-mil?
We wouldn't want them to discover you.
Y-Yes...
I understand-mil...
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
Welcome!
We've got price declines all across the store!
I wasn't able to be useful at all-mil...
Milk Runs Away and Causes Mass Chaos!
Arachnea-kun? Arachnea-?
Ah, there you are. Thanks for your efforts.
This is your bonus.
Thank you, sir.
What's this?!
You see, the quantity of your bonus
is based on the quality of your work.
In other words, that's about what you're worth to us.
I thought you had superior ability,
so I'd expected great things from you.
If you want a respectable bonus,
you should ask yourself how you can
be useful to Despariah-sama.
I'm well aware of that!
Arachnea-kun got angry...
But then again, even I  didn't get a bonus.
Milk wants to help with something too-mil...
Hi~! What the people
want to know, I want to know!
I'm the Chief Editor of the
Cinq Lumieres News, Masuko Mika!
Strung together, that makes Masukomi-ka!
She's back...
I'm here at Nuts House, which is packed with
bargain shoppers, and... huh?
I think I'll try and get an interview
with the hot guy who
owns the place, Nuts-sama!
Nuts-sama, you sure are busy today, aren't you?
Sorry, but things are
a little hectic right now.
Could you save the interview for later?
Oh, you girls are all helping out here too?
Or should I ask: why  are
all five of you are here to help?
What kind of relationship
do you have with Nuts-sama?
Well, it's kinda...
It just turned out this way.
What do you mean,
"It just turned out this way"?
Ah, I mean, in other words...
And what other words would those be?
Explain what you mean!
Milk!
What's she doing there?!
It's soooo cute!
Ah, Masuko-san, that's...
I think I'll buy this.
You really do have great taste, Nuts-sama!
Y-You can't!
You can't have that!
Why not?
Well, umm...
Sorry. That's not for sale.
But it has  a price tag on it.
Huh? But like I said, it's...
Ah, I put this out here by mistake!
Sensei! Why are you here?
Well, Nuts is a good friend of mine, so I'm helping out a bit too.
Sorry.
Huh? It blushed a little bit...
Y-You sure it's not just your imagination?
Why were you sitting out there
holding a price tag?
I wanted to be useful to you-mil...
How do you mean?
If you sit on the shelf with a price tag,
someone might buy you, like she tried to do.
That's fine with me-mil...
You're fine with that?!
How so...?
If someone bought Milk, then Coco-sama and Nuts-sama would profit-mil...
But what'd you do if you got bought?
Yeah! Were you planning on living in a different house?
Of course not-mil.
I'd sneak back here
under cover of darkness-mil!
If I did that enough times,
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama would get rich-mil!
Milk...
There's a term for what you were
trying to do, and it's called "fraud."
We don't want dirty money.
But that was the only way
I could think of to be useful-mil!
If you're going to take it that far,
I'd rather you didn't try and help at all.
As a subject of the Palmier Kingdom,
you ought to have more pride in yourself.
I wonder if Milk'll be okay.
She seemed pretty depressed.
Sometimes, you have to be
brutally honest with people.
Y-Yeah...
Nozomi, if you would...
Okay!
Thank you very much.
Is this the one?
Huh? Yeah, that's it.
Coco-sama, Nuts-sama...
Milk has no right to remain at your side-mil...
Excuse me forever-mil...
Isn't she from the Palmier Kingdom?
There are still others left out there?
Milk?
Milk!
Where the heck did she go?!
What's the matter, dear? Why the long face?
Milk isn't needed,
because she's utterly useless-mil...
Oh no, you'll be extremely  convenient!
Something's appeared-coco!
You're one of the refugees from
the Palmier Kingdom, aren't you?
Milk-coco!
Coco-sama!
Let's go!
Be careful!
Give Milk back!
You won't be getting her back quite so easily, little girl.
Ugh... what are those things?!
What's going on?!
It's creepy!
You've barely seen the start of it!
Today I shall finally obtain
the Dream Collet for Despariah-sama!
We'll never... let you have it!
How brave. But I wonder how long
you'll be able to keep acting tough!
Just take a look at this!
Milk!
Don't worry about Milk, Coco-sama-mil! Please save yourself-mil!
What're you saying-coco?!
I couldn't abandon one of my dear friends from the Palmier Kingdom-coco!
Oh? Is she that precious a friend to you?
Darn right she is!
Then will you trade her for
that Dream Collet you value so much?
Isn't that fair?
That's low!
We won't give you the Collet,
but we will  rescue Milk, no matter what!
Oh my, what are you saying?
Guys!
Right!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Give back Milk!
Hmph! Didn't she sneak out and come to me
without a word to you all?
You've forfeited all rights to determine her fate!
What are you talking about?!
Didn't she run away because you said such cruel things to her?
We didn't mean it like that-coco!
Coco had Milk's best interest at heart!
When you care about someone,
sometimes you have to be harsh with them!
That's right! Milk-san is a dear friend to us!
We wouldn't be mean to her
for no reason!
Coco and Nuts were overjoyed that Milk came back to them!
Coco-sama...
We'll save Milk, no matter what you do-coco!
You really think you can rescue her?
Milk!
Look out-coco!
You're wide open!
How careless you are, Pretty Cure!
Now then, hurry up and
hand over the Dream Collet!
Until you give me the Dream Collet, I'll show you no mercy!
Milk was wandering all alone for so long.
After all the hardships she faced, she was finally able to reunite with her friends!
Dream...
Milk...
I swear we'll bring you back home with us!
Lemonade!
Right!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
What?!
Pretty Cure Mint Protection!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Stream!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
There goes my winter bonus, too! Curse you!
You're safe now.
I was so scared-mil!
Eh?! You sold out of EVERYTHING? Amazing!
The bargain sale was a huge success-coco!
Thanks, you guys-nuts!
By the way, how've things been with Milk since then?
She seems to be reflecting on her actions.
I'm sorry about yesterday-mil...
Milk!
I'm sorry for making you all worry.
I shouldn't have done that-mil...
We're just glad you're okay.
She's become downright modest.
Nuts-san, Cinq Lumieres News has some pictures from the sale.
Cinq Lumieres News: Business Thrives at Nuts House!
Wow...
She wrote about Milk, too!
The very cute mascot
of Nuts House.
A cute stuffed animal,
not for sale.
"Though this stuffed animal is not for sale,
it is extremely cute
and eminently huggable."
She gave you a compliment, Milk.
Really...-mil?
Isn't that nice, Milk?
But of course-mil!
Those who serve princes must exude cuteness and refinement!
Well, Nozomi and I are
as different as heaven and hell...
How do you know that expression?
It's only natural-mil!
Milk's not only cute,
she can study with the best of them-mil!
Study...?
In this world's terms, Milk would be
a junior high school girl-coco.
She's about the same age as you, Nozomi-coco.
Except, Milk is far more mature
than she is-mil!
S-S-She ate it again!
Thanks for the food-mil!
Give me back my mamedaifuku!
You snooze, you lose-mil!
Give it back!
No way-mil!
That was my  mamedaifuku!
Serves you right-mil!
Guess they really are on the same level...
I fear we're in for more drama.
Give it baaaack!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Rin-chan, Urara,
Komachi-san, Karen-san...!
What should I do?! Everyone's hearts have been driven apart, and it's all my fault...
But... I'll never give up!
As long as there's something I can do, I'll keep trying!
I'll go to Nightmare... and save you all!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Crisis! Invitation to a Nightmare
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?