We're almost finished with this store decoration.
It was worth all the hard work.
Rin-san, that looks great!
I know, right? Not bad for my first try.
You're so clumsy, Nozomi-mil.
This is pretty hard, you know!
Milk will do it-mil!
Hey, give that back!
Let Milk handle it-mil!
Forget it, just give it back!
No way-mil!
Hey, Nozomi! Be careful!
Yeah, I know!
Caught you!
Let me go-mil!
No way...
We've been working on this for days...
We worked so hard on it, and yet...
...we're back to square one.
What happened?
M-Milk had nothing to do with this!
Nozomi! This is why I told you to be careful!
B-But it's Milk's fault...
Don't try to shift the blame!
You don't have to be so harsh about it.
Harsh? Who, me?
You're not even considering Nozomi's case here.
She won't reflect on her actions
unless we beat her over the head with them.
Now, now, Nozomi-san didn't do it on purpose, after all...
That's right!
Is that any way to act after ruining all our hard work?
N-No, that wasn't...
Isn't that enough? Komachi-san, don't you agree with me?
Eh? W-Well, there's some truth in your view of things, Urara-san,
but I understand Karen and Rin-san's perspective as well.
Trying to be neutral about it
won't do her any good.
You're naïve, Komachi.
And also indecisive.
Karen...
Is that how you've thought of me?
N-No! I didn't mean it!
Back to the point...
What do you mean, the point?!
There's no need to get so worked up...
Noble words from someone who's
trying to get herself off the hook!
I told you not to talk
to her like that, Rin-san!
My shop is covered in beads.
If you've got time to make a scene,
you've got time to clean.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
You're being reassigned due to your repeated failures, Girinma-kun.
Here you go.
You know what this black paper
means, don't you?
C-Could there be some kind of mistake?!
Kawarino-san just brought it here himself.
You have a decision to make about your future with Nightmare.
Two choices have been offered to you.
You can quit Nightmare...
or you can prove your loyalty!
So, whatcha gonna do?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll be sure to defeat Pretty Cure,
even if it costs me my life!
How much longer will these delays persist?!
I understand your anger, my lady.
I've come here because I believe
I'll have to deal with this personally.
I take it you have some sort of plan?
Indeed. If Pretty Cure consists of the united power of five people,
...then we'll just have to split those five apart!
Crisis! Invitation to a Nightmare
Milk.
M-Milk didn't do anything wrong-mil!
You need to apologize to people
if you upset or inconvenience them.
But that was all Nozomi-!
Do you honestly think you're blameless here, Milk?
Milk...
I'll go gather up the beads-mil!
Coco!...da-sensei.
You're alone? Where're the others?
Jeez, you won't believe this! Supposedly,
Rin-chan's got a club meeting today...
...Urara's out on a job,
Komachi-san's working in the library,
and Karen-san has
a Student Council meeting!
Why couldn't they at least
join me for lunch?
People's schedules fill up sometimes.
But look!
Nozomi, you're still feeling bad about yesterday, aren't you?
No I'm... not...
It was your strong spirit that
drew everyone together, Nozomi.
I think you're the only one who'll be able to make them all smile again.
But I was the one who wrecked their ornament.
What I should do?!
Everyone makes mistakes from time to time.
What's important is the follow-up.
The follow-up?
That's right. You should start by
coming back from the verge of tears.
This is... the accessory I was making?
If you never give up,
and always try your hardest,
then you're sure to succeed.
That's equally true for decorations and reconciliations.
Do you think I can do it?
I don't "think" you can; I know you can.
Hang in there.
He didn't have to go through the effort
to make this a keyholder...
But he went the extra mile for me.
All righty, I'm gonna make up with them, no matter what!
It's decided!
I'm sorry about yesterday...
Don't worry. It was nothing, really.
Pretty Cure!
Huh?! Something's appeared!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
I've paid more than my dues
working at Nightmare...
But now thanks to you brats,
I'm about to lose everything!
If I use this,
I won't ever be myself again...
But I don't care!
As long as it gives me
the power to defeat you!
Where am I?
We will now bring this meeting to order.
Today's agenda concerns
Student Council President Minazuki Karen.
Who are you?!
Highest grades in her class.
But those grades alienate her
from everyone else,
so she feels isolated from her classmates.
Now see here!
She worries about this,
but never talks to anyone about it.
She has nobody whom
she can truly call a friend.
That's a lie!
You are all alone.
What would you know about it?!
I know very well. After all...
I am your own self.
Where am I?
Hi there, Komachi-chan!
Komachi-chan! Komachi-chan! Komachi-chan!
These are...! But they couldn't be...
Komachi's Adventure
And so, Komachi set out on an adventure.
...copies of a character from the first story
I ever wrote as a child?
Komachi-chan, Komachi-chan!
Let's set out on an adventure together!
W-Wait! I have to return to where the others are!
But you don't really want to go back, do you?
You tried your hardest
to stop them from fighting,
but they just called you indecisive! Poor thing.
Aren't you sick and tired of looking after them?
T-That's not true!
But here, everything can be
the way you want it to be.
Forget about the bad things,
and spend all your time playing with us!
Girinma-san.
The loyalty you have displayed
to Nightmare is a wonder to behold!
But I do have one more little task for you.
That takes care of these two...
Rin-san! Where's Nozomi-san?
Don't know, don't care.
Eh? Aren't you two in the same class?
That doesn't mean I'm with her every minute of the day.
To be honest, I'm tired of
playing damage control.
I feel sorry for Nozomi-san when I hear you talk about her like that.
Every time you open your mouth, it's Nozomi this, Nozomi that.
Don't you have any other friends?!
When did that become any of your business?!
Don't take it out on me just because
you and Nozomi-san had an argument!
When did I take it out on you?!
You're doing it right now!
Piii...
Piiii...
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
Rouge!
Man, that's gotta hurt...
Y-You should get out of here... It's too dan-
This is Nozomi's fault, isn't it?
What?
Me?!
It happens all the time.
We always get in trouble 'cause of her.
We run ourselves ragged taking care of her,
but she doesn't even appreciate it.
That girl's no friend of ours.
That's not true!
Haven't you ever thought that...
...life would be easier without Nozomi?
Pretty Cure Lemonade Flash!
It's no use. I can't beat him alone!
Hello!
We're so busy with work these days.
Dad and Grandpa are so happy for us...
...so if we don't keep it up,
we'll let them down.
There won't be any more time for this Pretty Cure stuff.
I decided that I'd become an actress
and be Pretty Cure.
You're so naïve.
There are plenty of other girls who want to be actresses.
You don't have time to waste on anything else.
Nozomi-san is my friend! So we're going to keep on being Pretty Cure together!
You made a resolution when you entered this school:
"Becoming an actress is my biggest priority!
I don't care if I don't make any friends!"
Right?
It's completely impossible to do both.
What'll it be? Acting, or being Pretty Cure?
See? You're torn.
You could become a wonderful actress...
Nozomi! Where're the others-coco?!
Eh?! They haven't shown up here yet?!
Something appeared a little while ago-coco!
Nightmare?!
Something might've happened to those four-nuts!
Guys...!
I'm afraid your friends won't be coming.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a representative of Nightmare,
and my name is Kawarino.
He seems really dangerous-nuts! Be careful-nuts!
The other four Pretty Cures are
in custody at our headquarters.
They'd better all be okay!
That remains up to you.
I request that you relinquish the Dream Collet,
if you value your friends' lives.
If you hurt them at all, I'll break the Collet!
W-What are you saying-mil?!
I'm serious!
If you destroyed the Collet, wouldn't you be unable to restore the Palmier Kingdom?
If the alternative is having it
fall into your hands...
...then I'd rather she destroyed it-nuts!
If you want the Collet,
then take us to Nightmare's headquarters!
I'm going to get them back!
Very well.
Then allow me to invite you all
to our headquarters.
Milk, you stay behind-nuts.
Milk will come along-mil!
It's Milk's duty to protect the two of you!
You mustn't-nuts!
Milk.
I promise we'll come back,
so please watch the shop for us-coco.
Okay-coco?
Coco-sama...
This is Nightmare's headquarters-coco?!
Please be okay...
You guys!
W-W-What the?!
Why's there a Pretty Cure here?!
She insisted upon coming here,
so I brought her.
Why would you do that!?
D-Despariah-sama!
Despariah?!
That's Despariah-coco?!
The chief culprit behind the destruction
of the Palmier Kingdom-nuts!
Give me back my friends!
"Friends"? There are
no such things in this place.
Don't play dumb!
Ah, perhaps by "friends," you mean...
...these four?
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
I'm sorry, everyone... I know I'm always causing you so many problems...
What're you talking about?
We've come this far thanks to you!
I'm so happy you came to find us!
We're the ones who should apologize.
It's strange. When we're all together,
I feel this power welling up inside me...
Let's go! As long as the five of us
are together, we'll always find a way!
Yes!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The New Power of the Five!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?