Note: Original Aesir subs are in subtitle track 3.
Because I was so careless,
everybody got really mad at each other.
And before I could make up with them,
they were all taken to Nightmare's headquarters!
I went with Coco and Nuts to get them back, but...
What I found waiting for us was... a nightmare.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Original Translations: Eggplant, Aesir
Encode: K.o.R   Retiming, Editing, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
W-What the heck?!
Just... what in blazes is going on here?!
Are they... really Pretty Cure?!
You've all...
These are...
Nightmare masks-coco!
How can this be-nuts?!
Rin-chan! Komachi-san!
Urara! Karen-san!
What's going on?!
Hey, come on! Answer me!
You guys!
You waste your time.
No matter how many times you call out, your voice will never reach them.
If I take these weird masks off...!
That is futile.
Once they're applied,
removing them is simply impossible.
Those are the Masks of Despair.
Masks of... Despair?
The New Power of the Five!
Your companions have all sunken into the depths of despair.
How could you...
How could you do this to them?!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
Whoa now, don't fire off
your Dream Attack in here!
Our headquarters will be ruined!
Bunbee-san, there's no need for you to get so flustered.
Huh?! W-What the?!
Dream!
Oh, so you still cling to some last hope.
However, what do you intend to achieve all by yourself?
Your friends, as you knew them, are gone.
Such soothing despair...
Despariah-sama, what shall we do with these people?
My desire is for one thing -
the Dream Collet, and nothing else.
Do with them as you please.
As you command.
Well then, ladies of Pretty Cure...
This way, please.
Don't do it-coco!
Come to your senses-nuts!
Now now!
It's wrong to butt in where you're not wanted, you two!
Farewell, Pretty Cure.
Stop it-coco!
Rouge!
Lemonade!
Aqua!
Mint!
Dream!
If you two don't hand over
the Dream Collet without a fuss,
I'm gonna toss you  in there, too.
How 'bout them apples?
I won't let you-mil!
Milk!
What's with this little... ow, that hurt!
What is this thing?!
Why'd you follow us-nuts?!
It's Milk's duty to protect the two of you-mil!
Coco-sama!
Don't do it-nuts!
Coco!
Where are you all?!
Dream!
What's the matter, Nozomi?
Um, what?
You guys...
Hey now, if you don't hurry up and eat,
this feast'll go cold.
Feast?
It all looks so yummy!
What is this?
Nozomi, aren't you going to eat?
Eh? Of course I am! Time to dig in!
Pretty Cure, having fallen into despair,
are immersed in a tranquil world
where they can forget their harsh reality.
I should mention that nobody has ever managed to escape that world.
Oh, that's quite impressive...
Hey, stop struggling!
Let us go-mil!
We'll never give you the Dream Collet-nuts!
Why you stubborn little... Hey!
Mmm, yummy!
What could this thing be?
Nozomi.
Why so serious?
That thing doesn't make a bit of difference.
Don't worry your pretty little head about it.
Forget about the bad stuff,
and enjoy this delicious food with us.
Okay!
But...
I just...
...feel like I'm forgetting
something really important.
That sound!
Dream!
DREEEAM!!
Come on, wake up...
Nozomi.
Hey, how did the five of us
get together, again?
We're in different grades,
and our personalities aren't similar at all.
That's just too minor to matter, isn't it?
What matters is that we're
enjoying ourselves right now, isn't it?
Getting along with one another,
and spending fun times together...
...is what friendship is all about, am I right?
Yeah, but... But still...
What's important is the follow-up.
That's right.
It's wrong to just have fun!
Back then, you taught me
to never give up on anything,
and to try with all my might!
NOZOMI!!
COCO!!!
What's this? Impossible!
Stop it-nuts!
You stupid little...!
Nozomi...
Coco?!
Nozomi!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Thank goodness you're all right.
I heard your voice, Coco...
I was able to remember what was important because you called out to me.
"What's important"?
There's something I want to do...
...and a dream I want to make come true!
Nozomi!
I have you now!
Impossible!
Kawarino-san?
She shattered...
...her mask?!
Coco.
Dream!
Come on, let's go get the others!
Right!
Mint... Rouge...
Lemonade... Aqua...
Just hold on, okay?
We're on our way.
You guys, we've come to pick you up.
This place is not our world.
Let's go home together!
Sorry, but I can't go home.
I'm scared...
I don't have the confidence.
It's hopeless now...
It's not hopeless!
As long as the five of us are together, there's nothing we can't do!
We can do anything!
The five of us...
...together...
...can do...
...anything?
Yes, we can!
Rin-chan! Urara!
Komachi-san! Karen-san!
You guys...
It feels so warm...
I feel kind of... relieved.
We haven't all held hands
like this before, have we?
Strange. It's like my anxiety
is just melting away...
I'm so sorry. I'm always causing
all sorts of problems...
...and making you guys bail me out of trouble.
What're you talking about?
Huh?
You've always been bailing us out.
Rin-chan!
If anyone should apologize, it's us.
Our feelings got mixed up, and we started acting childishly towards each other.
That's why we all became scattered apart.
But now we've finally
gotten back together again!
Then...
Can we stay together from now on?
Of course!
You'll join me in chasing our dreams?
Yes!
W-What is this?!
The light of hope?!
Coco-sama!
You're all safe!
This cannot be!
How could my plan have failed?!
Ah, you mustn't do that!
If you get serious in here,
our headquarters will end up destroyed!
Hey, I'll make us some tea now, okay?
Despariah-sama will be angry with you!
So please, calm down!
You have a point.
Man, that was a close one.
Consider me surprised.
Even my calculations cannot
account for everything.
I never imagined you all would've shattered the Masks of Despair.
We're not going to let you...
...have your way!
Sadly, you won't be getting your way, either.
Your suffering is caused by
that so-called friend of yours.
I don't care what happens to me!
I just want to be with Nozomi!
Rin-chan!
Hmm, is that so?
You should have abandoned
your friends and saved yourself.
Now, your dreams will never come to fruition.
I'd never abandon my friends!
And I won't give up on my dream, either!
Oh really now?
Urara, I know you'll make
your dream come true!
Yeah! 'Cause you've got us cheering her on!
Nozomi-san, Rin-san...!
Once again, I see your friends have
left the tedious chores to you.
This is just Komachi's kindness at work!
And I know that better than anyone!
What could a loner like you possibly understand?
Karen isn't alone!
We're all here for her!
I won't let her feel lonely ever again!
Komachi...!
If the five of us are together...
...we can do anything!
This delay is beyond my projections.
Very well. But I'm only
doing this once, you understand?
Dream!
Are you okay-coco?!
I'll be fine. You guys go hide somewhere safe.
Milk is... Milk is utterly useless-mil!
All I do is cause you all problems-mil...
I'm so sorry-mil...
Milk...
When we get back to Nuts House,
let's rebuild that butterfly decoration together, okay?
Dream...
Have you felt the absolute difference between our powers?
Have you reconsidered the idea of giving up?
We didn't even consider it to begin with!
Coco and Nuts' homeland...
...the Palmier Kingdom!
We're going to bring it back!
Very well!
It's time to bring down
the curtain on this farce!
We'll rebuild it together-mil!
We'll all rebuild that butterfly decoration together-mil!
What the heck is that?!
It might be a new power for Pretty Cure-nuts!
Everybody, unite your feelings-coco!
Anyways, let's give it a shot!
Yes!
Together with the powers of Dreams and Hope...
O Five Lights...
...right here and now:
Pretty Cure Five Explosion!!
What on Earth just happened?
I was surprised too-coco!
I think Milk's wishes to save you summoned this new power-nuts!
Milk, you did really well-coco!
Coco-sama...!
I'm so glad you're all in one piece.
How perilous.
They were able to radiate the light of hope
amidst the darkness of despair.
These legendary warriors, Pretty Cure...
...are a force to be reckoned with.
It's finished!
Wow, that's a nice job!
It'll work for the shop.
Milk helped us too!
I had to help. I couldn't stand to watch Nozomi the Klutz screw it up again.
What was that?!
Now now.
Milk, you wanted to build it along with them, didn't you?
What's the matter, Milk? Your face is all red.
Hey, she's blushing! She's blushing!
I-I am not-mil!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Rin-chan, check out these plans for summer vacation!
I spent all night working on them!
A plan?
Yeah! It's a big, exciting event that'll allow the five of us
to become even better friends!
Or, "Pretty Cure Camp" for short.
Abbreviation fail.
Moving on, let's all go shopping for the trip! It's decided!
What, already?!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
The Great Pretty Cure
Training Camp Operation!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?