Those creeps at Nightmare...
...tried to split us apart.
But we'll never be defeated by cheap tricks like that!
By uniting our feelings,
we managed to pull through.
But... I never want to feel that way again.
From now on, we're all going to stay together,
no matter what happens!
Good morning!
Huh? Where's everybody else?
I haven't seen them.
Didn't summer vacation start today?
I'm sure they've got other things to do.
Ehhh?!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Rin-chan's off playing futsal.
Urara's got a concert.
Komachi-san's writing one of her stories.
And Karen-san's got
a Student Council meeting!
I'm so bored...
They're all enjoying their summer break.
Why not try making plans for your own?
I already have! And I came here
because I wanted to show everyone else!
"The First Annual Pretty Cure Training Camp"
Ta-da!
"The First Annual Pretty Cure Training Camp?!"
That's right!
The Great Pretty Cure Training Camp Operation!
Umm, Kawarino-san?
I wanted to tell you how much I regret what happened the other day...
Or should I say I'm repenting for it?
Who'd have thought Girinma-kun would turn into something like that...?
Pretty Cure 5...
Huh?!
How were they able to repulse
the power of despair like that?
And that power!
Just what happened to them back there?!
T-They certainly are a nuisance, aren't they?
Why?!
Kawarino-san, maybe I can be of some assistance.
N-Now look! What do you think you're playing at?!
Arachnea-kun, wasn't it?
Yes, sir!
Look, you can't just butt in like that!
Kawarino-san and I were in the middle of an important discussion!
Do you have some sort of plan, Arachnea-kun?
True, Pretty Cure do possess strong powers.
But if we could counteract that power,
they'd be left without
a leg to stand on.
Hrm... Despariah-sama is quite flustered over them at the moment.
Do you believe you could calm her nerves?
Of course, sir. Just leave it to me.
I'll be counting on you.
Thank you very much.
A-A-Arachnea-kun! Hey, Kawarino-san,
are you sure about this?!
One must be flexible enough to deal with rank-and-file employees.
Despariah-sama will surely be interested in the results of my judgment.
Was he ignoring me?!
So anyway!
Let's start our First Annual Pretty Cure Camp meeting!
First up on the agenda is...
...what snacks we're gonna bring!
Shouldn't we choose a place first?
If we don't know where we're going...
But snacks are really important too!
See?
That's really not the problem here, is it?
Besides, camps always remind me of...
Run faster-coco!
Nobody said being Pretty Cure was easy-nuts!
Go for it-mil! Faster, faster-mil!
It hurts just to think about it...
Sounds like fun to me-mil!
I could train Nozomi till she drops-mil!
It's not  gonna be like that!!
I've got a real reason for doing this!
C'mon, just say you'll come, okay?
What is this "reason"?
Let's go!
Well, I guess I'm up for some traveling.
But how are we gonna pay for this?
Snacks are limited to 300 yen apiece, right?
No, I'm talking about the travel costs!
It does seem rather expensive.
And will it work with everyone's schedules?
I'm sure it'll be fine!
Hmm, I do have a few jobs lined up...
And I've got clubs, too.
Not you too, Rin-chan?!
Karen, what about the Student Council?
No, we don't have any meetings planned.
Let's see... All I've got planned
is a trip to our resort.
Eh?! A resort?!
A resort-mil?!
Ah, I call it a resort,
but it's really not that impressive!
Yeah, but you also called Nuts House a "small storeroom," Karen-san.
So that means it must be a really huge resort!
It's not that huge. It's just one tiny little island.
An island-mil?!
An island?!
You own an island?!
The whole thing?!
Y-Yeah...
She owns an island...
The whole thing...
A-Amazing...
She's not in our league...
You really are full of surprises, Karen.
You think so?
Well, it would  be rather big for just Jiiya and me to stay in...
Yeah, it would!
It'd be waaay too big for the two of you alone! So we'll tag along!
Nozomi-san, I think you're pushing it.
Yeah, we can't expect Karen to subsidize our vacations.
Resorts are private places, after all.
Yeah, that's true.
Ah, I don't mind! If you can all make it,
I'd love for you to come with us.
Okay, our First Annual Pretty Cure Training Camp
will be held at Karen-san's resort!
It's decided!
All righty, tomorrow we'll go shopping to stock up for the trip.
Isn't she just a bundle of energy?
I can't wait for our resort camp!
It's just like Nozomi-san to organize a camp for us.
Somewhere along the line,
we got dragged along at her pace.
True, the only reason we're all here together is
because she got us caught up in all this.
It's kinda nostalgic...
I remember it like it happened yesterday.
Nozomi's always so carefree like that...
But she'll always pull through in the clutch.
Yeah. Just like last time...
I'll never forget what Nozomi
did for us back there.
And we're all here together again because her feelings reached us.
Nozomi-san's just full of mysteries.
And now, Crazy Nozomi says she
wants us to go to a training camp.
Let's do just that.
Yay!
Sheesh, is she running on "Nozomi Time" again?
I'm sure she overslept-coco!
Must be-mil!
Must be-nuts!
You really think so?
Sorry I'm late!
Nozomi!
Sorry, but I lost some time making this!
Ta-da! Our shopping list for today!
It's nothing but snacks!
Aww, what's wrong with that?
Come on, let's go!
Hah! Enjoy your fun while it lasts!
Potato chips, okay!
Ah, wait for me!
I'm gonna add some curry-flavored ones too~
Ah, I like those too!
Hold it right there.
We don't need this many snacks, do we?
We don't need these, or these...
So, Rin-chan, I assume we don't need this chocolate?
Ah, I need that!
Chocolate-mil...
At least they're having fun.
They're all such children.
Why can't they stick to the essentials?
Huh?
Cream puffs detected!
I think orange is the better choice.
That's just your preference, isn't it?
There're also people who prefer grape.
I found the mamedaifuku!
Yes yes, we get it,
you like grape, Karen-san.
You could've just said so.
That's not what I meant! You just need to keep others' preferences in mind.
U-Umm...
Why don't we just get both?
Faster-coco!
I feel a need for speed-mil!
Stop running!
I can't wait to eat these mamedaifuku-nuts!
All right, we're done!
Not so fast!
What's up, Rin-chan?
Can we afford all this?
Hmmm... well, I'm sure it'll work out!
No, it won't!
We didn't need this, or this, or THIS!
Eh?! No way!
Hmm... or this, either.
Ah, we do need that!
What the heck are we gonna use a stereo for?
See, this is the reason we're holding this camp!
Nightmare?!
I'm so terribly sorry to interrupt,
but there's something I'm just dying to get ahold of!
But it doesn't seem to be
for sale here...
It's that Dream Collet of yours!
We'll never hand it over...
...to the likes of you!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
That's...
Heh, that'll do just fine!
Pay close attention!
I'll show you just how useless
your powers have become!
What's going on?!
All of our attacks are being deflected away!
If you can't even handle this,
you're more pathetic than I thought!
Hang on, everyone!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Dream Attack!
Nice one, Dream!
You did it!
It's not down yet-coco!
No way...
Don't tell me that  didn't work...
Isn't it time to give up and hand over
the Dream Collet already?
No...
We'll never give up!
Give me back that stereo!
That's the whole reason I'm holding this camp!
Huh?!
That's... the reason?
What do you mean?
I wanted a way to remember the time we spent together!
All the fun times we had together, all the laughter we shared!
We could just spend the whole day talking...
...and record our voices with that stereo.
If we had a way we could always remember the good times,
...then we'd always have a way to get through the bad times, no matter what!
That was my plan!
I don't ever want to feel like I did back then!
Dream...
Hmph! How utterly pointless. So what?
You guys...
Dream... we all feel the same way!
I don't ever want to relive those feelings.
But it's all right now!
We'll never forget how you felt...
...or the words you said to us!
Because your words have been etched deep in our hearts!
We all believe in you, Dream!
We won't let ourselves doubt you
like we did before!
All together now!
That's why we'll get through this!
It's about time to end this!
This isn't the end!
We won't let you stand in our way!
There are still so many words left to say...
So many words left to fill our hearts,
never to be forgotten!
What is that-coco?!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Nobody told me you had an attack like that!
What is this power?
Dream, that was amazing-coco!
That's your new power-nuts!
No... it's not just mine. It's our power!
Dream!
Yes!
Nozomi-san, are you really okay with this?
Yeah... we can just keep our memories in here instead, right?
But still, I'm pretty shocked.
Eh?
That you gave this so much thought.
Really?
I assumed you just wanted to play around all day.
I was rather surprised as well.
Jeez, I do think things through occasionally, you know!
Nozomi-san, you're really
such an amazing person.
Thank you, Nozomi-san.
All righty, let's head to the checkout! It's decided!
Now hold on! There're still plenty of things in here we don't need!
Eh? I put the stereo back,
so that should cover it.
No, that's not what I mean.
We don't need more than
one bag of potato chips!
We can't transport raw fish.
And don't buy riceballs now.
Also, we don't need this grape juice.
Ehhh?! But I  need that!
Oh? I thought you were just
"considering others' preferences"?
But I like grape...
Maybe I should add my favorite drink, too.
Not you too, Komachi-san!
Come on, quit acting so childish.
Hey, don't put more things in!
And who added all these mamedaifuku and cream puffs, anyway?
I-I don't know-nuts!
It wasn't me-coco!
Hey, there's loads of chocolate in there too!
It's chock full-mil!
Oh jeez, not you three as well!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Summer, the southern isles, barbecues!
Nuts-san's running the barbecue, huh...
Hey, Komachi-san, isn't that iron skewer a little hot?!
Nuts! Come give me a hand over here!
I'm fine, really! Look, look, see?
What happened to the Komachi-san I know?!
There must be something off with me.
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Full Throttle Romance Resort Life!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?