Ah, the wind feels so nice...
Whoa! This is amazing...
This is so awesome!
Huh?
It's all sooooo yummy!
That's  what amazed them?
M'lady!
This year's vacation is shaping up to be a pleasant and lively one.
I suppose so!
Perhaps a little too  lively...
But it's a nice change of pace.
Hey, what're we gonna do
when we get to the resort?
Is this really the only
place we can hide-mil?
You'd better let Coco-sama and Nuts-sama out of here as soon as we arrive-mil!
Shhh! Jiiya-san will find you, Milk!
We can't stay in this
cramped little bag forever!
Be quiet!
Milk, stop wriggling-coco!
It's already cramped enough-nuts!
Ah! Nozomi-san, look over there!
Huh? What is it?
Land ho!
That's incredible...
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Huh? Wha-? Where?
Where on... Where the heck am I?!
Fancy...
It's like I'm on a movie set!
This is your room, Yumehara-sama.
Eh? Mine?
That's right. Natsuki-sama is next door to you...
Next to her room is Akimoto-sama's room.
And on the other side is...
Whoa, wait, hold on!
We each have our own rooms?
That's right. This resort has a total of 20 guest rooms.
Well then, I shall leave you all
to relax and unwind.
You two're awake?
T-This place is just like...
It's just like the royal palace-coco!
Ehh?! You two got to live in a luxurious place like this one?!
That's right-coco!
Well, I guess you are  princes, after all...
Full Throttle Romance Resort Life!
All right, let's get going!
We're gonna have a ton of fun!
Yay!
First thing we're doing is hitting the beach!
One moment, please.
Why not try to catch some dinner
while you're out enjoying yourselves?
Just bring back anything you manage to catch.
The Minazuki family's 1st-class chef will happily prepare it for you.
Anything?
Indeed; the ocean around this island is also the property of the Minazuki family.
So you are free to catch anything you wish from it.
So it's all-you-can-catch, all-you-can-eat?
This is awesome!
Food always seems to taste better when
you've personally gone out and caught it.
All righty, we'll go catch some side dishes
while we're out playing!
It's decided!
Okay!
My, my... it's not like they're under any time constraints.
What do you plan to do?
Oh, I know!
This place is exactly like what I had in mind...
Komachi?
Huh? What?
Oh, I'm just going to take a stroll around the resort.
I think it'll give me
some ideas for my story.
Just be careful in the woods, all right? They can be quite dangerous.
I will!
And what about you, m'lady?
Hmm... good question.
Maybe I'll just stick with what I always do.
Very well, m'lady.
The same as ever it is.
I'm gonna catch a tuna!
Go for it, Nozomi-coco!
I'm good at this, huh?
Look how far I casted it!
Huh? Coco?
The setting can be deep in the forest...
This feels so nice-coco!
She really put me through hell
back there-coco...
Did you catch anything-coco?
Look! I caught an octopus!
An octopus-coco!?!
Here you go! You have fun playing now-nuts!
You should watch where you're going.
I've never seen him
smile like that before...
Sorry, did I startle you?
Are you looking after the Pinkies?
Nuts-san, aren't you going to join Coco-san and the others?
I'd rather not.
But why?
The Pinkies wanted to play, too.
And somebody has to keep an eye on them.
I suppose so.
Look at this! I caught a whole bunch of stuff!
So did I!
I caught us something cool too!
Check this out!
That's not how fishing works-coco!
Huh? What's that noise?
Huh?! Karen...-san?!
No way!
She's so cool!
It feels so nice up here.
Yeah.
Maybe I should have
brought a book with me.
I could probably read to my heart's content up here.
I guess so.
Hey, where did you like to read, back in your homeland?
Somewhere quiet. Much like here.
Like here?
There was a relaxing hill like this back in the Palmier Kingdom too.
I see.
It must have been a beautiful place.
I wanted to protect it.
We'll get you back there... one day.
We'll make sure you can go back to that hill in your homeland.
The five of us will do our best!
W-What is it?
You've even got the Pinkies sleeping peacefully...
Komachi, you really are the Pretty Cure of Tranquility.
N-Not at all. I'm really not that tranquil...
It's true, though.
Just being around you seems to soothe me.
U-Umm, I really should get back
to the others...
Oh dear... what on earth is the matter with me?
I feel so sluggish after that...
Coco-sama! Nuts-sama!
Do you know where Coco-sama and Nuts-sama are-mil?!
I think they went to play with Nozomi and the others...
Why didn't they wake me up-mil?!
You were sleeping so soundly that Coco didn't want to disturb you.
Coco-sama said that?!
Yes, he did.
Didn't he want Milk there with him?
Look, Milk.
Why don't you relax and
take it easy while you're here?
I imagine Coco didn't wake you up because he had the same idea.
Wait just a second.
Here you go.
Why don't we just drink tea until they come back?
It's so deliciously cooling-mil!
This isn't half-bad, Karen-mil!
Oh, thank you very much.
Here you go~
Sorry for the wait!
This is so good!
It's like 100 times more delicious than normal food!
Please feel free to eat
as much as you like.
Okay!
Man, all his talk about
"the Minazuki family's 1st-class chef"
was just self-promotion.
That was quite a long stroll you took.
Did it give you any good ideas?
Komachi?
Eh? U-Umm...
Hot!
K-Komachi, are you all right?!
Y-Yeah...
Ah, I'm starvin'...
Huh?! Somethin' smells damn good...
Now we're talkin'!
That's weird. I'm sure it was around here somewhere...
There's only so much
you can see by moonlight.
Rin-chan's gonna get mad at me again!
Why not just look for it
tomorrow morning?
No way, I've gotta find it now or else!
All right! I found the towel that Rin-chan lent me!
That's great!
Thanks for helping me find it, Coco.
You're very welcome.
Shall we head back?
Wow!
Nozomi? Huh?
Nozomi...
So pretty...
There're so many stars.
There really are...
Hey, could you see the stars
back in the Palmier Kingdom?
Yeah, we could.
It looked just like this...
so very beautiful.
But now, it's...
Don't worry. You'll be able to see the stars from your home again...
...once we gather up all the Pinkies, and make your dream come true!
Nozomi...
Hey, what's the first thing you're
gonna do when you get back home?
Good question.
I guess I'd like to show you around the Palmier Kingdom.
Really? I can really come visit?!
Of course you can!
Wow! I can't wait to see it!
I wonder what it's like. Hey, you said
you lived in a castle, right?
I've always wanted to go to a ball!
If that is your wish.
May I take your hand, princess?
O-O-Of course... m-my prince.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What? What's so funny?
Coco-sama!
Ah, Coco-sama!
Ah, w-wait a second!
Owwww...
I've been looking all over for you-mil!
Milk!
Are you all right, Nozomi?
Yeah...
Komachi, Coco and the others still haven't come back-nuts...
I'm gonna go look for them-nuts.
I'll go with you.
Thanks.
Jeez...
Seriously, what are Coco and Milk doing?
You really do worry about them, Nuts-san.
Didn't you burn your hand earlier?
Is it all right?
I-It's fine, really...
Are you really okay?
That was Milk-san's voice!
Nozomi!
Nozomi-san, are you okay?
Ya just had ta go eat
all the good grub for yerselves...
Nozomi-san!
Nozomi!
Ya really know how ta piss me off!
You again?
You really don't give up!
Let's go!
Right!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Lemonade, look after Coco and the others!
Okay!
How'd ya like that?!
But ya ain't gettin' off that lightly, ya hear?!
Take cover!
It's so powerful....
There's no way we can fight it...
We can't even hurt that thing!
What're we gonna do?!
Ain't nothin' ya can  do!
I'm gonna crush yer stupid island!
T-The island!
He's destroying it-nuts...
This is horrible... Please, stop!
Why?
Why can't you people think of
anything except destruction?!
I wanted to protect it.
How could you destroy such beauty?
You'll pay for this!
I'm not letting you get away with this any longer!
The earth tremors of a young girl's anger... Take this!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Mint Shield?
It keeps on expanding...
Mint's abilities have powered up-coco!
T-The heck's with that thing?!
The heck are ya doin'?! Stop that!
Mint protected the island for us-nuts...
Does it still hurt?
No, it's fine! Really!
Look, I bandaged it and everything.
Good to know. And I'm glad
this island didn't get destroyed.
Thank you, Komachi.
Huh? Komachi-san, what's the matter?
U-Umm, I...
Oh, I know! Is your room also too big to feel comfy in?
Y-Y-Yeah, that's right!
Same here.
M'lady?
Good morning.
M'lady? It's time to get up.
As none of you have gotten up yet, I assume you're all together...
Ah, very well. I'll call you again
in an hour or so.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Nozomi, let's get out of here already.
Don't be like that, Rin-chan!
We're going to see the famous ghost of Cinq Lumieres Academy!
Look, I'm telling you there's no such thing!
So let's just go, okay? Okay?
What's the matter, Rin-san, are you scaaaared?
They come for you when you're scared...
Ah! Behind you!
N-Noooooooooo!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Rin-chan's Date with a Handsome Ghost!?
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?