Listen up.
In the old school building, which is no longer used...
In that place...
...it will appear.
W-W-What'll appear?
What's in there?
It is...
...a ghost.
Long ago, somewhere in the area around the old school building...
...stood a mansion belonging to one Count Rosett.
Count Rosett supposedly had a wonderful girlfriend.
But one day...
...she passed away in an
unforeseeable accident.
The anguished Count,
unable to accept her death,
waited in vain for her to return.
However, the Count's determination could not stop him from succumbing to illness.
I feel bad for the Count...
And every year thereafter on the anniversary of his lover's death,
the Count's ghost has wandered the old school building.
And then, whenever he
comes across a girl who is...
...around the same age as his girlfriend...
He snatches them up,
just... like... this...!
Rin-chan?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Timing, QC: Force_Gaia       Translation, etc.: Zalis
Pretty Cure!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
You called for me, Bunbee-san?
So sorry to inconvenience you.
Hm?
The one who called for you was...
...none other than I.
K-Kawarino-san?!
Arachnea-kun, you certainly have been diligent lately.
Although the encounter ended with your defeat,
you had Pretty Cure in very dire straits.
Nonetheless, there was
something missing in your work.
Something missing, you say?
Indeed, there was.
You lack the power of fear!
Fear?
That's right, fear.
Those who are gripped by fear
will exhaust all of their energy.
You must instill fear within Pretty Cure.
And then, drop them into the depths of despair!
Yes-
I-I understand.
Rin-chan's Date with a Handsome Ghost!?
So why are we going to
the old school building, again?
Because, the Count's ghost
is supposed to appear today!
I-I never knew we had a place like this at our school.
I-It lives up to its scary reputation.
Komachi?
Isn't it exciting?
Uh, no. Not exciting at all.
Rin-san sure is a scaredy-cat.
That's for sure. Rin-chan's always been afraid of ghosts and stuff.
There's no way ghosts exist-nuts.
If you're that scared,
you don't have to come with us-mil!
Here. Now, shall we get going?
A-Are we ready for this-coco?
Hmm, where should we start?
Pretty Cure... I'll make sure you taste plenty of terror.
Y-Yep, this place is kinda scary.
That's right.
Hey, I think I just heard something.
Really?
Yes, there was some kind of noise.
Hear no evil...
I'm brimming with anticipation...
Well, put a lid on it.
Hey!
Wait a sec...
It's all right. She just spooks easily, that's all.
Shall we follow her?
Oh man, what WAS that?
M-M-Masuko-san?!
Don't yell so loud.
What're you doing here?
What else could  I be doing here?
I am Cinq Lumieres News's
chief editor, Masuko Mika!
I'm here for no other reason than
to get the scoop on Count Rosett!
Don't freak me out like that.
So that skeleton bit before was your doing, Masuko-san?
Huh? What're you talking about?
Masuko-san...
W-What?
D-Do you want some...
help with your reporting?
S-Sure, why not? Let's investigate this place together!
Rin-chan!
Rin-san!
Rin-san, where are you?
Rin-san, where'd you go?
It's pitch black... which room IS this?
Rin!
I-I'm sorry.
Karen-san?
Karen?
I-I just got a little startled!
By the thunder.
I wasn't scared at all-mil.
Don't worry. They're just sculptures.
O-Oh, right.
This must be the art room.
Those are pretty old sculptures-nuts.
Up close, he looks kind of dashing.
This person must be Count Rosett!
Huh, he's the guy?
Huh?
He's holding something.
What could it be?
A hair pin?
Hey, you two!
What is it?
Might this be...?
Rin-san?
W-Wait, what?
M-Masuko-san, why are we
going through the science room?
Why not? Ghosts always appear in science rooms.
I-It's a little scary,
but my journalist's soul is blazing.
Not me, no burning here.
C-Count Rosett?
Get out here!
I'm fine if he doesn't...
What're you saying!? If he doesn't show up,
we've got no story!
Again, I'm perfectly fine with that!
Why?! Why, why, why, why's that skeleton-?
I don't believe this!!
W-Wait up! Don't leave me behind!!
It... can't be...
Pretty Cure, where have you gone?
T-THERE IT IS!!!
Rin-chan? Rin-chan!
Hey, Rin-chan? Wake up, Rin-chan!
Rin-chan, why were you sleeping out here?
I-I-I s-s-saw... a-a g-g-ghost!!
Wait, Rin-chan, calm down!
You're not making any sense.
Rin-san, do you think you saw Count Rosett?
Y-Yeah, I bet I did!
What? Really?!
I'm telling the truth here!
It was dark, so I couldn't tell for sure, but...
...there's a good chance I saw a tall man!
And he stretched out his right hand like this...
Was that man wearing a super-long coat?
Was he holding a hair pin?
U-Um, he might have had one...
Hey, those might be the same clothes as...
The sculpture we just saw might have had the same hair pin!
There's no mistaking it.
The man Rin-san met...
...was Count Rosett!
K-Komachi?
But, why would he give Rin-san the hair pin?
In the art room, we saw a picture of a girl that looked just like Rin-chan.
Could they be connected?
Huh?
The Count... a hair pin...
And the woman in the painting, who resembles Rin-san...
The woman in the painting...
must've been the Count's girlfriend!
K-Komachi?!
The Count wanted to give that hair pin
to his deceased girlfriend...
...and he's been waiting here all this time,
just to do that!
Now I get it.
How can you be so easily convinced?
That's it! It has to be!
He mistook Rin-san for his girlfriend,
so he tried to give her the hair pin!
Makes sense to me.
Not to me!
Rin-san, you should've accepted the hair pin.
She's right. Let's help the Count satisfy his unfulfilled desires!
You're the key, Rin-chan!
We can't do it without you!
Well, she may be right...
But I'm not his girlfriend in the first place!
Besides, I'm scared of meeting that ghost again...
I'm scared, afraid, terrified!
It's absolutely impossible for me!
Rin-chan!
Rin-san!
We've got to grant the Count's wish!
Wha? No way, no how,
not happening. I'm too scared!
Anybody home?
It really feels like he's going to appear...
That's right.
Rin-chan, good luck!
So I really have to go?
Yeah, yeah!
Gee, I guess there really isn't a ghos-
So you've finally made it.
Huh?
What is this place?
So he really existed...
Count Rosett...
I've been waiting for you all this time.
I've been waiting for the day to come...
...when I could give you this.
Um, I'm not the person you were waiting for...
What?
Perfect! I couldn't have asked for a better work environment than this space.
Now, Pretty Cure! You will taste fear like never before!
Rin-chan!
Nozomi, everyone...!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
This way!
Not my mansion...
How dare you wreck the Count's precious mansion?!
What nonsense is that?
I'm not wrecking anything.
This is nothing but a false world!
You're wrong!
The Count's feelings for his girlfriend are the real deal!
Every corner of this world is filled with the Count's true emotions!
It's not a false world at all!
The Count's been waiting for a long, long time...
...and I won't forgive you for trampling on his feelings!
And yet, you were just trembling in fear of the Count's ghost!
Once his feelings were communicated...
...there was nothing to be afraid of!
Let's go, team!
Yes!
Pretty Cure!!
I'm not gonna forgive you guys.
The powerful flame of
a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
This power is...
Amazing...
Is that Rouge's new power?
Thank you so much.
Um, I can't exactly take this.
I'm not the girl you were waiting for.
I'd like you to have it.
But...!
You fought so hard for my sake, so...
I want you to take it.
Will you accept it?
Yes.
Thank you.
But that Count was
a pretty cool guy, wasn't he?
Was he your type, Rin-chan?
Are you crazy, or just stupid?
It's an emergency!
An emergency, I say!
A skeleton started to run, and chased after me!
It was a ghost, a ghost! A ghost appeared!
T-There's no such thing as ghosts, right?
Did you get any pictures?
Well, I didn't get the chance...
But I'm telling the truth here!
In that case...
...let's go back in there and take some photos!
Eh?! N-No thanks.
I don't need to see any ghosts.
I've had enough of scary things like that!
There's no need to be afraid of ghosts or spirits.
Rin-chan?
I'm sure they experience the same feelings we do.
And once those feelings are communicated,
there's nothing to fear.
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Grilled squid, takoyaki, shaved ice, goldfish scooping, yo-yo bobbing!
You're really excited about the summer festival, aren't you?
Yes!
And, and, you're preparing a special assortment at your store, right?
Time to advertise, Komachi-san!
Huh? Oh, right.
How about some cool desserts in this hot summer?
Please drop by and see us!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Record of Komachi's
Summer Festival Struggles.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?