Special shaved ice?
Yes. I wanted to use traditional topping flavors...
...to create a different variety of shaved ice.
That sounds like it would go
quite well with the summer festival.
I agree! Let's pair it up with mamedaifuku!
That sounds so good-nuts!
I'd put seven servings of youkan on it!
Urara, don't encourage them.
I'll take cream puffs-coco!
I'm fine with chocolate-mil.
Those aren't exactly "traditional."
All right, I'll do all I can to help at the summer festival!
It's decided!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
So, what do you think? Huh?!
As you can see, I've thoroughly researched Pretty Cure.
We're currently dedicating all of our efforts...
...to finding some kind of weak point.
Umm, the sooner we manage to determine their weakness,
the sooner we'll see promising developments in this area.
All right!
Unless...
Hm?
Gamao-kun?
Hm, we employ him as well?
Well, is there anything amiss...?
What is Gamao-kun presently doing?
Gamao-kun... Let's see...
What's so special about Gamao?
I'm so hungry...
Record of Komachi's
Summer Festival Struggles
Table / Paper Cups
How's this?
Looks nice! Check mine out, too.
So, are things going well?
Yes, for the most part.
Ah, do you think I should have Dad taste it, too?
His tastes aren't all that refined.
Every year, he makes us do
all the work for the festival.
Why don't you do things your way this time?
Did things go badly last year, Sis?
Let's just say it wasn't all smooth sailing.
That's why I'm glad you're so into this.
You've got plenty of friends to help you out,
so things should be fine if you work together.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that's right, we got a whole bunch of summer mandarins
from Grandma's place.
Do you girls want to eat them?
Sure, thanks. We'll take some with us later.
Thanks for waiting!
Okay!
Oh yeah! Time for a taste test!
Let's eat!
Soo good~
My cheeks are...
...getting frozen.
There's anko, honey, and youkan... all the flavors are just right.
I've never eaten anything this delicious-coco!
It's good-nuts!
Tasty-mil!
Komachi-san, this is a guaranteed hit!
Tomorrow can't come soon enough!
Thanks, everybody.
My mouth's watering already...
Akimoto-san?
Coming!
Ah, thanks. You can leave it right there.
We'll put it in the freezer later.
You sure about that? Whatever...
So hungry...
I haven't eaten anything in three days...
Huh?
Ice, huh?
Japanese Confectionery
Komachi
It can't be! My ice isn't there!
That was so not filling.
Hello there!
Karen, what do I do!?
We've got a problem!
We've made the circuit, but nobody has any.
Hate to say it, but we're all sold out.
And I won't be able to
get more until this evening.
I guess it's the same story everywhere.
Without the ice, we can't open our stand.
Komachi, you mustn't give up!
But...
If you don't do everything within your power,
you'll regret it later.
Didn't you say the same thing
that one time, Komachi?
Do you remember? It was for
a Social Studies project, two years ago...
Social Studies Observation Project
Free-choice Site
Back then, I'd just become Class Rep,
and I was full of enthusiasm. But...
What? An emergency shutdown?!
But that doesn't give me enough time-
Y-Yes.
Yes.
What, they're on a break?!
Yes. A machine broke down at
the factory we're going to observe,
so there's a work stoppage.
What'll we do?
At this point, I think it'll be hard to find
a new location to observe.
So we have to cancel it?
You're the one who chose
our site, Minazuki-san.
Yeah...
What'll this do to our grades?
I"m worried...
Anyway, we'll have to cancel the observation scheduled two days from now.
Minazuki-san?
What is it, Akimoto-san?
Are you really content to cancel the project?
If you aren't, shouldn't you rethink things a little?
Akimoto-san, I've spent...
...all last night thinking,
and canceling is for the best.
Is that what you really think?
If you don't do everything within your power,
you'll regret it later.
But...
You still have two days. I'll help out too, so...
...why not keep fighting the good fight?
Please, can you help us?
I understand. Since you're being so earnest, I'll try to put something together.
Really?
Thank you so much!
It's done!
We pulled it off!
Yeah!
You're the reason I was able to get this far.
Thank you, Komachi.
It's okay.
I'm just happy to help, Karen.
We somehow got our Social Studies project in just before the deadline...
Everybody in the class liked it.
These are the materials from back then.
So you kept them?
They're a precious memory of...
...the time when you and I met.
This time, it's my turn to help you.
Thank you, Karen.
No luck there, either.
I thought we'd fare better if we checked farther away.
Let's see, the next one is...
In the next town over...
Good afternoon!
What? The ice is gone?!
You can't exactly make
shaved ice without the ice.
Huh, really? I'd totally eat it without any ice...
Honey, youkan, and anko mixed together
would taste so good...
That... would be too sweet.
Japanese sweets topped with honey...
...yes, that would be far too sugary.
But Rin-chan, you used to say that...
...you loved eating the leftover syrup
after the ice was gone!
Well, I can't say I hate it.
Ah, I like that too! And also,
the syrup that comes with canned mandarins...
Come on, we're getting off-topic here.
Canned mandarins...
I know, if we had something sour to add...
...it wouldn't come out too sweet.
We got some summer mandarins from Grandma!
That's it!
Japanese sweets with honey, plus some fruit...!
That'd work, that'd work! That'd work for sure!
It sounds so tasty!
All right, should we go with that?
Komachi, let's make a test sample right away.
Okay!
I'll take care of the cups and straws.
Nozomi, Rin, can you re-make the signboard?
Okay!
The fliers should be here any minute. Urara, can you go distribute them?
Sure, I'll be your campaign girl!
That just leaves... the decorations.
Do we have anything?
Leave it to us-nuts!
Very well.
Now now, come one, come all!
Everyone!
Would you like to try some
sweet, delicious Komachi à la mode?
Trust us, it tastes great!
Awesome!
Okay, please don't push!
All right, line up in order.
Let's do our best.
Yeah.
Thanks for waiting, girls!
"Komachi"
Here it is.
Incredible!
It's so pretty.
Nuts, you really went all-out.
It's electrically-lit-mil.
I knew you could do it!
Yeah...
Here.
Thank you!
Let's hang this up with
some tape, Komachi-san.
Sure.
I'll go buy a roll at the convenience store!
I'm counting on you, Nozomi-san!
Sure, I won't let you down!
Oh yeah, this way's a shortcut.
Huh? There was a store over here?
I tried opening a stand at the festival...
...but I'm not selling a damn thing!
This sucks!
Something's appeared-nuts!
You came at just the right time.
If I can't sell any masks,
I can't buy anything to eat.
I'm freakin' starving here!
But if I get the Dream Collet,
I can stuff my stomach till it's full!
So, will you buy this mask,
or hand over the Dream Collet?
Pick one or the other!
None of the above!
Say what?!
Nozomi!
Nozomi-san!
You guys...!
Are you all right-coco?
Are you all right-nuts?
I'm fine!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the light of the future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
What a pain in the...
I'd better get this out,
and cause even more mayhem-
Stop it!
Don't interfere with the festival!
Shut up!
My stomach's threatening to eat itself alive.
The only thing I've eaten all day is some ice!
Some ice?
You mean you were the one
who ate our valuable ice?!
Don't get so worked up over one little block of ice.
So cruel!
We were all up really late...
...getting stuff ready for today!
And you almost ruined it for us!
Lemonade! Rouge!
Hold it!
Not so fast!
Don't mess up the festival!
Shut up!!
Mint!
What is it now?
It's just one festival,
so don't get so pissed off about it.
It may be just a small festival, but still...
Everybody worked together to put it on.
They spent their precious time on it!
This festival is really important to Komachi,
and you would dare to wreck it?!
I won't forgive you!
W-What?
The rock-crushing power of a young maiden's outpourings... take this!
Pretty Cure...
Aqua Tornado!
A-Amazing power...
Oh shi-
We'd better get back to the stand-coco.
Right!
Here you go.
Thanks for stopping by!
There's still plenty of
Komachi à la mode to go around!
There's no need to rush.
Please don't push! Stay in line!
It's a big hit.
Thanks.
You and the others really saved me today.
I just hope I've returned the favor a little.
Returned the favor?
Yes.
When I was running for Student Council President,
those few words of yours really encouraged me.
They did?
To serve others, and never
give up until the very end...
And to do everything within my power.
I still haven't forgotten about them.
I see.
Oh no! We've got an order for thirty-two!
T-Thirty-two?!
Ah, okay, right away!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
What am I gonna do for my
summer vacation free-choice report?
Nozomi-san, do you want to
come with me tomorrow?
You might get some ideas for your report.
Urara, you're my bestest friend...
I'll do anything! Performing in a concert,
being an extra in a period drama...
Um, you don't have to do any of that...
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Nozomi Becomes Manager for a Day.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?