What? You've all finished your homework?!
Of course.
E-Even the independent research?
Sure have.
Nozomi, are you all right?
Summer vacation is just about over.
And if I don't figure out what to do,
it's all over for me, too!
Umm...
Actually, I haven't finished my independent research either.
I've been too busy with work...
Really?
Why're you so happy about that?
But I've already chosen the theme,
and I'll try and throw something together at my next work site.
S-Sounds like a plan...
Lucky you; I haven't even picked a theme yet.
What'll I do...?
Well, would you like to come to work with me?
You might stumble across a good theme as we go from place to place.
Plus, there'll be good stuff to eat,
and plenty of time to relax and play around.
What?! Is it really okay for me to come with you?
Yes.
Oh yeah!
Hey, do you all want to come along, too?
I'd love to go, but I have to help out at the store.
There's a piano lesson that I have to go to.
I've got a kimono-wearing class to attend.
I see...
Milk, you wanna come?
I have to take care of Coco-sama and Nuts-sama, so I won't go-mil!
I don't want to eat tasty things or play around-mil!
Nuts, does this store observe summer vacation?
Maybe it should. A little break shouldn't hurt.
Milk, let's go with her.
Coco-sama! Nuts-sama!
All right, I'm gonna get this independent research done once and for all!
It's decided!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
So hot out here!
And it's not a dry heat, either.
Still, something's definitely not right around here.
How can he just ignore me?
What the heck is Kawarino-san thinking?
It's as if he's treating me like a bug. A lowly bug!
But then again, this is no time for idle talk.
If this goes on, my position could be jeopardized!
It's time for me to show them
what I'm made of.
And then, I'll get a promotion, and so much glory...
...that they'll never ignore me again!
They're on VACATION?!?
Nozomi Becomes Manager for a Day
Please treat me well!
I heard all about it! Good luck with your independent research.
I'd love to help out somehow, but we're gearing up for an outdoor live show.
Ah, that's right!
I'll get you a good seat, so please do come by if you get a moment.
An amazing topic might drift into your head while Urara-chan is singing.
I just know it will!
Um, yeah...
Sorry, gotta take this.
Yes, this is Washio,
Kasugano Urara's manager!
Ah, why thank you!
You've always done so much for us.
Yes, yes, we're truly in your debt!
Yes, yes, I hope we can arrange that.
Eh? About that one issue? Yes...
Washio-san sure is a busy man.
I'm going to go get changed.
Okay, have fun!
Well now...
I'd better get to work, too.
First off, picking a theme...
I don't need to play-mil.
I don't want to see the amusement park-mil!
If you wanted to have fun,
you should've just said so.
I'm not here to play-mil!
You're not fooling anyone.
That's right-coco! We're just on a walk together-coco!
A walk-nuts. I suppose that's okay-nuts.
Milk will accompany you-mil.
It's my duty as a maid-mil!
See you.
Good luck.
Okay.
Hello? Huh? The period-film village?
Yes, this afternoon, Kasugano Urara will appear in a vintage goods commercial...
You want to change the starting time?
P-Please wait a moment!
Go ahead. Yes. Okay.
I'd better tell Washio-san about this
as soon as possible.
But where'd he go?
We need to milk Kasugano Urara's charm for all it's worth!
Do you guys understand?!
You'll never succeed with that mindset. It's fundamentally flawed!
Excuse me.
Who might you be?
U-Umm, I'm Kasugano Urara's...
Ah, you're just in time! Come on in.
No, wait...
Actually, we were thinking of changing up the set list.
And as her manager, we were hoping you could pass along the message.
N-No, I'm not...
This is bad!
The band's keyboardist had to
drop out at the last minute.
We can't have a live show without
a keyboard. Do we have a backup?
I've made some calls, but nobody
could squeeze it into their schedule.
This is why I've told you to
prepare a "no band" setup!
Please calm down! If nothing can be worked out, we'll have to cancel.
This is no laughing matter!
We have to do something...
Umm...
I've got a friend who's a really
good musician. Maybe she can...?
♪...strong enough to pass through...♫
Yeah!
♪...the door of courage~♫
Yes, I'll take care of it.
♪Facing down the face in the mirror...♫
♪...on the morning of a test...♫
What do I do?
♪I totally studied, but...♫
♪...I'm still scared.♫
Can't stand it!
♪It'll be fine if I do my best...♫
Do my best...
♪My friends...♫
♪...are all here...♫
The very best!
♪...to push me along!♫
Shining bright, yes!
♪The very best! A mysterious power appears...♫
Let's go!
♪...when I set my sights high.♫
With You!
♪Walking forward under a lemon glow...♫
The very best!
♪Admiration, bursting forth...♫
♪Because everyone's with me...♫
♪...I can open up...♫
Hi!
♪...the door of courage!♫
"The Very Best! The Door of Courage"
Kasugano Urara
So...
That's why you called for me?
Sorry to bother you when you're so busy.
Karen-san, I understand this was inconvenient for you...
Don't worry about it.
I'm just glad that the concert went well.
Yes it did, thanks to you two.
So, where are we going now?
The next work site is...
Filming at the period-film village.
By the way, the starting time's been moved back an hour.
How'd you know that?
This is where you'll change into a kimono.
Rehearsal starts in half an hour.
After a break, the shooting will begin.
Isn't that right, Washio-san?
That's exactly it!
Pardon me.
Yes, this is her manager, Washio.
Ah, well now...
We've lost touch lately.
What a rough time it's been.
Um, where's her manager?
He had to...
We have a problem. The kimono
dressers are all busy elsewhere,
so that leaves Urara-san's attire in doubt.
In that case...
So, this time you've called on me?
Sorry, I know you're busy...
And now we've bothered Komachi-san, too...
No, you haven't. You're the one in trouble,
so I couldn't have left you alone.
There, all done.
Thanks so much.
We'll have to thank Madoka-san later,
since she brought Komachi here on her bike.
Yes.
It seems like she happened to be in the area...
Excuse me, is her manager around here?
The thing is, the director said he wanted to change out all the flowers on the set.
If you need flowers, then...
Oh, so I'm the last person you've called on?
Sorry, I know you were busy...
And now we've even
inconvenienced Rin-san...
What're you talking about?
I'm always willing to lend a hand.
Plus, this'll bring another
new customer into our shop.
So I have to thank you.
Now that we're all together, this feels like summer vacation's "last hurrah."
That's for sure.
Ah, I'll get it.
Oh yeah, Nozomi?
How's that independent research going?
Making progress?
Oh shoot, I forgot.
I have to pick a topic, and soon!
Say, Miss Manager?
The director wants to see you, so...
Huh? What does he want with me?
No, we were together into the morning, so I barely slept at all.
I've been running around all day...
The grind never ends.
How about a drink later on?
The schedule got pushed back,
so we're going ahead without any rehearsal.
Wait, why did we get changed?!
Because you're playing extras, duh.
Well, the director asked me if I knew of any good extras.
And... you said "yes."
Sure did!
This is my debut as an actress-mil.
We'll be starting the filming.
All right, good luck out there!
Extras, please gather over here.
Looks like...
...we'll have to do this.
Um, how should I play this role?
Just do whatever.
We'll fix things up with CG later on.
Okay...
Time to show my charm.
And... Action!
Hold it!
We won't let you...
...lay your hands on these girls!
Very well.
All right!
Noo~ Young Master!
"Young Master"?
Thou must protect us.
"Thou"? Really?
You are in the wrong.
Not quite.
You young ones seem
quite powerful, that you do.
However, quietly handing over the girl
will be in your best interest.
Y-You are-!
I am the most successful man in the Nightmare Group.
From the upper executive echelons, the great Bunbee...
...has appeared before you in the flesh!
Today's the day I'll be taking your treasure, that I will!
Look out!
Get away!
What're you doing?
Cut!
Okay!
That was OK!
Hey, I said it was okay!
Were you deluded enough as to think your escape possible?!
I admire your courage,
as well as your skills.
Has a worthy opponent at last appeared?
You puny apes!
Is that all you've got?!
Nuts-san!
Dang you guys are weak.
Coco!
Coco-sama!
I'd be done for if that weren't just a prop katana-coco...
COCO!!
Coco-sama!!
He's not dead, you know.
What're you doing?
Wait just a darned minute!
Nozomi-san!
Vile rogue, you have threatened
the peace of the 808 towns of Edo!
Your ancestors may forgive you,
but I cannot respond in kind!
I won't allow you to do anything or everything you want!
Somebody stop me!
Nozomi-san!
What're you trying to do?!
Well, this period film looked so fun...
You're too reckless!
T-The town...!
If he intends to wreck the city of Edo,
I won't stand for it!
Fellow citizens, move out!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Stand back! Stand back, I say!
I know full well who dares to stand in my presence!
Whether they fear me much, or fear me little, all will-
Hey! Don't ignore me!
I just came up with that intro!
Don't the unspoken rules say to let everyone finish their speeches?!
Your companions have already been defeated.
And you would stand up alone against the great Bunbee?
Karen-san helped me with my concert.
Komachi-san helped with the fitting.
Rin-san brought the flowers.
And Nozomi-san's stayed with me all day.
They all did their best for my sake.
They're all precious to me, and if you hurt them...
I'll never...
...I'll never forgive you!
The effervescent power of a shining maiden... take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
Curses! I was hoping to charm my way into a promotion!
I'll let you off the hook for today!
I pity the fool!
Thanks a lot, everybody.
Aw, don't mention it.
I'm just glad the filming went okay.
Not only was it fun,
it was a good experience for us.
Thank you so much!
You really saved me today!
You'll make a great manager!
I will?
Washio-san, please don't cause any more trouble for Nozomi-san.
She's been through enough.
My deepest apologies.
But I still couldn't find an
independent research topic.
That's a shame. You were actually working for once, not just playing around.
Can I have a look at this?
Sure.
Is that your schedule, Urara?
Yes. And it's got all the work site details and schedule changes.
Impressions from the concert, too.
Every little thing's written down-nuts.
I never thought Nozomi'd write so much-mil.
Well, it's all important to Urara, so...
Couldn't you use this notebook as your project?
She's right! Managing a celebrity
for a day is quite the experience.
I'm sure it'd make for a great research project.
It's not half-bad-coco!
It's just the thing!
It is?
Yeah, it is!
Aren't you glad, Nozomi-san?
Yep! Thanks, everyone!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Karen-san, listen to me! Milk is such a meanie!!
You're fighting again?
She started it! She said I wasn't cut out to be Pretty Cure!
Milk's just a maid. What does she  know?
Nozomi, you know she doesn't really believe that, right?
Just be honest with her, okay?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Milk's Resolve and Everyone's Power!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?