HEY!!
Give it back!
I won't-mil!
You'd better give it back, or else!
They're at it again.
They never quit.
Grudges over food sure are scary.
Especially between those two.
Hold it right there!
Um, Nozomi-san, Milk-san?
Give me back my chocolate!
I can't return something I've eaten-mil.
Be quiet!
Don't act up in the store.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry-mil.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Hey, Coco, don't you think it's mean to eat something that somebody else bought?
I suppose so.
Nozomi's at fault for not eating it fast enough-mil.
You snooze, you lose-mil!
Hey now, is that something
an apprentice caregiver should be doing?
We apprentice caregivers need require strength and wisdom-mil.
Unlike Nozomi, we can't afford to be slacking on the job.
What was that?!
Now now, calm down, calm down.
Look, there's still more chocolates around.
Let's stop this, you two.
I know! I want to hear about the apprentice caregiver business from Milk.
You want to hear-mil?
Yeah, yeah!
Sure, why not?
I'd really like to know!
Ahem-mil.
Apprentice caregivers in the Palmier Kingdom must learn about its politics,
economics, culture, history,
and everything else about the kingdom.
Reconciling the wills of the kingdom
and the citizens is a highly important job-mil!
That's why apprentice caregivers must learn many things each day,
in order to master this difficult curriculum.
Huh?
Wow, if people who steal chocolates from others got to be caregivers,
the Palmier Kingdom must've been
pretty short-handed.
How dare you say that-mil?!
I won't allow you to insult the kingdom-mil!
I'm not insulting the Palmier Kingdom.
I'm insulting your abilities as an apprentice maid!
Nozomi, cut it out.
Milk has dreamed of being a maid from a very young age-mil!
So I won't stand to be criticized by you, Nozomi-mil!
You have no dreams for the future-mil!
I do too have dreams!
Like reviving Coco's and your kingdom-
Everyone in the kingdom has that dream-mil!
It's not your your own dream-mil!
I don't want to entrust the kingdom's future to someone with no dreams-mil!
Which means that you aren't cut out to be a Pretty Cure-mil.
Hey, Milk, that's-
Nozomi, you fail as a Pretty Cure-mil!
I fail as... a Pretty Cure?
Milk's Resolve and Everyone's Power!
Kawarino-san.
Kawarino-san!
My, you're noisy.
I'm right here; you don't have to yell so loudly.
Did you need me for something?
This time, I will defeat Pretty Cure.
Therefore, I'd like "the item."
"The item"?
Don't act like you don't know!
The thing Girinma used when he almost took down Pretty Cure!
Oh, you mean that?
But I'm not sure if you should be using "that."
Have you consulted with your direct superior?
I'm standing here asking you,
Kawarino-san.
If you insist that much, then...
But, you might not make much progress.
If you use this, you'll receive phenomenal powers...
...at the expense of your own free will.
Are you saying you accept this?
For the sake of Nightmare...
And also, for the sake of my pride...
This is... my last resort.
Oh, my! You needed it that much?
You've shown impressive resolve.
I can't wait to see the results.
I hope to meet your expectations.
A-Arachnea-kun...
Where's Nozomi?
She went home before we could stop her.
It must've been pretty shocking.
She got called a failure as a Pretty Cure.
So, is Milk-san still...
Yes. She's shut herself away in her room,
and won't come out.
Those two just don't mix.
Rin-san, they remind me of you and...
...Karen-san.
Ehh?!
That's completely...
...wrong!
If only those two could be honest.
That'd be nice. Huh?
I... said some awful things to Milk.
Maybe I really do fail as a Pretty Cure.
Can I come in?
We had some chocolate left over, so I brought you some.
I don't want it-mil!
Huh? Why not? Don't you like chocolate?
I love it, but I don't want it-mil!
Sometimes you have fights
with the people you're close to.
Will your beloved chocolate
not taste as good without Nozomi around?
Am I right?
Mil! That's not true-mil!
I feel a lot better without Nozomi around-mil!
Well, I  wish she were here.
Ever since I was young,
I've lived apart from my parents.
So I never told them I was lonely,
so that I wouldn't worry them.
But in truth, I was extremely lonely.
But ever since I met Nozomi,
I've been able to admit I was lonely.
That girl has the power to make people become honest with themselves.
The power to make people
honest with themselves-mil?
That's right. Why don't you try telling Nozomi everything that's on your mind?
I'm sure you'll come to an understanding.
But Nozomi doesn't have any dreams-mil.
She doesn't understand my feelings as a caregiver-mil.
I still haven't decided what I
want to be in the future, either.
You haven't-mil?
That's why I'm striving towards my own dreams.
I think you, Komachi,
and Urara are all incredible.
But...
But I think people who focus on the task at hand while searching for their dreams,
like Nozomi and Rin, are also incredible.
Actually, I find myself wishing I could
find my dream by doing what they're doing.
Karen...
You're both very earnest people.
I'm sure you can find some common ground.
Pretty Cure... this day will be your last.
Arachnea-kun!
I must ask you not to use that.
Oh, this is rich. Didn't you give one of these
to Girinma, Bunbee-san?
It's too dangerous.
Kawarino-san is just trying to use you.
Hah. You're only trying to stop me because your position is in danger.
Okay, you got me there...
But that doesn't matter anymore!
I'm worried about YOU!
I will complete this job successfully, with my own powers!
A-Arachnea-kun!
Wait!
Pretty Cure!!
Has something appeared?
This is...
Nightmare!
Pretty Cure...
Pretty Cure, I'm going to send you to the deepest depths of despair!
She seems...
...different from usual.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Everyone, be careful!
Yes!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
Take this, Pretty Cure!
Aqua!
Rouge!
Girls!
Hand over the Dream Collet.
What? What is  this?
With this, my work record will be perfect!
Give it back-coco!
Give it back-nuts!
I've got no use for you anymo-
Your actions are futile. Let go of the Collet.
I love it-mil.
Huh?
Milk loves the Palmier Kingdom-mil!
Milk!
So I'll never let you have the Dream Collet-mil!
Your country is gone, never to return.
I will  bring it back!
What can you do in your condition?
We can do anything.
If we...
...work together...
...there's nothing we can't do!
"Together," you say?
I see. I'd been thinking that
something was missing.
Where's the fifth one?
At any rate, it's time for you all to meet your doom!
Farewell, Pretty Cure!
Such stubbornness.
But it'll all be over after the next attack.
It won't matter if there are four or five of you;
you'll have no chance to stop me.
That's what you think!
There's nothing we can't do if we're all together!
Nozomi-san!
Nozomi!
Milk, I'm sorry about those
awful things I said back there.
I might be a failure as a Pretty Cure.
Nozomi, Milk is...
But, I want to work with all of you to restore the Palmier Kingdom!
So I want to keep being Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
Dream!
Sorry I'm late, you guys.
Even if there's five of you, it doesn't matter!
You won't be able to lay a hand on the new me regardless!
"I can't do anything."
Huh?!
I'm clumsy, my grades suck, and I'm bad at sports.
I haven't found my dream for the future yet.
But there's one thing I've made up my mind on:
I will make Coco's, Nuts',
and Milk's dreams come true.
No price is too great for the cause of reviving the Palmier Kingdom!
Dream...
Without fail...
...by our hands...
...the Palmier Kingdom...
...will definitely...
...be restored!
As long as I possess the Collet,
the kingdom will see no resurrection!
Give up already!!
We won't give up!
Dream's return made them all shine again-coco!
Dream has the power to do that-nuts!
The power to make everyone shine...
Curse you all...
I already made up my mind to take this path.
No matter what else may happen,
I'll defeat you!
That's the-!
This is goodbye, Pretty Cure...
You three...
No, you can't! Hurry up and escape!
Milk was...
Milk was always lonely-mil.
After I escaped from the Palmier Kingdom by myself, I was scared and alone.
I didn't know what I could believe in-mil.
Nozomi, I trusted you and the others from the bottom of my heart-mil.
But I didn't know how I should express those feelings-mil!
Milk...
Karen-san taught me-mil...
...that it's okay to be honest-mil.
And to act the way I think I should act-mil!
Th-That's the spirit...
Milk does...
Dream... Nozomi...
I love you-mil!!
Dream, you're a precious Pretty Cure to me-mil!
You mustn't quit-mil!
I want you to restore the Palmier Kingdom-mil!
Milk...
Milk wants to join you, Dream...
...along with the rest of Pretty Cure...
...and shine together-mil!!
Milk? Wha?
Together with the powers of Dreams and Hope...
O Five Lights...
...right here and now:
Pretty Cure Five Explosion!!
Amazing power-nuts!
This is Pretty Cure's true strength-coco!
Thank you, Milk.
Milk went overboard too-mil.
I'm sorry-mil.
I'm so glad they've made up.
Shall we have some tea to celebrate that?
Sounds good.
I'll heat the water.
Ah, Milk will help too-mil!
This is...
Give it back-mil! That's mine-mil!
Huh? Didn't somebody say that  "you snooze, you lose?"
Just kidding.
Let's split it. You know,
to make up for what you ate yesterday.
Very well-mil.
On second thought, it's all mine-mil.
Hey! No fair!
Get back here, Milk!
Hold it right there!
No way-mil!
Oh, brother-coco.
Why am I not surprised?
No running in the store-nuts!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
I didn't know Coco got a love letter.
It's not like he hid it from you.
He did too hide it!
I don't know what Coco's thinking anymore.
Nozomi, you need to talk things out with him.
Yeah. Huh, Coco?
Coco!
What's with him? I've never seen Coco like that!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Nozomi, Coco,
and the Love Letter Incident!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?