I just found a store that sells really good chocolates.
I might buy some for Milk.
Wow, you've gotten pretty friendly with her.
And I just might pick up
some choux cremes for Coco, too.
Look, it's the man himself.
Huh?
Isn't that girl holding a love letter?
Cocoda-sensei's pretty popular...
with girls who don't know his true form.
Nozomi? You listening?
Uh... yeah.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
QC: Force_Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Translation, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
This makes 28 Pinkies you've collected.
You just need 27 more to have all 55 assembled.
I'm sure we'll get it done.
We've already made a lot of progress.
Nozomi-san?
Nozomi?
Eh? What is it?
It's like your mind's somewhere else.
No, it's right here.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Welcome home-mil!
Coco-sama, did you get
another letter today-mil?
Um... Well, yes.
What kind of letter?
One like this-mil!
More love letters,
like the one you got this morning?
Nozomi and I saw it.
Are ALL of these love letters?
There's so many.
That's the prince of the
Palmier Kingdom for you-mil!
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama were loved by all-mil.
You get them too, Nuts-san?
I reject them on the spot.
You kept... all the letters?
Y-Yeah, I did.
Have you answered them?
Only in writing.
Wouldn't it be tough to answer this many?
Coco-sama is so kind-mil.
It's good etiquette to reply to letters you receive.
A man of manners.
I didn't know.
I never knew you received
and answered so many letters.
Not at all.
B-But, I didn't mean to hide it from you...
Though it's not my place to say that.
I'm... going home.
Nozomi-san!
Wait, Nozomi!
Nozomi!
Nozomi, Coco, and the Love Letter Incident!
Nozomi, I said stop!
What's wrong?
Coco hid them from me.
Hid what? The love letters?
I didn't know about them either.
C'mon, Coco's a teacher.
It must be hard to reject letters from students, so it's not as if he was hidi-
He was hiding them!
She must've been shocked that Coco would hide things from her.
Isn't it exaggerating to say he was hiding things?
But doesn't this seem like
a very important thing to Nozomi-san?
Nozomi-san didn't seem like her usual self today.
Don't worry about it.
Nozomi should understand things if I explain them to her.
What should I do?
I'm losing personnel here.
First Girinma-kun, and now Arachnea-kun?
And it's all Kawarino-san's fault, too.
Yet, as their supervisor,
the blame falls on me.
I can't take this anymore. Can't Kawarino-san get transferred or something? {
Nobody's here!
W-W-Where'd everybody go?! Hey!!
They've all been transferred.
K-Kawarino-san!?
They announced a re-organization, Bunbee-san.
As of today, this department is disbanded.
Dis-Disbanded?!
H-Hang on! What happened to Arachnea-kun was your fault, not mine!
H-Hey!
Let's head over to the new section.
New section?
Bunbee-san, you'll be working under-
I know that already!
Bloody-san, your reputation precedes you.
It's an honor just to work in the same office.
I'm looking forward to-
You're in the way!
This is my seat!
Ha-Hadenya-san!
Are we in the same section now??
The pleasure's all mine, Bunbee-chan.
Your seat is over there.
No... any seat but that one. My seat is...
You seem awfully surprised.
Did you really think you could sit
next to me, after so many failures?
Despariah-sama.
Pretty Cure's resistance has claimed another victim.
We cannot allow them to go unpunished.
I may...
...even have to send Bloody and Hadenya into the fray.
Please entrust this to me, Despariah-sama!
Hadenya, I will leave everything
concerning the Dream Collet in your hands.
Yes ma'am!
You had best be on your guard, Hadenya-san.
Pretty Cure have proven to be
formidable opponents.
Aww, are you worried about me?
You're such a nice guy, Kawarino-chan!
See you!
Nozomi...
Shouldn't you answer it?
N-Nuts! Why're you here?
If the students find you...
Have you spoken with Nozomi?
You were worried enough to
come all the way here and ask me that?
You know I hate lies more than anything else.
Huh? Ah, yes.
Then don't you laugh that forced laugh at me!
Back in Palmier,
it was all about the citizens.
And now, it's all about the students.
When will you ever put yourself first?
A Prince is one who works
for his people.
And a teacher is one who works
for his students.
And that makes you happy?!
Seeing everyone's smiles makes me happy.
You're always like that!
Why can't you take better care of yourself?!
Thank you, Nuts.
But...
I don't really know what I want to do.
I envy your blunt honesty.
Keeping your worries to yourself
has always been one of your flaws.
You need to talk things out with others.
Nuts...
"I just wonder what Coco's up to."
Eh?!
Isn't that what you're thinking?
I-I am not!
Nozomi, I understand your thought processes.
I'm not your childhood friend for nothing, you know.
Coco's nice to everybody, and always smiling.
But I have no idea what's really on his mind!
What do you  want to do, Nozomi?
Huh?
The important thing is your feelings, right?
Can you leave things with Coco like this?
I want to fix things.
Well, you won't fix things by sulking all the time.
You have to talk to him face-to-face.
I want to do that.
And with a smile, too.
I don't know what to say to Nozomi-coco.
You have to tell her your true feelings-nuts.
My feelings-coco?
What do you think about Nozomi-nuts?
What do I think about Nozomi?
So there you are.
Long time no see,
little boys from the Palmier Kingdom.
Do you think those two have talked things over?
I don't believe so, at least not yet.
There wouldn't be time during school hours.
Do you think we should check on them?
Karen! Emergency-mil!
Milk?
What is it?
Something's appeared-mil!
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama are in danger-mil!
Coco is?
Coco-sama! Nuts-sama!
What do you girls want?
So cruel.
I wonder why my co-workers have been unable to accomplish such a simple task.
She's got the Dream Collet!
It was all too easy.
So you were the one who did this
to Coco and Nuts?
So what if I was?
You'll pay!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
The Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
So, you girls are Pretty Cure?
Dream!
Kids these days are so impatient.
You've got to work on
your listening skills!
I don't wanna listen to you!
You've got a rude mouth on you.
You know, I find your sort utterly repugnant!
Dream!
It's fast!
And so powerful!
It isn't like the others!
What's wrong, little girls?
You'd better hustle, or you'll get dirty!
Aww, you're not so tough at all.
What's with that look in your eyes? Are you mad?
You... hurt Coco!
Coco? Ah, you mean that boy.
I'll let you in on a secret.
I've attempted to catch these two before.
And I gave them plenty of pain that time, too.
Dream, that's reckless!
W-We've gotta do something.
Yes!
Nuts, are you okay-coco?
I'm fine-nuts.
We've seen that one before-nuts!
Nuts! Hang on-coco!
Nuts!
NUTS!!!!
After I got injured,
you were left by yourself-nuts.
After escaping from Nightmare into the Human World,
you were alone, searching for the Collet
with no idea where to look.
Things looked hopeless-nuts.
I'm thankful to the person
who saved you from that-nuts.
And who was the one who saved you-nuts?
Dream was...
Dream...
Dream!!
Quiet, you!
Look out!
I won't let you harm Coco any more!
Dream...
Ha! I'll harm him as many times as I want to!
I just can't stand you!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Well, what have we here?
Hmm, you're more cunning than I thought.
Until next time!
Are you okay?
Yes-nuts. You saved us-nuts!
Hey, you can't ignore
that look on Nozomi's face-nuts.
I'm heading out!
Huh?
Nozomi.
Good morning.
Uh, it's not what you think! I didn't receive this.
I wrote it... to you.
Eh? To me?
B-But, it's really sloppy,
so I planned to rewrite it.
I want that one.
So, I thought I'd write what I was thinking...
But the words got in the way.
You answer all the girls who write to you, right?
The replies to my students are all roughly the same.
"I can't answer your feelings."
Sorry. Can't really call that a letter, can you?
But there were things I just had to tell you-
N-Nozomi...
Your feelings... got through.
Thank you.
Let's go!
Teachers shouldn't be tardy, you know!
Y-Yeah!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
What should I do?
I'm totally stumped on this tiara design.
The tiara for that wedding ceremony?
Right. And I'm all out of time.
Got any good ideas?
Oh, I know! Wedding cake!
Um, I'm not doing a cake.
With tons of cream.
Can we move away from the cake thing?
I want to eat it all up!
Yeah, I thought so.
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Rin-chan's Happy Wedding.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?