Gorgeous...
Ah, Madoka-san.
And you were...
...that's right, one of Komachi's friends...
...Rin-chan!
Yes!
Madoka-san, are you getting married or something?
Huh? Ah, no, no.
There's a planning meeting for my friend's wedding today.
Your friend?
Hi there.
Good afternoon.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
A wedding?!
Yes. It won't be long before Miku becomes a happy bride. Right?
Yes.
Wow, that's so cool!
This bracelet is so cute.
It sure is. Is it an original product from this store?
Yes, it's one of our hottest sellers.
Isn't it a lovely design?
The designer of that bracelet... is standing right behind you.
It's Rin-chan!
It was you?
Yes.
Whoa.
Hey, Madoka, aren't we still missing one thing for the ceremony?
Oh, you mean that?
I think I'd like to ask her.
Brilliant idea.
Ask her what?
I'd like you to design something for me.
W-What would that be?
It'd be something that Miku
will wear during her wedding.
Could I have you make my tiara?
Can I ask this favor?
M-Me?!
Rin-chan's Happy Wedding!
This is awesome, Rin-chan!
You got a major commission.
Yeah...
I'm glad I met you, Rin-chan.
Is this destiny?
Umm... I'm not sure if someone like me can make that.
You'll do fine!
Miku's the bride, and you've got her
praising your design sense.
Be a little more confident.
"Design sense"...
That's right, Rin-san!
It's a big responsibility,
but I think it's worth taking on.
I'm looking forward to seeing what you'll make.
Huh? But...
It's all good, it's all good!
You'll be able to throw
something together, Rin-chan.
Hey, Nozomi! Weddings are
serious business, you know.
Listen up. A wedding is an extremely important day for any young woman.
It's the biggest event in her life. She has to look her best!
Ahem.
Tucked away somewhere
deep in the forest lies a lovely chapel.
Clothed in a pure white dress,
she softly declares her eternal love.
Ah, what a fabulous moment!
It's any maiden's finest hour!
Um, Rin-chan?
"No, Darling, you mustn't!"
She's become completely absorbed in fantasy.
However, in the heart of the bride,
there dwells another unerasable existence!
Hold it right there!
Let's go, Komachi. Come with me!
Yes!
It's so very dramatic!
Uh, no. I beg to differ.
But this scenario makes the story more exciting!
I'd rather have a wedding
so flashy that it's explosive!
My wedding ceremony will be entertainment for everyone.
Everybody, welcome to Kasugano Urara's
wedding ceremony!
Enjoy yourselves until the end of the day, okay?
Urara-chaaan~!
I'd have the entire arena filled with
foam bubbles while I'm changing outfits.
It'll be beautiful, the stuff legends are made of.
And of course, I'd execute perfectly all through the end of the encore.
That sounds pretty flashy.
And fun, too.
Hey, what about you, Karen-san?
Eh? Me?
Yeah, yeah. What kind of
wedding ceremony do you want?
Come to think of it, I've never heard Karen talk about this, either.
For me...
I'd be completely robed in a pure white dress.
Preferably a dignified white kimono that epitomizes Japanese beauty.
I can feel my heart tightening at the thought.
So, you want to go Japanese-style, Karen-san?
Didn't see that coming.
So, so, what about your husband?
What'll he be like?
H-Husband? Oh no, I haven't really given a thought to that matter...
Here, here! I would like...
...to wear a bunch of dresses!
And then, I'd eat a huge cake, all by myself!
Weddings are so great! They're
the perfect excuse to totally pig out!
That cake is a fake, you know.
What?!
Yeah, it's papier-mache.
Only the part you cut with a knife is real;
the rest is all fake.
What? I can't eat it?
Behold the tremendous powers of maidens' imaginations.
Yeah. I can't keep up.
I'm so happy-mil.
No-mil. It's so embarrassing-mil!
M-Milk?
That one's a maiden, too.
I'm starving.
I've been looking everywhere for you,
Gamao-kun.
Now now, don't mind me.
W-What do you want?!
Let's see...
I'd like you to resume working for Nightmare,
if you are so inclined.
W-What're you saying?
I've taken an interest in you from the very beginning.
If you can successfully use this to
take the Dream Collet from Pretty Cure,
then becoming an executive
wouldn't be unthinkable. Not for you.
E-Executive? Me?
It's just that your superiors
haven't nurtured you up till now.
Don't you think I can understand you
far better than they can?
Me, become an executive?
Rin-san's not here today?
No, Rin-chan's gone into seclusion in the classroom.
She's been staring at her notebooks this whole time.
No good.
She didn't want any lunch.
Eh?!?
If Rin's skipping lunch...
...it's a major crisis!
Perhaps she hasn't had any ideas?
I see.
It seems like Rin-san's really worried.
Do you think she'll finish in time for the ceremony?
No good.
Huh?
That's right, I could use that for the crown...
Umm...
Would this look cuter over here?
Pardon me!
Ehh... Uh, yes?
Hello there.
Ah, Miku-san.
Good afternoon.
I had fun the other day.
Huh?
Hearing you all talk about ideal weddings.
Everyone had their own images, didn't they?
Yeah, they did.
So, you're worrying about the tiara design?
Huh?
I heard about it from Madoka.
Yeah, since you'll be wearing it at your important wedding ceremony,
I figured I had to make it as good as possible.
And then I felt pressured,
and didn't know how to proceed.
I'm sorry for placing this burden on you, Rin-chan.
But I'm glad.
Huh?
You see, my wedding ceremony...
...won't be anything like anybody else's.
I'm getting some close friends together,
and we're doing a "hand-crafted" ceremony.
"Hand-crafted"?
We all collaborate and help with the preparations.
Wow, that sounds wonderful.
It's a lot of work,
but everybody's keeping my best interests in mind in everything they're doing.
I feel blessed to have friends like that.
That's why I was glad to hear that you were worried, too.
Those feelings of yours
make me happier than anything.
Thank you.
Miku-san...
Whatever you make, I'm sure it'll be
the finest tiara in my eyes.
I...
I'll try to make a tiara that will make you happy, Miku-san.
No, I will  make it, no question.
All right, I've got the design, so time to get cracking!
It's finished!
Congratulations, Miku!
Miku, it's time to change your outfit.
Okay.
Miku-san should be back any minute.
Yeah.
She's wearing your tiara with the next dress, right?
What kind of tiara is it?
Yeah-coco!
We haven't seen the finished version-nuts.
Stop being bashful and show us-mil.
Okay.
Rin-san?
Huh? Sorry, what was that?
Aw, Rin-chan, you're way too nervous.
Well of course I am! You see, Nozomi,
the thing about weddings is...
Ah, it's Miku-san!
The wedding cake?
What's the cake doing here?
What's it matter?
Huh?!
It's a bit of a pain, but a mission's a mission.
Nightmare!
This is for the sake of getting stable employment.
Here goes!
Rin!
We'll take care of the tiara-mil!
Keep it safe.
Leave it to us-coco!
How could you do this to
Miku-san's precious wedding cake?!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
The Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Man, these are some awesome power-ups!
This just has to work!
Give that back!
The tiara's safe!
Thank goodness!
Hurry up and hide somewhere safe.
Heh, that junk doesn't matter at all!
There's no way it...
...doesn't matter!
W-What?!
You wouldn't understand, but...
...all the objects in this room, and the
wedding ceremony that's going on outside...
...are packed full with everyone's precious feelings!
Huh? Enough with the worthless babble!
It's NOT worthless!
Today is the biggest day in a young girl's life!
We won't let you ruin it!
That's all irrelevant.
I don't care anymore, so why don't you just hand over the Dream Collet?
We DO care!
We can't let you wreck Miku-san's precious wedding ceremony!
I won't forgive you!
The powerful flame of
a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
Waah?!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Oooohhh noooooo~...!
Great job-coco!
Thanks for waiting, everybody!
And now, the debut of the bride in her new outfit!
A clover that summons good luck.
A crown of flowers made with white Dutch clovers...
You can really tell it's Rin-chan's design.
Way to go, Rin-chan!
Aw, it's not that great.
Let's get some flower motifs and accessories added to the store-nuts!
I'm sure they'll be a big hit-coco!
Miku-san, congratulations.
And now, the much-anticipated bouquet toss!
Whoever catches this lucky bouquet will be the next bride!
Miku, if you would.
Now, who will get the lucky bouquet?
This means my turn is next, along with Coco-sama...!
A-As a maiden, once I've had a taste of happiness, I can't let it go-mil!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
Yeah~!
Like a coconut
kokonattsu mitai na
A sweet fluffy kiss
funwari amai kisu
If I do it without thinking
uttori shiteitara
My alarm clock went off
mezamashi ga natta
I open the curtain
kaaten wo hiraite
I've got to find the continuation of my dream
yume no tsuzuki sagasanakucha
The rays of the sun on my chest are too bright
mabushisugiru mune no hizashi ni
I'm enchanted by them, they won't disappear
torokete kienai you ni
Oh~!
The happy, carefree face of the sun
nonki de omedetai kaoshiteru taiyou
How can you just laugh like that!?
nande sonna ni waratte irareru no!?
You're really just that same cautious color
hontou wa onajikurai yabai color
Sparkle, My True Love!
kirakirashichatte My True Love!
I wanna dream, I wanna love!
yume mitai koi shitai
With all my heart!
chou meippai
With a smile and a good luck charm
hohoende omajinai
Ain't I cute?
kawaiijan!
Ain't I the best?
saikou jan!
Pretty-pretty-pretty Cure Five!
puripuripurikyua faivu
What'll we do?! Masuko-san said she's shutting Cinq Lumieres News down!
This is bad. I need her to write
more and more articles about me!
Let's do something about it, Nozomi-san!
I know! I bet Masuko-san'll feel motivated if she gets
an exclusive interview with Pretty Cure!
That's the ticket! Let's go with that!
Yeah!
You... think it's okay?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Big Scoop! Exclusive Interview with Pretty Cure 5!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?!