Good morning, everybody!
Wow, it's the new issue of the Cinq Lumieres News!
Futsal Team Suffers Crushing Defeat!!
Autumn Season
News Roundup!
The Futsal team's match?
"Captain Konno's Critical Mistake. Failure to Adjust!?
Captain Konno Getting the Ball Stolen from Her
"Insufficient Practice!?
The Captain will Resign?"
Ah...
C-Captain!
'Morning.
What the people want to know,
I want to know!
The chief editor of the Cinq Lumieres News,
Masuko Mika!
Also known as...
Masuko-san!
Huh?
What's with this article?
There's no way Konno-san would quit being captain!
That's why I added the question mark.
I'll have you know, the captain hurt her leg
on the day before the match!
Since she didn't have reserves, she was forced to play hurt.
I didn't know... she was injured.
You didn't know? Why didn't you do
the research before writing that article?!
It's okay.
She was right about the failure to adjust and the insufficient practice.
And maybe that's why I got hurt.
We'll do better next time.
C-Captain...
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
QC: Force_Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Translation, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
They certainly have provided some entertainment.
Didn't I warn you that they would be
formidable opponents?
That means it's finally my turn, isn't it?
Just watch and see.
I'll recover the Dream Collet without fail.
Kawarino-chan, those little girls
can't hope to compete against me.
Please take care of it.
Despariah-sama places more trust in this department than any other.
That's exactly why I should-
Hadenya-san, please do not disappoint Despariah-sama.
You don't even have to tell me.
Is anybody listening to me?!
This doesn't hurt at all! No pain!
Nobody in Nightmare knows
Pretty Cure better than I do.
Don't you think I should handle this?
I don't understand why they're ignoring me.
I'll do it all alone! You'll see!
Big Scoop! Exclusive Interview with Pretty Cure 5!
Huh? Is Masuko-san skipping lunch?
Looks like this morning's events are still weighing heavily on her.
Like how she hurt Captain Konno.
Still, I kinda feel sorry for her.
Yeah.
This isn't good.
Huh?
You have to eat your lunch.
Transmitting what you've seen and heard to others is a very important task.
But with that great task
comes great responsibility.
When the burden's too great to bear alone, you have to rely on your friends.
Isn't that option worth exploring?
I'm always here to support you.
Masuko-san!
Here, you forgot this.
If you don't eat, you'll never
last through the afternoon.
Don't you have more interviews?
But it's amazing that you can take pictures,
write articles, and put out
a newspaper all by yourself.
I only wound up... by myself.
There used to be other
club members, besides me.
I got so obsessed that I
lost sight of my surroundings.
They all said they couldn't work with me anymore.
At some point, I looked around and realized I was all alone.
I buckled down and forged ahead by myself.
But I wound up doing less and less research,
"Cute Guys at the School Festival"
and writing more and more articles full of rumors and wild exaggerations.
"The School Trip is Canceled!?"
Including the most recent incident.
I couldn't check into things thoroughly enough,
and wound up hurting Konno-san.
Maybe I just can't go it alone.
I'm thinking I should quit.
"What the people want to know,
I want to know!"
Huh?
Isn't that what you always say, Masuko-san?
I'm on the same page.
Congrats on Getting In
Welcome to Cinq Lumieres Academy
There's always tons of entertaining and informative articles!
Otaka-san's                           New Menu
I like the Cinq Lumieres News.
So do I!
Please give me more coverage!
I always look forward to reading your hard-hitting interviews.
A newspaper dealing with issues relevant to the students' interests is necessary.
Yeah, I wouldn't want it to go away, either.
You all...?
Natsuki-san...
After all, the Futsal team
makes the front page if it wins.
Come on, let's keep
the Newspaper club going!
I'm happy you all feel that way.
But...
Masuko-san!
I'll show you the "power of one."
I have to decline.
Can't you do something?
I think Masuko-san would be motivated to keep the newspaper going
if she could do an
exclusive interview with you.
If she really wants to quit,
you shouldn't force her to keep going.
That's right-mil. You can't come running to Nuts-sama for every little thing-mil.
Even if she were to interview me and continue the newspaper,
it wouldn't solve anything.
I suppose it wouldn't.
Nuts might be right on this one.
I'm gonna talk to her one more time!
N-Nozomi!
"Cinq Lumieres News Back Issues"
(First Issue)
"Dog Returned to Owner"
In-Depth Coverage of
the Legendary Newspaper Delivery Dog
Are you an acquaintance of Pretty Cure?
W-Who ARE you?!
You can't possibly not know them.
Can't you help me out a bit here?
Nozomi!
Something's appeared-coco!
Hurry-nuts!
Okay!
What have we here?
And over here...
Where could she have gone?
Maybe over here?
Hold it!
Rats.
So you've appeared, Pretty Cure!
"Pretty Cure"?
Wait a sec, aren't these Masuko-san's?
What have you done with Masuko-san?
Hmm, good question.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
The Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cure 5?
Time to test out my new powers!
No! Not my newspaper!
Masuko-san!
You okay?
Y-Yes.
This is what you get for relying on friends.
Incompetent people are incompetent,
no matter how many of them gather together!
What... what's so wrong with
not being able to do it all yourself?
Alone, we think, worry, and strive our hardest.
Even if things don't work out,
those feelings will
definitely reach out to others.
And when those feelings reach you,
they make you think,
"I want to help that person."
Even if they're powerless.
If we all stand united,
we might be able to do it.
That's what friends are all about!
You're just licking each other's wounds and leaving yourselves defenseless!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
It's been awhile since I've had opponents this formidable.
Retreat!
Why am I taking pictures when I've already quit the newspaper?
Here. This file's important to you, right?
Thank you very much. Excuse me.
Masuko-san!
Don't you want to interview us?
Huh?
Hey-
But, I've already...
You've been taking our pictures, haven't you?
Don't you want to continue the Newspaper Club?
Masuko-san?
Can I really...
...interview you?
You sure can!
Are you sure about this?
Masuko-san's finally gotten motivated,
so it's all good.
I suppose, but there's a lot we shouldn't talk about.
I can handle that kind of interview.
Should they really be interviewed-mil?
They all decided to do it, so I trust them-coco.
Is this what you're going for?
How's the camera angle?
Can you be a bit more natural?
And what's with those poses?
Should they really be interviewed-mil?
They all... decided to do it,
so I... trust them-coco.
What do you normally do?
Let's see, we come to this school, and-
That type of question is no good.
Then, what were those monsters?
Ah, they were from Nightma-
Um, we don't know, either.
You can tell she's a veteran interviewee.
Yes.
So why were you all
fighting against those monsters?
To fulfill a certain dream.
Dream?
What dream could be worth
going through such dangers?
It's the dream of someone precious to us.
Aren't you scared to
take on those monsters?
We'll be just fine, as long as
we combine all our powers.
Combine all... your powers?
Perhaps this is a good stopping point?
What?! Already!?
Come on, don't get carried away.
You can interview us any time.
I hope you can get
a good article out of this.
I will!
Okay, then!
Umm, can I ask one last thing?
Huh?
Do you think I can find...
...friends like you girls?
YES!
'Morning, everybody!
Ah, it's the Cinq Lumieres News'
latest issue!
An exclusive interview with
the Futsal Team's Captain Konno!
Speaking about her aspirations for the next match.
What the people want to know,
I want to know!
Cinq Lumieres News' Chief Editor,
Masuko Mika!
Also known as... Masukomi-ka!
Masuko-san!
Yumehara-san, I'm sorry I made you worry.
I decided to keep the Newspaper Club running.
Nozomi-san!
The Mysterious Ladies...
Exclusive Interview with Pretty Cure 5!
Wow, she got some great shots!
That's our captain!
You really have a way with words.
Let's keep working together in the future.
Yes, the Captain's awesome,
but did you see the article below it?
Let's do our best at the next match.
Yes, do your best in the next match!
But hey, what about Pretty Cure 5?!
Quit making a fuss about Pretty Cure!
Aw, come on...
Isn't it for the best that it
didn't become a hot topic?
And after all I went through
to set up the shot...
I think the article's very well-written.
Looks like we didn't have to keep an eye on things-nuts.
But you're really here out of concern for Masuko-san,
not the article on Pretty Cure, right?
Nuts-sama may say some harsh things, but he's really a softie-mil.
Hey, does Pretty Cure resemble anyone you know?
H-Hey! Darn it, Nozomi...
I don't know about any resemblance...
...but I think they're incredible people.
I'd like to introduce you all
to them sometime.
Y-Yeah, sure...
I'd really like to meet them!
But it'd be pretty strange to meet them, since we-
Stop! That's about enough out of you.
But she finally wrote an article about Pretty Cu-
Stop talking about Pretty Cure!
♪ Pu-ri-ti-de, Cu-Cu-Cu-Cure... ♪
And don't sing about them, either.
Cinq Lumieres News Seeking Fantastic Fellow Writers!!
All Applicants, see Chief Editor Masuko Mika!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun (Go! Go!)
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Nozomi, we have a situation with Milk!
This "situation" had better not involve her eating all my chocolate again!
No, it doesn't!
Wait, I know! She drank all the grape juice,
AND ate all the chocolate!
Hey, I was saving tha-
No, you're wrong again!
Milk's fallen ill!
Oh, I see. EEHH? Milk's sick?!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Protect Milk! Karen, the Knight on a White Horse.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?!