Karen-san!
I knew she rode horses, but...
...I never knew she had one at home.
Karen-san's so cool! When she's riding on a white horse, it's almost like...
...oh, hey, you two are princes, right?
Yeah, we are.
A prince on a white horse...?
Princess Nozomi!
A prince on a...
...white horse.
Now, Princess, give me your hand.
I-I'd love to...
Nozomi? What're you doing?
It's been a while, so I'm a bit rusty.
But you get the idea.
Milk?
Milk, you should take this chance to go for a ride.
I don't need to ride-mil.
Milk...
Coco-sama... Nuts-sama...
Milk?
I think you've got a fever!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
This is bad.
Yes, we have to treat her quickly.
Is Milk really that sick?
It's what you'd call a “cold” in this world, but...
Okay, then I'll go get some medicine!
Don't; it won't work.
If we were in the Palmier Kingdom,
we could have a Pinky cure her.
Only a Pinky named Cappy can help Milk now.
I don't suppose that Pinky's among the ones we've caught so far?
No, it isn't.
Then we'd better find it, and fast!
You're right.
Let's start searching immediately.
I'll come with you-mil...
Milk!
Don't strain yourself.
You have to get your rest.
Karen?
Leave the Pinky-finding to us.
You just take care of Milk while we're gone!
Please!
All right.
Protect Milk! Karen,
the Knight on a White Horse
You know...
If you're that sick,
you can always go home.
But if I left, that would cause all kinds of—
If you go on vacation,
we won't even notice you're gone.
T-That's harsh...
It's just as Hadenya-san says.
You're quite free to take a vacation.
A permanent one.
N-No, this time, I'll be sure
to defeat Pretty Cure, and then...
...did I misspeak?
Excuse me, boys.
Just let me handle everything.
Evasive maneuvers!
Here I go!
I've never gotten along with Hadenya-san...
Neither have I.
Is something wrong?
The lips are moving,
even on top of the mask...
Oh no! Her fever's gone up.
Milk!
Must hurry back... to Natts House...
Must... prepare meals...
Milk!
You're in no condition to.
Karen...
Milk...
If there's anything I can do for you...
Wait, I know!
All right, girls. If you find Cappy,
meet up back here.
Nozomi and Rin, you're with me.
Urara and Komachi, you go with Nuts.
How did I care for you when you were younger?
Please tell me, in as much detail as possible!
Why would you ask about that?
Has one of your friends fallen ill?
Ah, no...
Yes.
I see. How unfortunate.
You always had this much on hand?
Yes.
The best thing for a fever is a towel soaked in ice water.
Dip it into the water like this,
and then wring it out thoroughly.
Then, place it gently on
their forehead, like this.
I-I understand.
This brings back memories.
I always did this first thing in the morning.
Ah, and then...
...they will have sweated profusely, and you'll need to wipe that off.
Make sure they have water to drink.
Right.
And also, if they feel up to eating something...
These apples, right?
Yes. Although it might be best to peel them beforehand, if they're for a small child.
I'm remembering...
all the times I caught colds.
You'd peel them,
and then feed them to me...
Jiiya...
Yes?
Did you always go through
all this trouble to care for me?
Well, I wouldn't have called it “trouble.”
I always wanted to see
a healthy smile on your face.
Jiiya...
Yes?
Thank you!
Not at all...
I want to see Milk smile, too.
Because I love Milk's smile.
Milk, are you all right?
Cappy... where are you?
Leave the cleaning to me-mil!
No snacking before meals-mil!
We have to do something for Milk.
It'll be fine.
Once we find Cappy...
...we'll take him back to Milk.
Yeah.
Nuts-sama, I made some accessories too-mil.
Coco-sama, Nuts-sama,
it's time for snacks-mil!
Milk... always seemed so lively.
But she was actually exhausted.
We want...
We want to do something for her too.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Charlie?
Is this little guy Cappy?
Yes, he is.
Huh? Something's appeared!
It's just you?
Yes, it's just me.
How strange.
I thought I felt the presence of
some Palmier Kingdom residents.
Doesn't one of them have...
...the Dream Collet?
I won't let you reach Milk!
In that case, shall we get started?
Go ahead, attack me.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
Let's go!
Not so fast!
Hah. You're no match for me
all by your lonesome.
Is that where she is?
Stop... right there.
Huh?
Oh, there's still some fight in you?
I won't...
...let you...
...reach Milk!
In that case, go ahead...
...try and stop me!
Karen...
How disappointing.
You aren't able to protect anything!
Time to end this!
It's over for you!
You guys...
We won't let you...
...hurt Karen-san any more!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of
the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
What a bunch of willful girls.
Before you act concerned about others, you should worry about yourselves!
What do we have here? Nothing that can stand against me, that's for sure!
Charlie...
What a shame.
Are you already beaten?
Not yet, we aren't!
Huh?
If you think you'll be getting to Milk...
...think again!
How amusing.
Aqua...
Didn't I tell you?
You won't be reaching Milk!
Not on my watch!
The rock-crushing power of a young maiden's outpourings... take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
You've managed to surprise me.
Charlie...
Aqua!
How did I... wind up here?
Coco-sama, Nuts-sama...!
I apologize for troubling you.
It's okay-coco.
This all happened because you pushed yourself too hard for our sake-nuts.
Thanks for everything-coco.
Coco-sama... Nuts-sama...
Girls, I have tea and snacks
prepared for you on the terrace.
Tea?!
Snacks-coco!
Snacks-nuts!
I'm gonna be first!
Hey, wait up, Nozomi!
Hey, no fair!
There's no need to rush, you three.
Milk...
Karen...
You changed my towels, fed me apples,
and protected me from Nightmare...
Thank you-mil, Karen.
I don't mind...
...because I love your smile, Milk.
Let’s dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun (Go! Go!)
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You’ll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let’s go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
“Hey, what’s with that?”
“dondakee!?” tte
It’s okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let’s turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you’ll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let’s go!
It’s your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you’re worried
nayandemo
Even if you’re tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you’re stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Komachi-san, aren't you glad you finished your novel?
Thank you. I never could've done it
without all your support.
But Nuts sure is a tough critic.
Y-Yeah, I guess so.
But I really appreciated it.
Komachi-san, what kind of novel are you writing next?
I don't know... maybe something about someone who's closed their heart off?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Nuts's Key and Komachi's Heart.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?