I'm home!
What's up?
Right now, Nuts is reading "Pirate Hurricane."
Ah, Komachi's novel.
She's scrapped it all and
started over again and again.
This makes the seventh time.
It wouldn't kill Nuts to praise her a little.
They may be harsh,
but Nuts' critiques are sound.
I hope she gets a good review this time...
Interesting.
The hero and his companions
affirm their friendship,
and the hero opens the door with the key.
The hopeful ending wasn't bad, either.
I think it's a good piece of work.
Komachi? You did it!
Isn't this great, Komachi-san?
Congratulations, Komachi-san!
Really?
Nuts doesn't tell lies.
Being recognized by Nuts-sama
is impressive-mil!
Do you feel honored-mil?
Nuts-san, thank you!
It's the result of your efforts.
All righty, we're all gonna celebrate!
It's decided!
I'll get started on the tea.
The key of hope, huh?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Hey you guys, it's getting late-nuts.
I don't want anyone finding out about you-nuts.
I got it-coco!
Give it back-nuts!
Don't get so worked up over a useless key-coco!
I'll take it off your hands-coco!
Give it back-nuts!
There's no point staying hung up
on the past-coco!
The future is more important-coco...
Nuts's Key and Komachi's Heart
It appears that Hadenya-san has failed again, hasn't she?
Wait, where IS Hadenya-san?
Huh? You were talking to me?
Well, I've been here all morning, and I haven't seen her at all.
Didn't she have the day off?
Taking the day off,
despite being a failure?
What do you think of that, Mr. Bloody?
Shall I have you take care of it?
You've grown quite arrogant, Kawarino, if you think you can order me around.
I assure you, that is not the case.
As your former subordinate, I know better than anyone
the many contributions you've made
to the Nightmare cause.
I'm scarcely worthy to sit at your feet.
You've always had
quite the way with words.
Your words of praise honor me greatly.
That's for sure! Kawarino-san,
you really are one smooth talker...
I will get results.
But I'll be doing things my way.
Good luck out there.
I wish for Komachi-san's novel to win a prize at the contest.
Please grant her wish-coco!
Please grant her wish-mil!
Nuts, you wish too-coco.
The world's not kind enough to fulfill dreams from wishes alone-nuts.
NUTS!
He's right.
Huh?
If I rest on my laurels after writing one book,
I'll never become an author.
I'll get started on the next story!
What kind of story will you be writing next?
Well, I'm still not sure...
Maybe I'll write something
completely unlike an adventure novel.
All right!
Watching Komachi-san has filled me with motivation.
Time to get back to work!
Oh right, your next job involves appearing on a morning talk show, doesn't it?
Yep. My manager, Washio-san,
said that I can choose
my own outfit for tomorrow.
I was about to go buy one.
In that case, why don't we all tag along?
It's decided!
You're hopeless, Nozomi.
However, I was heading to the bookstore,
so this is convenient for me.
I suppose I can come, if it
wouldn't be a nuisance to you, Urara.
Okay! Let's all go!
Yeah!
Let's get going.
Autumn Classical Concert
Nuts-san and I are going to
stop by the bookstore.
We'll meet up in an hour.
At this spot.
Right!
Urara!
I bet this'll look great on you!
I think you're right!
I think this one would be better.
Karen and Rin can never agree on anyth-
Aren't they both pretty cute?
Oh man, I am so screwed!
I got separated from the others...
Rin-chan~!
Are you lost, young lady?
I'll show you the way.
I'm not anybody you should be... afraid of.
Coco, you look way too suspicious with those on!
Do I?
Yeah, they're totally weird!
Still, this brings back memories.
I used to disguise myself and sneak out of
the Palmier Kingdom like this all the time.
Huh? Wouldn't everybody flip out if their prince up and disappeared?
Yeah, it was kingdom-wide chaos.
Wow, that conflicts with...
...the serious image I'd had of you.
I felt bad for all the people
who'd worry about me,
but I wanted to see
things in the world for myself.
So you were a troublemaker, huh?
I bet Nuts was right there with you,
every step of the way.
No...
Did you find a book
that you wanted to read?
Lots of them. So many that I can't decide.
I see.
Coco always used to give me books.
He'd sneak out of the kingdom
and travel around to various places.
Nuts always seemed interested in the outside world,
but I could never get him to leave the kingdom.
He'd always cite his mission of protecting the Dream Collet and the Pinkies.
"There's no way I can leave the kingdom."
So I'd always bring back books as souvenirs for Nuts.
Nuts may be grumpy now,
but back then, he'd laugh and act happy.
I see.
I want to see Nuts smile, too.
After all, Nuts is always like
"I mustn't laugh." He brings himself down.
That's... how you see him?
Yeah.
Someday, I want to laugh and have fun
with Nuts and everyone else.
It's gotta be possible.
Yeah! We should all try
to make him burst out laughing.
Autumn Classical Concert
It looks like the others aren't here yet.
Yeah, we're a bit early.
What are you looking at?
The glimmering greenery, and the bustling breeze.
People smiling.
It's all so peaceful.
It certainly is.
Normally, I'd never notice it.
They are precious things.
And upon recognizing these precious things,
you realize they will be lost.
And what remains after
having lost everything...
...is known as "despair."
Do you understand?
You're...
That key hangs like a millstone
on your chest...
...and serves as a reminder.
What?
Isn't that the key to the gates of the Palmier Kingdom?
The Palmier Kingdom's ...key?
Don't tell me you're the one who...?
Sadly, I have no business card.
But perhaps you'll understand this?
Something's appeared!
I have come to retrieve the Dream Collet.
Won't you give it to me?
We'll never let you have it!
I wasn't asking you.
Komachi!
Are you all right?
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth,
Cure Mint!
Ah, so you were a Pretty Cure?
However, I have no time to spare for sparring with you.
That's right...
I'll fill in some gaps in your knowledge...
...concerning the demise of the Palmier Kingdom.
The precious kingdom where you were born and raised...
...was razed to the ground,
with nary a stone or a trace remaining.
It was I who accomplished all that.
You were the one-nuts!
That was the job I was tasked with.
Being an adult means fully executing all of one's assignments.
What about you?
Weren't you a prince?
Were you able to protect your subjects?
I...
...couldn't do anything-nuts.
That's not true, Nuts-san!
Nuts-san!
W-What is this?
You guys!
Nozomi-san!
I feel the presences of Nightmare and Nuts on the other side-coco!
Does that include Komachi?
Let's go, girls!
Yeah!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
Now why did the kingdom fall to ruin?
What do you think?
I...
Because I opened
the Palmier Kingdom gates-nuts.
It was my fault-nuts.
If I hadn't been there...
...the Palmier Kingdom wouldn't have been destroyed-nuts!
Precisely. It was all your fault.
Nuts-san, he's wrong!
It wasn't your fault!
You have no right to possess the Dream Collet.
Surrender it.
What is the matter?
Surely...
...you don't still intend to protect the Collet?
You are involving innocents from an unaffiliated world.
As things stand, this world will wind up like the Palmier Kingdom:
gone, vanished, destroyed.
You'll be to blame.
Nuts-san...
Now, give it to me.
Stop stalling!
You have a dream!
Do you plan on throwing it away?!
"Don't give up on it!"
Isn't that what you told me?
Weren't we going to revive the Palmier Kingdom?
Wasn't that your dream?!?
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Nuts-san! Don't you let go of that Dream Collet!
Be sure to hold it tight!
The Dream Collet is to be used
by those with power.
By us, the Nightmares.
That's not true!
The Dream Collet should be used by someone who knows, fears, and reveres its power.
It's fit for someone who'd sacrifice everything and burn themselves out!
There's only one person who can do that.
Someone who's straightforward and kind,
and has a strong spirit!
Nuts-san!
You're the only one.
You cannot protect the Collet with "spirit" alone.
It's impossible.
With that level of power,
you can't protect anything.
Mint!
Everyone...
Nuts-sama!
Nuts-coco!
I'm so glad you're unharmed-mil.
I'm impressed you've broken my barrier
to make it this far.
If it's to save our friends,
there's no place we won't or can't go!
For your companions?
Is that the motive behind your power?
We're hoping that someday,
we'll all be able to laugh together.
And we'll overcome any hardships to fulfill that hope.
You'd better believe it!
Why don't you show me the extent
of your powers, and what they can do?
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Heh heh. So this is the power of Pretty Cure?
Thank you.
I'm... still immature.
If you hadn't been there for me...
...I would've followed his commands.
There's no way...
I thought I knew what I
should do from here on out.
Coco said the same thing.
"There's no point replaying the past."
You look a little pale.
Are you getting enough sleep at night?
A-Ah, no. I've been piling up
a bit of sleep debt lately...
Writing novels is admirable,
but not at the expense of your health.
I'll read anything and everything you write...
...until you fulfill that dream
of becoming an author.
I'll give you as much advice as I can.
So I want you to take
better care of yourself.
Komachi... what's wrong?
All I could do was cry.
He praised me, and I felt flattered.
When he was kind to me,
I was unable to stop my tears.
But he was more than just kind.
I could tell he couldn't forgive himself.
The key to his kingdom always
weighed heavily upon his heart.
I wanted to lighten the burden
of that key, if only a little.
A new story?
You don't have to hide it.
W-Well, it's just that I feel embarrassed when people see my rough drafts.
What kind of novel is it this time?
In this story,
a lonely woman...
...meets someone who lights up her heart.
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Aww, I can't run a race! I just can't!
Marathons are just too hardcore for me...
It's all good! As long as you keep running,
you'll eventually reach the goal.
Come on, let's run together.
Wait, is that the goal already?
Isn't this just a dead end?
Or maybe it's a Nightmare?!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Go for the Goal! Marathon Race
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?