No, no! I don't wanna! No way!
Dang it, Nozomi! Get back here!
No! No, no, noooo!
You promised to practice
for the marathon, didn't you?
But I just can't run 4 km...
Wrong answer.
All students must participate in the marathon.
Let's all do our best.
Fight!
No, no! I'm not doing anything!
This is why I said I'd practice with you!
Wait, I know! Rin-chan,
if you win this year, it'll be two years in a row. I'll be cheering for you!
See ya!
Hey! You'll be running, too!
How pathetic-mil.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Man, I'm so hungry.
Gamao-san?
I hear you have been by
the Nightmare main office lately.
Yeah, I dropped by to see you.
You said you could make me
an official member of Nightmare.
Official member, you say?
I'm well aware of your skills and experience.
But unfortunately,
you've yet to produce any results.
Have you contributed a single thing
to Nightmare thus far?
W-Well...
If you could produce results,
it might be your inroads to management.
Pretty Cure just don't let up.
I'm begging you,
promote me to management!
Management gets fat salaries for easy work, right?
I won't say that there isn't a way, but...
If you use a certain black paper...
Black... paper?
Oh, I've heard of that! The stuff that gives you
ridiculous amounts of power, right?
True, that power is formidable.
However, I cannot recommend it for you.
There have been cases where it hasn't worked correctly...
I don't care, just give it to me! I need it!
On second thought, perhaps I shouldn't.
Only the chosen few are able to use it.
Ah, a management meeting is about to begin.
I'll have to excuse myself, Gamao-san.
H-Hey!
Man, why does he keep yanking my chain?
This is the real deal!
Winning'll be a piece of cake with this!
I'll be on the fast track to management!
As long as you obtain the Dream Collet...
...it matters naught what becomes of you.
Go for the Goal! Marathon Race
I can't go on...
We haven't even run 2 km.
I'm sleepy! I'm tired!
Suck it up, you wimp! I only have free time in the morning.
And now I've got to get to futsal practice.
Don't fall asleep, Nozomi!
Rin's a hard worker.
Unlike some people...
I'm not sleeping...
Rin-san, how's Nozomi-san's
practice coming along?
She's got a long ways to go.
I have to find some way to motivate her
before the race.
If you're with her, I'm sure Nozomi-san'll be able to finish the race.
Yes. There's not a coach around
who's more passionate than you.
I suppose so.
Rin, you're looking a little pale.
Are you tired?
Huh? Ah, no, of course not!
I don't have any time to be tired.
And now, I have to go help out at home.
It's as if she'd rather collapse than complain.
Isn't there anything
we can do to help her?
No, nooo! I don't wanna run 4 km!
You'll survive. And once you've run 4 km once,
you'll feel a lot better.
She's right!
Huh? You three?
Let's all run together, okay?
I'm not such a good runner,
but I'll do the best I can.
I'm running to build up my stamina for work!
But why do we have to run, too?
Don't be that way. Let's go along with it,
for Nozomi-san's sake.
There's no honor greater than running alongside Coco-sama and Nuts-sama-mil.
You'd better not drag them down, Nozomi-mil!
You're just riding along in a bag, Milk!
Whether I'm cheering from inside a bag,
or running with them...
...my feelings are the same-mil!
They're not the same! They're so not the same!
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Anyway, we'll be running
the actual 4 km course today.
We'll all reach the goal!
Yeah!
Yeah...
Just run your race at your pace.
Umm, sure, yeah...
N-Nozomi?!
I can't... go on...
Nozomi, it's just a bit farther.
Once we climb this hill,
the goal will be in sight.
Come on.
Rin-chan?!
Rin-san!
Rin!
I'm okay now.
I was just a bit exhausted.
Rin-san, haven't you been
pushing yourself too hard?
You're always overdoing things.
I'm sorry to worry you.
But why'd you do all that
to run with Nozomi?
Because...
Well, the truth is...
Nozomi, do you remember the Sports Meet
from our 3rd-grade year?
Back then, there wasn't anyone faster than me.
The whole class was absolutely certain I'd win.
But I tripped along the way,
and as everyone started to pass me,
I thought about quitting the race and giving up on running entirely.
But then...
Rin-chan!
Nozomi?
You okay?
I'll run with you, so let's keep going till the end.
Y-Yeah.
1-2, 1-2, 1-2...
1-2, 1-2, 1-2...!
S-Something like that happened?
Nozomi, you were the one who taught me...
...to run to the end without giving up.
I wanted you to run till the end,
just like you wanted me to do back then.
Rin-chan...
Thank you!
I'll try my hardest not to give up
until I've reached the goal!
Nozomi...
I'll put all my effort into winning that repeat championship!
Great!
Everyone's feelings are united-mil!
I'm sure you'll be able to
see things through to the end-mil!
Campus Marathon Race
Rin, are you all right?
Yeah! I got plenty of rest,
so I'm in top form!
Nozomi, remember to keep your own pace.
Y-Yeah.
The All-Student 4-km Marathon will now begin.
On your marks, get set...
Good luck, everyone.
What're they getting so worked up about?
All they're doing is running.
One more to go...
Um, what?
Rin?
You're all...
Nozomi?
Wait, what? How'd we wind up here?
Over here! You've all run a good race!
This is the end of the line for you!
Nightmare!
Something's appeared!
Come on, can't you just give me the Dream Collet already?
Once I get the Dream Collet,
I'll be a Nightmare manager,
and enjoy a relaxing, fun-filled lifestyle!
You really think we'll let you have it?
I hope you're ready!
I'll take you all down with one shot!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth,
Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the power of hope...
...and the light of the future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Was there really a point to that!?
There's more where that came from!
Dream!
Rouge!
This is awful! They're
completely drained-coco!
It's only natural. They've just been running their hearts out-nuts!
You okay?
Yeah.
This is just painful to watch.
You're all worn out from that marathon, right?
You don't even get anything from it,
you just get tired.
It's just running around for nothing.
Really, it's completely pointless!
There is too a point!
Putting in effort, and not giving up...
...aren't pointless things at all!
Don't you ever shut up!?
What?
We're aiming for the same goal,
and doing our very best to reach it!
No matter how difficult or frustrating things get...
...if our feelings are as one...
...we will  reach that goal!
That's why there's a point to us running together!
Listening to you all makes me feel like I've run a marathon!
That's...!
Thanks to this thing's power,
I'm gonna score an easy win today!
This'll make me a straight shooter to upper manageme-
The heck?! What is this I don't even-
Dream!
Lemonade, Aqua, Mint!
Take this!
Rouge!
Dream!
He's after the Dream Collet-coco!
We'll never hand it over to a freak like you!
Dream!
What she said!
Anyone who makes fun of
what we've strove for together...
Rouge!
We won't surrender the Dream Collet!
We'll see things through...
...to the very end!
As long as our feelings are united...
...we'll never give up!
Milk's feelings are the same as everyone else's-mil!
Together with the powers of Dreams and Hope...
O Five Lights, right here and now...
Pretty Cure Five Explosion!!
Well, we'd better hurry back.
Right!
And... we're in last place, aren't we?
The goal's just ahead.
Yeah.
Here they come!
The final group is now returning.
Nozomi, we managed to reach the goal together.
Yeah...
But you lost your chance at a repeat title.
That is a crying shame.
But at this point, being able
to run till the end with you guys...
...is enough to make me really happy.
Rin-chan!
Come on, we're almost at the goal.
All righty, now it's a race between the five of us!
No fair!
Wait a sec!
That's cheating!
Wait for me!
Everyone!
Do your best!
They ran strong to the very end-mil.
Let’s dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You’ll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let’s go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
“Hey, what’s with that?”
“dondakee!?” tte
It’s okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let’s turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you’ll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let’s go!
It’s your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you’re worried
nayandemo
Even if you’re tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you’re stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Guess what's next for us after the marathon race!
What're we doing?
It's the big big big operation to protect Coco's health!
Big operation?
You can't just eat choux a la creme-
you need vegetables, meat, and fish, too.
Keep a good balance, and be sure to stay active. Let's exercise!
Too bad your energy can't burn his fat.
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Grand Operation: Coco's Health!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay!?