Soooo good!
Like a bite of happiness!
Coco-san? Don't you think you're eating a bit too much?
You know, we've still got the cream puffs Karen brought from Celeb Hall.
There's no limit to the number of cream puffs I can eat-coco!
Coco?
I'm all right-coco. Dokkoisho!
"Dokkoisho"?
What, you're some kind of sumo wrestler now?
Is it just me, or have you... "expanded" a little?
I have not-coco!
Then can you prove it by turning into Cocoda-sensei?
No problem-coco!
Seems normal to me.
You're right.
No, he only appears normal at first glance.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Timing, QC: Force Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Translation, etc.: Zalis
Not for Sale, Rent, Auction or Streaming
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
W-What was with that stomach?!
His belly looked all fat and pudgy!
Seeing it up close was pretty shocking.
A fat and pudgy stomach-mil?
That's right! Lately, Coco-sama's been eating nothing but cream puffs-mil!
We have seen a lot of tasty new cream puff varieties in here.
If we don't do something about this...
Come on, a little fat never hurt anybody.
I'm always stuffing my face with cream puffs too.
So am I!
The problem lies with eating
cream puffs and nothing else.
In addition to cream puffs, you two also eat rice, meat, fish, vegetables, and fruit.
Since you're not picky, you eat anything you can get your hands on, right?
Indeed, continuing this unbalanced diet
of yours would be unhealthy.
You might get seriously ill.
We can't let that happen!
Being healthy is top priority!
I've decided-mil! Starting today, Milk will firmly take control of...
...and rebalance Coco-sama's unbalanced diet-mil!
All right! Let's make Coco
a shining example of health!
It's decided!
Grand Operation: Coco's Health!
Hey everyone, your tea is ready.
In the end, Gamao-kun really was worthless.
"Was," as in past tense?
Don't tell me he went and did it again!?
Why is no one able to make full use of
the highly effective items I give them?
Those actions were far too dangerous!
My, what's going on here?
You're getting unusually heated.
I'm losing one subordinate after another...
Fall time is food time.
Aren't you just irritated because your stomach's empty?
G-Gamao was my subordinate-!
Useless people are useless.
There's no need to feel any pity for them.
Forget about him already!
Now that I've eaten my fill,
it's time I stepped out.
It was a good meal-coco!
For the time being, you'll be eating
nutritious cuisine prepared by Milk-mil.
And now for desert-!
No-mil!
Cream puffs are not allowed-mil!
But Nuts is always
wolfing down daifuku, too-coco.
Why isn't he  fat-coco?
Because I eat a balanced diet with lots of different things-nuts.
Ahem-mil.
Coco-sama, snacking between meals is a no-no-mil!
Just one more. This'll be
my last cream puff, I swear...
I can't eat any more-mil...
M-Milk...
Coco?
Is he all right?
His heart seems deeply conflicted.
The ban on cream puffs has hit him hard.
Anyone would react like that
if their favorite food was taken away.
Is it really that hard?
What if I told you that you
couldn't eat fried eggs?
Eh?! No way! I'd totally hate that!
That's exactly what Coco's going through right now.
Coco...
Coco's looking completely drained.
He won't even touch the food you make for him, Milk-san?
It looks like he wants cream puffs-mil.
If Milk can't help Coco-sama restore his health,
then she's a failure as a caregiver-mil.
Milk...
In that case, we should cook something to re-energize Coco!
She's right! Let's all
work together to make it.
Of course, I'll want Rin-chan and Milk as the cooking leaders.
That'd be great, since Milk
knows Coco better than any of us.
A servant like Milk can be the leader-mil?
Yeah.
If it concerns Coco-sama,
you can count on Milk-mil!
Let's all do our best
for Coco-sama's sake-mil!
Yeah!
It's peeled.
Urara, what's this-mil?
I thought he should eat some fruit,
so I peeled this apple.
With as much as you've cut off,
I think the peel will be tastier-mil.
K-Karen-san?!
What?
W-What're you making?
Miso soup. The inclusion of dried sardines
not only adds flavor, it also provides
plenty of inosinic acid and glutamine,
which makes for a very nutritious miso soup.
How can you know so much about flavoring,
but so little about measuring?
Don't you think that's a bit too much?
Hey, hold it!
Why are you adding youkan?!
As caregiver and cooking leader,
I can't serve this to Coco-sama-mil.
Get it together-mil!
Okay...
Seriously, who puts youkan in porridge-mil?
It's surprisingly good-mil.
I'll use this chance to grab one of
Karen's Celeb Hall cream puffs-coco!
Coco?
I built it-nuts.
You put this here-coco?
You've got to eat a balanced diet and get plenty of exercise-nuts.
Those are the basics of staying healthy-nuts.
Huh? This scent is...
Cream puffs! I knew it!
Care for a sample, young man?
Our cream puffs are to die for!
To die for?
Come on, try one.
T-Try one?
Yes, just take a little bite...
If it's just a bite...
I suppose I can...
That's right, just gobble it down!
Can I, really?!
They're sweet and delicious!
Eat it now, don't delay!
You love cream puffs, don't you?
Come now, don't hold back.
On second thought, I'll pass.
Oh, you're saying you don't want them?
Always being cautious and going without...
you people are in chains of your own making.
You'll never beat my extravagant self-indulgence with that attitude!
When I see a food I like, I eat it.
And when I see something I want, I take it!
A Nightmare!
I won't hesitate to take
anything and everything!
Including, but not limited to,
glory, fame, and your Dream Collet!
Something's appeared!
Coco!
You girls sure got here quickly.
Give Coco back!
Sure, I'll give him back.
In exchange for the Dream Collet, that is!
What're you saying-coco?!
You can't do that-coco!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the power of Hope...
...and the Light of the future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Coco!
Look out-mil!
You can't attack me while this one
is in here, can you?
Give Coco back to us!
How can I "give him back"?
He came in here under his own free will.
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
He wound up inside this car because he
gave in to temptation and ate cream puffs.
Notice how he hasn't been saying anything?
Your efforts have been wasted on him!
T-That's not true-coco!
That's wrong-coco...
True, I was about  to give in-coco. But...!
Liar!
The Coco I know would never lose to temptation!
Dream!
That's right!
He's pure-hearted and hardworking...
Once he's made up his mind,
he sees things through to the end!
That's how Coco is!
You all...
Still playing the friendship game?
Useless people are nothing but obstacles to be removed!
Why can't you understand such simple logic?!
Coco!
Coco, jump!
Dream...!
You'll be fine. I know you can make it!
There's no way someone who can't resist temptation would have that kind of courage!
Coco!!
What?!
Coco!
Coco-sama!
I knew you could pull it off.
Don't act so arrogant just because
you caught a lucky break!
Now that Coco's safe and sound,
this fight is ours!
Yeah!
The powerful flame of
a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Now my stomach's running on empty. Hmph!
Thanks for waiting!
It smells so good-coco!
Here you go!
Cream puffs-coco!!
But cream puffs were banned-coco...
They're special Pretty Cure cream puffs,
so we'll make an exception.
They've got vegetable sweeteners
instead of sugar, so they're low-calorie!
Vegetables-coco?
Yes-mil. First, you steam and crush the vegetables-mil.
Then you add tofu grease and soy milk,
and heat it over a low flame.
Finally, you add scented vanilla sugar,
and you're done.
The cream contains carrots, pumpkin, and green soybeans.
Incredible-nuts!
Everyone...
Coco, go ahead and eat it.
It's yummy-coco!
Thank you all-coco!
Glad you like it!
Coco-sama, if you eat any more, you'll suffer a relapse-mil.
There's nothing more
insecure than security.
Milk will take care of the remaining ones-mil.
No way-coco!
Dokkoisho...
Dokkoisho?!
Milk, can you turn this way for a moment?
W-Why-mil?
I get the feeling you've...
"expanded" a little.
You think so too, Komachi?
She's been taste-testing all the food we've made.
And polishing it off
to the last bite.
You've been eating and eating, without ever exercising-nuts.
You can use this-coco!
That's right, Milk. If you're going to eat,
you'd better exercise!
It's decided!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Once upon a time, in a land far away,
there was a girl named Cinderella-mil.
Ooh, I've heard this one!
The girl was clumsy and stupid,
so they didn't take her to the ball-mil.
Is that how the story went?
She somehow made it to the ball,
but she did more tripping than dancing.
Yes, Nozomi certainly is clumsy-
Okay, now you're just badmouthing me!!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Pretty Cure 5's Cinderella Story
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?