Here, Milk-san.
Thank you-mil.
Cinderella? How nostalgic.
When I was little, my parents read it to me all the time.
Milk, want me to read it to you?
Huh? Why would I need a lousy reader like you to do that for me-mil?
And here I was trying to be nice!
Milk didn't borrow this
storybook to read  it-mil.
It's for the sake of the novel I'm writing-mil.
Novel?!
And... you're writing one?
That's right-mil! Unlike Nozomi, Milk is very studious.
I want to write a story from this world-mil.
Did you really need
the "Unlike Nozomi" part?
But what're you going to do with that Cinderella storybook?
I'm going to copy down its story-mil.
Transcribing a story can be very helpful in learning about story structure
and how to express oneself in writing.
It's good practice for writing a novel.
I'll do my best-mil!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Pretty Cure!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go! Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Bloody-san... Bloody-san?
Bloody-san, your tea is ready.
Or something to that effect.
Now what if I were to sit here...?
Oh yeah, this feels like the place I was always meant to be.
Isn't this seat just perfect for me?
I'm sure I fill it better than that  guy.
Don't you all agree?
What, ignoring me again?
Mirror, mirror, in my hand,
who's the greatest in the Nightmare band?
Why of course,
that would have to be Bunbee-san.
Right?
Whoa, tough crowd.
This isn't right.
This isn't how my success story
was supposed to be!
Pretty Cure 5's Cinderella Story
Milk's shut herself in her room
and won't come out.
If she's skipping snacks,
she must be working pretty hard.
Just copying it down is too boring-mil.
I'll tweak the story a little-mil.
Once upon a time, in a faraway land...
...there lived a girl named Cinderella,
along with her wicked mother...
...and two wicked older sisters-mil.
Aah~ I was just about to finish,
but now I have even more to clean!
Cinderella, unless this place is spotless,
we can't make a deal.
Aw, c'mon...!
She's right. Good luck, Cinderella!
You're supposed to be the wicked  mother here.
Don't encourage her with
kind words and a smile!
Oh no...
Say, isn't it about time we got ready for the ball?
You mean the ball that the Prince is throwing tonight?!
Y-Yeah.
That's right! I'd better start
getting ready, or I'll be late!
Um, I hate to say it, but...
What kind of dress should I wear...?
Maybe something cute,
yet attention-grabbing!
And if I want to stand out,
I'd better have some frills...
You  can't go.
Huh? Why not!?
Cinderella, you have to mind the house.
Sucks to be you,
but that's how the story goes.
No way! I've just gotta go!
I know how you feel,
but we must conform to the story.
You three are just so so unfair!
We'll be sure to buy a souvenir for you.
They sell souvenirs at dances?
Maybe, maybe not. Anyway, it's been decided
that you're minding the house.
Tidy up for us, will you?
I just hope the house
will still be standing.
I bet they're having a ball at the ball right now.
If only I had a fabulous dress,
then I could go too...
Huh?
Aaaah, move it, clear the way!!!
What the...?
Good evening, Cinderella.
I'm Urara the Witch.
You're a witch?!
Yes! I'll get you all dolled up for the ball with my magic.
Really?!
First off, I'll get you a dress and some shoes. Here we go!
Please, please do!
Crackle, pop!
All right, perfect.
Now I can go to Ogre Island...
Wait, why am I Momotaro?!
Ah, sorry. I got my stories mixed up.
You're my only hope!
Second time's the charm. Crackle, pop!
Hey...
Hmm, that's strange...
It didn't work right.
If you don't get me into a dress soon,
the ball will be over!
Leave it to me, I'll get it right this time. Crackle, pop!
All right!
Wow, it's so wonderfully lovely!
I finally got you dressed up.
Listen closely. The magic will wear off
at the stroke of midnight.
You'll return to your original form.
Therefore, you must be home
from the ball by 12:00.
Got it!
Now then, we should be dancing, too.
They're not called "slippers" for nothing.
Are you all right?
Y-Yes, I'm fine!
T-Thank you very much!
It's Prince Coco!
Prince... Coco?
If you don't mind,
may I have this dance?
Yes.
That's the kind of story we're in.
Want to dance?
Prince Nuts... sure!
Hey, who's that girl
dancing with Prince Coco?
It's Cinderella, as in
the story's title character.
I already knew that,
but I still had to say my lines.
Wow, that dance looks so fun!
Wait, you're the Witch.
What're you doing at the ball?
And you've even dressed up...
I just felt like coming to the ball.
And I was just at the good part, too...!
Cinderella had a great fall-mil.
Poor clumsy Cinderella will trip and fall
while dancing at the ball...
How's it going?
What do you want, Cinderella -
I mean, Nozomi-mil?
I brought you some snacks.
Don't disturb her, Nozomi.
Milk won't be able to concentrate.
She's got a point, Nozomi-san.
I understand; even though
the manuscript is copied,
you're still too embarrassed
to have it read.
Maybe I'll have a change of pace in a different place-mil.
They were this  close to reading it-mil.
Now, where should I write
the next part-mil?
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
Give that manuscript back to Milk-mil!
Not bad. In fact, it's pretty good!
Maybe it's interesting enough
for me to use?
Something's appeared!
And very close by.
Milk went outside!
What?!
We were  just outside the store, right?
What is this place?
We're inside a castle.
What's with these outfits?
I'm wearing a dress!
And also... glass slippers?
A grand ball... and glass slippers?
Cinderella?!
Komachi, this is just like that time when
we were in your novel, "Pirate Hurricane."
Yes. Nightmare's behind this.
This is probably the world
of Milk's "Cinderella."
We've become the characters in the story!
So where's Milk?
You really do look the part of princes,
princes of the Palmier Kingdom.
Milk!
Give Milk back!
I'm happy to welcome you all to my masquerade ball!
I'll defeat Pretty Cure and take the Dream Collet.
I'll be using this world to further my agenda and my perfect story!
We'll never let you...
...do that!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future...
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Milk!
Go!
Milk, you okay?
Thank you-mil.
Take Milk somewhere safe.
Right!
I'll blow up this place, castle and all!
Just like I did back in
the Palmier Kingdom.
Stop it! Don't wreck this
storybook world any more!
The prince in this story loses his castle and his kingdom.
That's the kind of tragedy I'm going for!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Time to re-experience the despair
you felt at the end of the Palmier Kingdom!
We won't let you!
You won't be getting your way!
As long as the five of us are here...
...we'll never let you destroy this castle or this world!
Besides, this story's ending is a happy one!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Just wait 'til next time!
My success story will  have a sequel!
Thank goodness!
It looks like it's reverted to
the original Cinderella world.
Thanks, everyone-mil!
Is that...
...the stroke of midnight?
I guess we are following
the Cinderella story.
We'd better hurry home, or else!
Let's go.
Yeah.
We're back.
But it's kind of a shame.
It was such a lovely ball.
My dress was so wonderful...
I wanted to have some more fun.
I've had enough of this brand of
"immersive storytelling."
Well, at least we made it back safely.
Huh?
What is it, Karen?
Is this...?
A glass slipper?!
What's it doing here?
Do you think it made the trip back with us?
What?
Whoever this glass slipper fits will be married...
...to the Prince!
The glass slipper...
...is a perfect fit-mil!
Um, you may fit in  it,
but it doesn't fit you.
H-Hey, the glass slipper was mine!
Get back here, you hateful ball of fluff!
What's this?
Milk fits perfectly into the glass slipper-mil!
That means I'll be
marrying the Prince-mil!
Say, Milk-san...
Milk, I read through it...
Why am I a wicked older sister?
Something's been lost in the transfer...
You're scarier than Cinderella's sisters-mil...
What was that?!
Next time, I want to be Cinderella,
instead of the witch!
But right now, I'm Cinderella.
So give me back that glass slipper!
Stop right there, Milk!
I'll never give it back-mil!!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Such nice, calm weather we're having...
It's like a taste of spring, during autumn.
You sure know a lot, Nozomi-san.
I learned it from Cocoda-sensei.
But it's almost too calm.
I hope nothing bad happens...
There's no way-
We've got trouble! She's here!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Terror! Despariah Appears
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay!?