It's so quiet-mil.
It certainly is-nuts.
Aren't Nozomi and the others
coming over-mil?
They're not helping at the store today,
and they don't have school either-nuts.
So they're all doing their own things-nuts.
It's so quiet that it almost scares me-mil.
It's times like this when
earth-shattering things happen-mil.
There's no way that'll happen-coco!
You're too paranoid-coco!
Milk, on a peaceful day like this,
you should also take it easy-coco.
But Milk is an apprentice caregiver.
It's fine-coco! Nuts, don't you agree-coco?
Yes-nuts.
Very well, I shall do as you say
and excuse myself-mil.
It is awfully calm. Maybe Milk's right,
and something awful will happen-nuts.
Oh, don't you take her side-coco.
Anyway, check out this 72 that Nozomi got on her test-coco!
It's an amazing improvement over the 30 she got last time-coco.
Why don't you meet up with and show it to her instead-nuts?
Because today's a day off-coco!
That doesn't matter-nuts.
What's holding you back-nuts?
Coco!
I found a Pinky.
She came over here herself-nuts.
Huh?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Shoot, the numbers aren't adding up again.
I forgot how much I've entered so far.
I can't believe  I'm doing accounting on my day off!
Ah, Kawarino-san!
Is the irreplaceable Kawarino-san also here to work on a day off? How diligent.
Oh, that's right, should I make some tea?
Have you seen Despariah-sama at all?
Why no, I haven't. Since today's a holiday,
maybe she's on vacation somewhere?
Meanwhile, I'm  working...
Despariah-sama leaves her room so infrequently that she's scarcely ever gone.
Where could she be?
Terror! Despariah Appears
This is strange. Where'd that Pinky go?
I don't feel its presence.
Well, these things happen.
Sorry for bringing you
out here on a day off.
Ah, it's like a little taste of spring.
Spring? But it's almost winter.
They call these surprisingly warm days in a stretch of cold weather a "taste of spring."
Wow, really?
It's such a waste to sit at home on such a lovely day. Want to go out somewhere?
Sure, that sounds great!
Maybe I should go ho-
Right, let's move out!
Hey!
All right, we're all going out!
It's decided!
Good afternoon.
Isn't anybody here?
Karen!
Listen to this-mil!
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama went out with Nozomi and left Milk behind.
And they're still not back yet-mil!
I know today's a caregiver's day off,
but I feel so lonely-mil!
Is that so? How about this?
You can spend your day off chatting with me...
...and eating delicious cake.
Great idea-mil!
Say, you two...
Our magazine is recruiting models
for its "Hotties on the Street" section.
Would you mind if I took your picture?
You're in the way.
Can you get out of my shot?
Eh? Ah, sorry.
Let's go, Nozomi.
Wait, can I get a solo shot of you?
I decline.
Okay, I can take a hint...
Why'd you get so mad over nothing?
She said you were in the way. That's not "nothing," it's rude!
This sure is a big tree.
It's the tallest tree in town. When I was little,
I always wanted to climb it.
But people told me I couldn't,
since it was dangerous.
Let's climb it!
Wha?
Don't do it. Those "people" were right.
We'll be fine. C'mon.
Whoa, what a view!
It's really pretty.
Are you sure this branch is strong enough?
It's perfectly sturdy. Don't tell me you're dredging up the "incident."
Eh? Hey, what's all this
about an incident?
It happened back in the Palmier Kingdom,
at a tree that overlooked
the entire country.
We climbed that tree
when we were really young.
I was against it because
I thought it was dangerous.
You were the one who wanted
to gaze upon the whole kingdom, Nuts.
But that was no reason to climb the King's most prized tree.
And we wound up damaging it.
We searched frantically
for a way to repair it.
So we snuck out of the kingdom
to look for a Pinky that would do that.
And ever since then,
you'd constantly sneak out of the kingdom.
In the end, our caregiver caught us.
But it sure was fun.
They severely scolded us.
Not exactly my idea of "fun."
We got pretty acquainted with
the Reflection Room after that.
I guess you two really were
great friends!
I just wonder what the others are up to.
Rin-san!
Urara? What about your job?
It's finished.
And you? Done helping at the store?
Yes, I am.
Let me guess what's on your mind.
"I wonder how Nozomi and
everyone else are doing," right?
I'm thinking the same thing.
Should we head over to Natts House?
Yes!
Wow, they're sooo cute!
Just adorable!
I'm out of here.
Hey, wait!
I can only stand to be
around you two for so long.
W-What's that  mean?
This isn't like you.
What're you so afraid of?
It's not like we'll be able to stay in this world forever.
Once the Palmier Kingdom is revived...
So I shouldn't get
too close to Nozomi-
W-What was that for?
If you wanted to climb a tree,
you climbed it.
If you wanted to leave
the kingdom, you left it.
That's the kind of guy you were.
But...
Being dragged around by you all the time...
...had its good points.
The kingdom we saw from that tree
was truly beautiful.
Nuts...
See you.
I'm back! But where's Nuts going?
Um, well, he remembered
something he had to do...
What could they all be doing?
Komachi?
Using your day off to work on your novel?
Yes. I had some ideas.
I see. In that case...
Eh? You're leaving?
Umm...
Would you like to come to Natts House with me?
Sure.
Just look around! They're so pretty!
Huh?
Oh, by the way,
I've finished grading the last test.
You have?
Way to go. You got a 72.
I did?
Yeah.
I'm so awesome!
That's the best score I've ever gotten!
If you keep this up, you might be able to raise your grades in other subjects, too.
Yeah, but Japanese is the only one
I really care about.
Huh?
I worked really hard,
since it's your subject.
Coco... thank you...
Coco?
Let's go back.
Nozomi is from this world.
But I'm not.
I know that, but...
No matter how vividly
you envision your dreams,
those dreams will never come true.
When dreams are shattered,
and hope is lost,
all that remains in the end... is despair.
That's...!
Kneel down before despair!
D-Despariah!
Something's appeared!
What?
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
Coco, stand back!
Okay!
I shall see just how "great"
your power of hope is.
Dream!
Hmph. You wish for the revival of your kingdom,
yet you also wish to avoid parting with that girl.
Neither of those dreams will be fulfilled.
And clinging to hopeless hopes
is a fool's endeavor!
Coco!!
Those eyes...
Those eyes that have not lost hope...
Do you really think you can win
this desperate battle all by yourself?
Yes, I do. After all, I'm not alone!
Nozomi!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
You all...
That's Despariah-nuts!
Why is she here-mil?
This really is earth-shattering-mil!
Go, my shadows!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
They're endless!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Look, everybody! If they get separated from the ground, they'll disappear!
Now I get it.
Dream, leave these guys to us!
You guys-!
Companions?!
But that hope will eventually vanish.
It's only a matter of time.
None of us will ever abandon hope!
The potential of a young girl's dreams... take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Is this all you've got?
Dream, behind you!
It isn't nearly enough.
Not one person can resist despair.
Dream!
Coco!
Meeting the ones from the Palmier Kingdom was your greatest misfortune.
Regret it, and fall into despair.
He taught me...
Coco taught me...
...that sunny fall days like today are called "a taste of spring"!
Huh?
Not only that, he taught me the value of studying and the importance of friends!
I'll never ever regret meeting Coco!
Nozomi...
Pointless. Your fleeting emotions
have no value.
They will all fade away,
leaving only despair in their wake!
You're wrong about that!
The random conversations...
The scenery we saw together...
They're all...
...precious, irreplaceable things to me!
Yes, the feelings may be temporary...
...but the treasures they leave in the heart last forever!
Any and all eras will come to an end,
with only despair lying beyond!
No matter what lies beyond,
my feelings won't change-coco.
No one can erase the hope that Dream gave me-coco!
I'll be sure to fulfill your dreams, Coco!
What good comes from
fulfilling others' dreams?
Seeing the happy looks on their faces, what else?
People don't only act
to further their own interests.
If you think of another,
your hearts reach an understanding!
That's how powerful emotions are born!
That's why we'll...
...always keep standing back up!
Everyone...
It's pointless to struggle.
Do you really think you can defeat me?
Well, who knows? But we'll still struggle just for the heck of it!
If it's for our friends, we'll stand up to any opponent, no matter who they are!
The important thing isn't whether you win or lose.
It's to do everything you can,
the best way you can!
Someday, the world will end in despair,
and your dreams will collapse!
We won't give up! And that's why our dreams will never die!
Milk wants to make everyone's
dreams come true too-mil!
Together with the Powers
of Dreams and Hope...
O Five Lights, right here and now...
Pretty Cure Five Explosion!!
We did it!
This is... the power of hope?
Despariah-sama?!
Wherever have you been?
Despariah-sama?
Get me the Dream Collet.
Immediately, if not sooner!
I-I will, with utmost haste.
I cannot...
...hope to match that power
unless I become immortal.
A power that drives away despair...
Is that their source of hope...?
I can't believe Despariah
actually showed up.
What do we do now-mil?
Whatever happens, happens! Right, Coco?
That's right. No matter what happens,
I think we can get through it as long as we're together.
Well, at least some  of us
can be easygoing.
Still, I get the feeling things'll be fine.
We've been able to overcome
all the crises that came our way,
so this shouldn't be any different.
W-We'll be fine, right?
Yes!
Let's head home.
Oh yeah, there's still some of the cake
that Karen-san brought over.
What? Cake? Nobody ever told me~!
I've decided. I want to see Nozomi's smile for a little- no, a while longer.
So I'm going to live in
and treasure the present,
instead of thinking about
what may or may not happen later.
That's the Coco I know.
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming*
*happy coming*
yes!
I'm going to see the Principal.
I just want to have one
face-to-face conversation with her!
I'm coming too! Oh hey,
that woman looks like a big shot!
Well she is  the Principal,
of course she has a great dignity...
That's for sure! She opens her mouth up real big, laughs like "gahaha~",
sends Kowainaas to attack us...
That's so right! You'd expect nothing less from the Pri-
Wait, that's so wrong!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Seek Out the Principal's True Identity!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?