The 7 Wonders of the Academy, Special Feature:
The Mystery of the Principal!
Our Principal's identity is unknown.
Not a single student has seen her!
In order to remove
the veil from her true form,
Cinq Lumieres News is conducting
in-depth research.
Ah, Karen-san's in it.
I said I wanted to meet the Principal and have a real conversation,
as a representative of the students.
There are lots of school issues I'd like to consult about,
and I'd like to deliver people's thoughts to her directly.
I know how you feel.
Ah, Otaka-san!
Don't you think the Principal has her reasons?
Even so, I'd like to talk to her in person.
It sure is strange that
nobody's ever met her.
If there were any pictures or portraits of the Principal around,
they might give us a clue,
but there aren't any.
I wound up talking to the Vice-Principal about my showbiz work.
So what kind of person could the Principal be?
I wanna know, wanna know, wanna know!
What a mess.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Say, Hadenya-san?
What?
Have you ever seen
Despariah-sama's real face?
No, I haven't. She's far too important to be showing herself to any of us.
Wow, a person of your standing
doesn't know what she looks like?
Don't you think there's
some reason you haven't seen it?
My, Bunbee-san, do you have some sort of complaint about Despariah-sama?
N-No, of course not!
I was just curious, that's all.
Since you're her personal aide,
I suppose you've seen her, Kawarino?
In fact, I have not seen her face,
nor have I ever wanted to.
Well, people in charge tend to keep themselves hidden.
Is that how it is?
Yes, it makes them seem
more mysterious and dignified.
And those who do gaze upon them...
What happens to them?!
They receive a punishment!
Is this a punishment?
Seek Out the Principal's Identity!
Rin-chan sure is late.
I wonder what's keeping her.
Sorry, sorry!
What could've come between you and your lunch?
Ah, the brick wall by the old schoolhouse was falling apart, so I went to see it.
You shouldn't do that. It's dangerous!
You went all the way there
just to see that?
Huh? Y-Yeah, something like that...
Oh, right, that's where you made
all those memories with Count Rosen!
Y-You didn't have to remember that.
So you went to see it
because you were worried?
T-That's not it...
True, the old school building is getting on in years...
Unless it's fixed up soon, it won't last.
Student Council President!
Huh?
We had an unmatched shoe
show up in the Lost & Found.
Eh? Where was it?
Apparently, it was dropped in the rear garden.
Has someone lost a shoe?
Three days ago, some shoes and towels
went missing from the athletics clubs' area.
I was worried that they were being stolen.
Thank you. I'll report this to the teachers.
Thanks! Sorry to bother you!
But why would a lost shoe
show up in the rear garden?
I'll look into it later.
Huh? Coco-da-sensei...
I'll go with you.
Me too! I'm coming too!
So will I!
Hey now, we're not playing around.
This also went missing from the athletics clubrooms.
Huh? What's it doing here?
Be careful.
Vice-Principal?!
What're you up to?
Ah, well, the Principal told me
to investigate this area.
The Principal did?
Yes. The Principal heard that some missing items
had been found in the rear garden.
But the case has been solved;
this guy was behind it all.
So cute!
It was this puppy?
This dog picked up shoes and towels
from the clubrooms and carried them here.
So that's what happened?
I'll make sure he gets safely returned to his owner.
But how did this little dog get in here?
Who knows?
Wow! They've already started fixing the wall!
Our school always responds to things quickly.
This morning, the Principal told me that the dog
must've entered through this hole.
So she had the construction started right away.
She did?
Yes, I'd also noticed that
the bricks in this wall were aging,
but I'd never thought
they'd gotten this bad.
The Principal always picks up on the slightest of things.
Wow, the Principal is amazing!
Now I want to meet her even more.
Vice-Principal, have you met the Principal in person?
Of course I have.
You have? What kind of person is she?
A very wonderful person.
So yeah, he managed to find the dog's owner.
Thank goodness...
What's got you looking so down, Karen?
I really do... have to meet the Principal!
Huh? Why?
She's always been looking out for and caring about us students.
I just have to meet her
and thank her in person.
And...
And what?
I felt a bit annoyed that the Principal's never appeared before her students.
And I went and said all those things
in that interview...
I want to apologize properly.
I see.
Coco, have you met the Principal?
Just like you girls,
I've only met the Vice-Principal.
Eh? But you're a teacher!
All the communications
come through the Vice-Principal.
Why doesn't she show herself?
It certainly is strange-mil.
Back in the Palmier Kingdom, Coco-sama and Nuts-sama
were always meeting and talking to everyone-mil.
Karen, if you're that concerned, you should just go see her.
Sitting here thinking about it
won't solve anything.
You're right.
Okay, let's all go there tomorrow!
You think I can't handle it alone?
But we all want to meet the Principal...
All right, we're all gonna go see her!
It's decided!
This is so exciting-mil!
Calm down-nuts.
Why're they all tagging along?
Vice-Principal's Office
You enter the Principal's office
through the Vice-Principal's office-coco.
Is he not in?
Um, good morning...
Could the Vice-Principal be late?!
Not a chance. He's not you.
May I help you?
Principal's Office
Um, I'm the Student Council President, Minazuki.
I felt like I had to meet you
today, Principal.
Principal's Office
Sure, come on in.
Excuse us.
Princi...pal?
Yes, I am. So what brings you here?
We came to thank you for always thinking about us...
I wanted to apologize
for not understanding you,
and feeling dissatisfied.
Is that all?
Yes! We wanted to meet you,
so we came all the way here.
You wanted to meet me over such
trifling matters? What bothersome girls.
No...
Now that's just rude!
She's not...!
This person isn't our Principal!
Whatever makes you say that?
Our Principal does so much for the sake of the school.
There's no way she'd say that!
You're quite discerning. Indeed,
I am far greater than your Principal!
Huh?
Those who meddle in mysteries will receive their due rewards!
That includes you girls!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the power of hope...
...and the light of the future...
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
It's fast!
Look out-coco!
Rouge!
Right!
Aqua!
Are you okay-mil?
I'm fine.
Where's the Principal?
And for that matter,
where's the Vice-Principal?!
I suppose I could tell you,
if you were to give me the Dream Collet.
They're important people to you, aren't they?
How cowardly!
Now, hand over the Dream Collet!
Fat chance, lady!
Everyone...
You wound up like this because you fussed over
pointless things like
your school and your Principal!
Our school is important to us...
They care for all of us students...!
Our Principal and Vice-Principal are always warmly watching over us!
And if anyone tries to hurt them...
...we won't forgive them!
Do it now, Dream!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
And I was so close, too!
It's the Vice-Principal!
Sensei, please wake up!
This woman is... the Principal?
She looks just like Otaka-san.
Look at this brooch!
Wasn't Otaka-san wearing that?
Huh? You girls are...
We happened to be passing by,
and we heard a strange noise...
We came in and found that you two had collapsed.
Ow... Some woman I'd never seen before burst in here and attacked us...
Ah! Principal, are you all right?
Um, Principal, might you be...
...Otaka-san?
Uh, no, I assure you she's not-!
That's enough, Vice-Principal.
These girls came in here because they were worried about us.
There's nothing to hide from them now.
Don't do it, Otaka-san! If you go in there,
the Principal will get mad at you!
Why are you always so clueless!?
I'm sorry for hiding this from you.
Follow me.
Otaka-san, are you sure you should be
sitting in the Principal's chair?
Don't you get it? Otaka-san IS the Principal!
Eh?!
Wha!?
Really, you two?
But why would the Principal work at the lunch counter?
Before I became the Principal,
I had been teaching at this school
for a long time.
Back then, I was always around the students.
Giving advice and talking to them all day...
I enjoyed every day of it.
But when I became the Principal,
my chances to be around them dwindled.
I wanted to experience things
the same way everyone else did.
If anything was troubling or inconvenient,
I wanted to hear about it right away.
So, I played the part of "Otaka" to be around the students.
So that's how it was?
You were thinking of us to that extent...
That's great!
Hey, that means we ate
curry made by the Principal!
And spaghetti, too!
And yakisoba bread!
Not to mention the pizza toast!
Is food all you girls think about?!
Principal?
Yes?
I didn't know how you felt,
so I'm deeply sorry I acted dissatisfied
and came to see you unannounced.
But still, I'm very glad I got to meet you.
I'm also glad I met you.
I'm really happy to have an upstanding
Student Council President such as yourself.
And you've been blessed with such good friends...
It's truly incredible.
However...
In the future, I want to keep feeling
what everyone else is feeling.
So please keep all this a secret from the other students.
I'm counting on you.
Okay!
What's the matter, Masuko-san?
I've been investigating
the Principal's identity ever since then...
...but I haven't been able to discover it.
Do you girls know anything?
Well, it's a secret, but...
Nozomi!
You know something?
Masuko-san?
The Principal doesn't reveal herself,
but she always has us in her thoughts.
I think we should stop
looking into her identity.
Eh?
Of course, as Student Council President,
I'll continue to pass
people's opinions to her.
That's right.
I agree.
So do I!
Me three!
After all, we can always see-
Fine, I guess.
But what'll I do about the next issue?
Masuko-san, just the person I wanted to see!
I experimented with
some new sweetbread recipes.
Why not feature those in the newspaper?
Delicious!
That decides it: the next issue can be
about Otaka-san's new menu.
Yeah, this might work!
I'm counting on you!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Try as I might, I can't decide on
the "final farewell" lines.
Komachi-san, you're worried about your novel?
Leave it to me! I just heard
some great lines from Urara!
How would you say it?
"Bye bye!" "See you tomorrow!" "I'm leaving!"
Thanks, but I don't think those will work...
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Feelings Shared Between Komachi and Urara
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?!