To the boy who'd turned
his back on her, the girl said...
Writer's block. I just can't think of the line.
Urara-san!
Urara-san?
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Actually, I've got an audition
for a drama coming up.
That's awesome!
Love Squash
The thing is...
You want us to watch you practice?
Yes.
I will, I will!
If you don't mind...
Sure.
Please do.
Also, there is a script for the audition...
...but I have to come up with
the final lines myself.
Let's do some brainstorming!
Thanks, that'd be great.
So, what kind of story is it?
It's a love story, and the audition uses the farewell scene.
The farewell...?
A girl has to be separated from the boy she's always loved.
And in this farewell scene,
she has to get her feelings across to him.
What's on your mind?
O-Oh, nothing...
Feelings Shared Between Komachi and Urara
Things are NOT proceeding according to plan.
This department should have been dismantled by now,
as its objective should have been completed long ago.
That would have allowed me to take
the new position that I was promised...
Bunbee-san is predictably ineffective,
but I'm surprised that even Hadenya-san has failed to obtain the Dream Collet.
What do you think, Bloody-san?
This department will be
dismantled today, as you wish.
Oh, and what might you mean by that?
Just what I said.
All problems will be eliminated if I fulfill the objective, correct?
Yes, but only if  you fulfill the objective.
They've looked down on me
for far too long.
Please, stay well.
Sure thing.
But, I still...
Yeah.
I...
I can't say goodbye!
"I can't say goodbye"?
CUT! Cut, cut!
H-How was it?
Urara, your acting was dead on!
But Nuts was dead weight. No passion at all!
I disagree-mil. Nuts-sama was very good-mil.
Yes, at playing himself, anyway.
I'm tired-nuts.
But Urara was perfect,
and that's what really counts.
As long as you act normally and don't get nervous, you should be fine.
Um, what did you think of my final line?
Ah, that's right. You came up
with that yourself, didn't you?
Yes.
I thought it was a genuine, heartfelt line.
I think so too. What about you, Komachi?
Huh?
What did you think, Komachi-san?
I thought it was excellent.
It was very heartfelt, just like Rin said.
I... see.
The audition's coming up, so go ahead and pig out!
Eat a lot, and stay healthy!
Good luck.
I'm sure you'll pass.
Yes, there's not a doubt in my mind.
What's wrong?
Komachi-san, are you sure that final line was okay?
Huh?
Yes, I truly thought it was a great line.
Did you, really?
I'm sorry! I thought you'd be able to
come up with a great idea, Komachi-san.
I'm... going to practice some more!
Komachi-san!
Urara-san isn't with you?
She's nowhere to be found.
You think she already went home?
She might have.
The audition's right around the corner,
so must be busy practicing and preparing.
No, I'm sure Urara's still at school.
Huh?
Yeah, she's gotta be here!
So let's look for her.
We're all walking home with Urara! It's decided!
If you say so, it must be true.
Let's split up and look for her.
Okay.
All right, let's get going!
Could she be...?
U-ra-ra-san!
Komachi-san!
What're you doing here?
Good question.
But I knew you'd be here.
Komachi-san...
There was something I had to talk to you about.
I swear it's a coincidence,
but I've been worried about the same thing.
The heroine doesn't know how
to express her love to the hero...
...and the line's not coming to me.
So I couldn't come up with an answer to your problem, either.
All I can do now is...
It's still just an embarrassing rough draft,
but this is all I can show you for now!
You've re-written this manuscript over and over again.
But answers are still hard to come by, huh?
I'm sorry I wasn't able to help you at all.
No, you did.
Thanks to you, I feel like I've realized something important.
Before I knew it, this moment was upon us...
Please, stay well...
I will.
You have to leave, no matter what?
Sorry.
The path you're choosing is endlessly long.
Why do you have to take it?
Just as the sun rises in the sky,
this path is a path of hope!
Or something like that.
I guess we nibbled the scenery a little.
Chasing after one's dreams...
...sure can be hard, huh?
But...
I'm sure it's a very happy thing.
Someday, I'd like to act out
one of your books.
I was thinking the same thing!
I'd love for you to bring
one of my characters to life.
Feelings can still be expressed,
even if you don't put them into words!
Ah, I KNEW you'd be in here!
I couldn't have imagined you being anywhere else!
Huh? Komachi-san's with you?
And here comes someone who don't need words to understand feelings.
That's for sure!
Hey, what're you talking about?
Oh... Nothing...
You've put on an entertaining play for me.
Huh? You're...!
All this about feelings being conveyed is nothing but fantasy.
It's foolish to believe in
anyone other than yourself.
That's not true!
I know they can be conveyed!
Oh, is that so?
Then why don't you show me?
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
I can't find them anywhere!
Rin, Karen! Something's appeared-coco!
Behind you!
Above you!
Dream!
You're somewhat competent.
Time for the main performance!
Dream! Mint!
You guys!
Lemonade, Mint, you okay?
You won't be talking about worthless concepts like "unity of will" anymore.
They're in there-coco!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
Dream!
Lemonade! Mint!
Dream! Lemonade!
What could be the matter?
Have you become disheartened,
now that you're all alone?
If that's the case, shouldn't you be calling for your friends about now?
Under these circumstances,
I'm afraid you'll be unable to tell them just how much danger you're in.
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Anything you do is futile.
Your thoughts will never reach a single soul!
You're wrong about that!
Everyone...
Unite your thoughts with mine...
Mint!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
The effervescent power of a young girl's sparkle... Take this!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Didn't I tell you it's futile?!
Your thoughts and feelings will never reach any-
Yes, they will.
If your feelings are strong enough...
...they will definitely be understood!
Dream!
Lemonade, Mint!
It cannot be!
Why...?
Didn't we tell you?
Our thoughts for each other...
...will surely be transmitted.
Yes. And as you can see, they reached...
...right into here.
Why didn't I realize it?
You found an answer?
Yes.
Huh?
So then what happened?
In the end, I decided to scrap the last line,
and just stared into his eyes.
But thanks to that,
my feelings really shone through.
That's great.
And now for the real deal.
Do your best.
I will. Thank you very much.
No, I  should thank you
for giving me inspiration.
Komachi-san...
I think I'll follow your lead and
have my heroine say nothing at all.
I'm sure her feelings will reach her lover that way.
Oh, by the way, I've been wondering...
Are you basing your novel on something?
Huh?
N-No, it's complete and utter fiction!
Okay, so where'd you get the idea?
U-Umm...
I'm... not telling.
Hey, wait up!
Huh?
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Okay, question one: who hates losing the most?
That'd have to be Rin.
Nobody could be any more stubborn.
So close, yet so far.
The correct answer is:
Rin-chan and Karen-san!
Eh?! We're tied?
After all, you're so similar.
I suppose so.
But we're not always  competing.
We have a secret just between us.
Eh? C'mon, tell me too!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
A Secret Promise Between Rin and Karen
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?!