Do your thing.
Copying complete. I finished the fliers!
All righty!
Let's decorate the store nice and pretty for the Christmas sale!
It's decided!
Yeah!
Like this?
Or maybe this way...?
Urara, what're you doing?
Thinking about the lighting.
If even one light is misplaced,
it can totally change people's perceptions.
Oh, really?
The lighting director at my drama shoot taught me...
..."how to shine."
That's amazing, Urara.
It's like you're a real actress.
Thanks for the compliment!
A holy day, a holy night.
What sort of sky lies above you?
Once again, I wander in search of you
in the sea of stars this night.
Hey, Karen!
This is great, Komachi!
This introduction is going to be a poem for a loved one, right?
D-Don't read it. It's embarrassing.
There's no avoiding this "Christmas Spirit."
It's barely even December yet.
It can't be all  bad.
Look how much fun they're having.
You see, Christmas is...
...a REALLY important event in a young girl's life!
It's not all fun and games.
To us, it's serious business.
I-I see.
Yeah!
Oh no, I forgot to put up the flowers!
The flowers?
Well, if that's what you need...
...Karen-san and Rin will get them. It's decided!
You mean we  will...
...be in charge of flowers?
That's right, you two are on flower duty!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
QC: Force Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Timing, Translation.: Zalis
Not for Sale, Rent, Auction or Streaming
Pretty Cure!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Feels good, doesn't it?
How about this? How's it feel?
You're too weak. Put a little - no, a lot more power into it.
Fine, very well. I'll just kick the power UP a notch or two.
That's the spirit. Now I'm feeling it.
I bet you are.
Did you say something?
N-No, I didn't. But I was thinking...
I sure haven't seen Bloody-san around here lately.
Well, Bloody-san has unshakable faith in himself,
so he hardly ever comes here.
He just has to carry out his assignments.
Huh? But won't he get yelled at
if he doesn't show up?
By whom, Kawarino? Don't make me laugh.
Don't you think you should worry more about yourself?
By "you," do you mean me?
You're just hanging around here without any objectives.
You think a few shoulder massages will solve everything?
I-I...
Besides, wasn't your former department shut down?
Those who don't carry out their assignments will get the infamous "black paper."
That department was shut down by Kawarino. No black paper was involved.
Are you sure about that?
Rin and Karen's Secret Promise
I'm home!
Ah, welcome back, Rin. And none too soon.
Well, if it isn't Minazuki-san!
Good afternoon.
What's going on, Mom?
I have to go pick up Yuu and Ai.
I know it's short notice,
but can you watch the shop?
Huh? B-But, wai-
Please do.
Okay...
I'm sorry things are so hectic around here, Minazuki-san. But you can take it easy.
S-Sure.
Hold the fort while I'm gone, Rin.
Some things you just can't escape.
Sorry about this, Karen-san.
Since I'm stuck here,
can you take the flowers back yourself?
Isn't it hard to handle alone?
I'll help you out.
You don't have to. It'll be harder on you,
since you're not used to it.
Ah, but surely I can be of some  help.
I've watched you in action.
There's a difference between watching and doing.
I'll be fine.
Yes, this is Natsuki Flower Shop.
You have an order?
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes. Yes...
Excuse me.
U-Um...
Ah, yes, yes.
It seems like she's busy.
I think you're right.
Oh well.
Welcome!
I'm sorry you had to wait.
What are you looking for?
Thank you very much!
Do you think this will bloom soon?
You'll have to wait and see.
Since it's cold out,
you can grow it in your room.
I recommend planting that bulb in the garden, rather than potting it indoors.
Exposure to exterior frost will cause
the flowers to bloom more beautifully.
Is that so? Then we'll do that.
Thanks!
Thank you very much!
Excuse me... I'd like a flower...
Welcome. What can we get for you?
Um, well...
Come on in! Are you by yourself?
That's so great!
Is this a present for somebody?
Or are you on an errand for your mother?
You see...
It's my mom's birthday...
I see. I'll help you pick something out.
Really?
Yes, really.
Karen and Rin-san have been gone for awhile now...
Too long, if you ask me.
Do you think those two...
...got into a fight about flowers,
like they did last time?
Oh yeah, there was that...
That'd be awful-mil. Letting those two handle the flowers was a mistake-mil.
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm sure Rin-chan and Karen-san will be JUST fine.
Here. Raise it with care, okay?
'Kay! Bye bye!
Bye bye!
Karen-san...
When it comes to flowers,
you really know your stuff.
I'm still nowhere near your level.
You were a big help. Thanks a lot.
Don't mention it. I had fun, too.
You really love flowers, don't you?
Huh? Yeah, but don't you love them too?
Yes, but not the way a florist would.
You keep the customers' needs in mind at all times,
and handle their orders politely and kindly.
You wouldn't be able to do that if you didn't really love them.
I can definitely see you doing
this kind of work in the future.
W-Well, yeah, I like to do this...
...but I'm not sure about all this "career" and "future" stuff.
The more I think, the less I know.
I haven't exactly found something I truly want to do.
I see. So you haven't found it, huh?
I don't really know what I want to do, either.
Eh? But Karen-san, you get top grades, you're Student Council President...
And come on, those customers
walked away completely satisfied.
Why is the girl that can
do anything so worried?
True, I always give my best efforts
to the task at hand.
But I always find myself wondering whether it's something...
...I truly want to do in the future.
That's why I really envy people like Komachi and Urara...
...who have their own dreams and can dedicate everything to achieving them.
And when I saw those two earlier,
I couldn't help thinking:
"If only I had my own dreams, too."
We should be getting back to the others...
I...
...have plenty of fun playing futsal
or helping out here.
Every day is fulfilling in some way.
But still, watching Nozomi always gets me thinking.
She became Pretty Cure for Coco and Nuts' sake,
and brought us all together to fight.
It's all pretty amazing.
She gives her all at what she really wants to do.
I'm not confident that I can find something I want to do...
...like Nozomi did.
So maybe we're not so different.
Oh, I know! Let's make a promise.
A promise?
Once we find what we want to do in the future,
we'll each tell the other first.
Sounds good.
Now, let's see who finds their goal first...
"What you want to do?"
You'll never find anything like that.
Because you girls have no future.
Time sure has flown.
Let's hurry back. Everyone's waiting for us.
Yeah, and I bet they're tired of waiting by now.
Nightmare!
Those shoulder massages weren't helping anyone's mood, least of all mine.
What does that  mean?!
When push comes to shove,
I do whatever I have to do!
Something's appeared!
Yeah!
Rin!
Right!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
Compared to mine,
your powers may as well be
withered leaves falling from a branch!
Don't you two want to be more powerful?
What?!
I happened to overhear...
that you girls have "nothing."
As in no dreams or hopes for the future!
Isn't that what they call "despair"?
So I thought the power of despair would come in handy for you.
What're you talking about?!
We'll be sure to...
...find our dreams someday!
What, you actually believe  that?
Essentially, "dreams" are...
...nothing more than illusions!
You'll never find something like that,
no matter where you look!
You're wrong!
Nozomi, Urara...
...and Komachi...
...have all found theirs!
They're not  illusions!
Don't make me laugh!
No matter how hard you search,
they're just delusions that will never be real!
And despair lies just beyond any delusion!
Hopes and dreams are all meaningless!
Despair is the only absolute power!
What?
Dreams and hopes...
...aren't meaningless!
You're pretty strong today.
But you'd better be ready!
Hold it right there!
Karen...
...and Rin-san...
...will never give in to despair!
You guys!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
Are you all right-coco?!
Hang on-mil!
Rouge, Aqua, you okay?
Yes.
It's pointless to go on. You're all beat up.
I've learned lots of important things
from Rouge and Aqua.
What?
How to keep others in mind,
and communicate your feelings.
That's right! The tiara Rin-san made for the wedding ceremony...
...had all her heart and soul in it,
and it truly displayed her feelings!
When Milk was sick,
Karen always took care of her-mil.
Karen's hands were so very warm-mil.
Milk...
The power to sympathize with others,
and make them smile...
That's what dreams are!
That's what hope is!
To make everyone...
...smile.
PRETTY CURE!!
Is this the end for the
lovely ladies of Pretty Cure?
It's not the end. Not by a long shot!
What?!
Rouge! Aqua!
What they said...
...was right.
We've always done our best at anything that came our way.
And as long as someone appreciates that...
That alone makes us... really happy!
I'm not buying it!
The powerful flame of a young girl's pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
The rock-crushing power of a young girl's outpourings... Take this!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Aww, back to shoulder massages again...?
Okay, let's head home.
Yeah!
And here're the flowers.
They're all different varieties.
Cattleya and cyclamen, huh?
We thought two types of flowers would be better than one, right?
We managed to agree on something.
Yes, you could say that.
We wanted to make you all smile...
See, I told you so. Those two came up
with the perfect arrangement.
All right. And now, for some tea!
It's decided!
And as usual, Nozomi puts her mind
where her mouth is-mil...
Rin...
Yes?
I may have made some progress...
...towards realizing what I want to do.
Believe it or not, I have too.
And do you have the others to thank?
Maybe, maybe not...
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Komachi-san, have you finished your novel?
I just can't write the last scene...
Do you want me to look at it for you?!
Um, I'm just about finished.
Then why don't you ask Nuts for advice?
I can't do that! I just simply can't!
Huh?
W-Well, you know...
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Komachi's Resolve and Nuts' Future
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?!