What's wrong? You don't look so good.
Karen?
You've been like that
ever since you got here.
You aren't making progress on your novel?
No...
I'm not sure if I can help,
but if you want to talk,
you know I'm here for you.
Thank you. But it's more of a personal issue.
I know, why don't you talk to Nuts?
I'm sure he'd have some good advi-
I can't!
I can't... this is my own problem, so...
...I have to solve it myself.
Oh.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Timing, QC: Force Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Translation, etc.: Zalis
Not for Sale, Rent, Auction or Streaming
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
That's so awesome!
You read ALL of these in one day?
Nuts-sama is a diligent student-mil.
I want to learn as much as I can while I have the chance.
I'm sure it'll come in handy
once the Palmier Kingdom is restored.
You're the greatest-mil!
I guess so. I'd better hit the books too.
Speaking of books, did you finish that novel you were writing?
Huh? Ah, well... not yet.
I can't wait to read it!
It was a love story, wasn't it?
W-Well, I wouldn't be TOO SURE about that!
It's just, I kind of... hit a dead end.
Then let me break down that wall for you!
I'll give you tons of advice!
So, what're you stuck on?
I have to wonder if any story
Nozomi wrote would be intelligible-mil.
What're you getting at?!
Really, she would've already breezed through anything you could've advised her on.
Not you too, Rin-chan...
Though I'm still curious:
is your novel based on anything?
T-There couldn't possibly be! It's just
a fictional story, no relation to anything real.
I'd better just head home. That next section isn't going to write itself, you know.
Komachi's Resolve and Nuts' Future
Now what's got you looking so down?
Despariah-sama has finally
sent one of these  to me.
Whatever should I do?
Black paper?
Cheer up. All you need is
a fresh perspective.
Anyone who has that will surely be
able to bring Pretty Cure down,
and obtain the Dream Collet, right?
Oh, hearing those words from you
has truly saved me!
Well, I was  rather conflicted about giving this to you.
What say you, Hadenya-san?
I-It's for me? You must be joking.
I may look funny, but I detest jokes.
Hadenya-san, you've forgotten something!
I don't believe a word you say.
I'll take this up with
Despariah-sama directly.
My words and Despariah-sama's words
are one and the same.
Meaning, that this is Despariah-sama's will.
Go ahead, take it.
I don't need that junk!
Once I get serious,
those little girls won't stand a chance!
Just you wait! I'll be right back,
Dream Collet in hand!
Bunbee!!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Just yelling your name for the heck of it!
And I was just giving a response...
Now, how can I get some grand results to match that grand exit?
Huh? "Go Go"? That's the strangest pigeon call I've ever heard...
It looks like I've just caught a break!
How're things going?
Karen?
At first, ideas just kept coming to me.
So many of my feelings were taking shape that I couldn't contain them all.
But as I proceeded to write them down...
...I found that I couldn't.
Komachi?
I want to do anything I can to make his dream come true.
If it's for his sake...
"His"?
Ah, um, I'm talking about the story...
But as soon as his dream comes true,
that person will go somewhere far away.
A faraway place, where I can't reach him.
Yes, I knew that from the very beginning.
But I don't know what I can do...
what I should do...
If the last scene never arrived,
I'd be fine with that.
I don't know how the last scene will turn out,
but I get the feeling that it's all up to you.
If you change, the last scene
will change too.
In the story, of course.
Didn't I say...
...that I'd always be willing to give her advice?
Komachi knows that better than anyone.
But if she doesn't come to me,
there's nothing I can do.
And this  is why I'm always saying you're cold-hearted!
What?
This is inexcusable-mil!
I'm sure there's a reason
Komachi can't say anything.
It's times like this when you have to go and give her advice!
Doing that when nobody
asks you to is called being nosy.
Interrogating people about their problems only makes them worse.
That's right-mil.
Still, Komachi's been totally bummed out these days.
Yeah, she has.
That's for sure. And the outlook
for change doesn't look good, either.
That's why I'm worried. Nuts, don't you think
we should do something for her?
Calm down, you guys. It's not like I don't know how you all feel,
but I think we'll have to keep
watching over Komachi for now.
I agree with that.
Karen-san?
I'm sure Komachi can sense what you're feeling.
But...
She'll be fine.
I'm sure she'll find her own solution to this issue.
They're all worried about you.
I'll do whatever I can,
if there's anything I can do.
T-Thank you. But this time, I have to...
I see. Well, if you change
your mind, let me know.
I can always lend an ear.
Why?
Why are you being so nice to me, Nuts-san?
"Why"?
You're always praising or consoling me.
But I can't return the favor.
I don't deserve to be treated so kindly by you.
I'm not as strong or kind as you think I am.
Nuts-san?
I can't do anything on my own.
I need others' help...
...to make my dreams come true.
So I try to make an effort
to do the things I can  do.
And you're always putting your full effort
into realizing your dreams.
I respect how you're struggling like mad right now.
That's the kind of person I like.
The key is not to regret anything.
Why...?
Karen's always saying,
"Komachi taught me that."
Don't worry. Everyone is watching over you, supporting you.
They all... Karen...?
I only ever thought about myself!
I was always afraid...
I thought that the moment I found the courage to speak up,
everything that had come before, as well as the future...
...would crumble away in an instant.
I thought I'd lose everything!
I always feared that!
I'm afraid to face the future, too.
But...
Komachi, your future belongs to you.
I'm sure you'll find a final scene
that works for you.
Yeah...
I won't tell you to act happy.
Just try to relax a bit.
Basically, what I mean is...
...it's okay to be more carefree,
like Nozomi.
Huh? What? What was that?!?
Okay.
So sorry to spoil the mood, you two.
Whatever future you have,
I'll be happy to crush it.
You're...!
Nightmare!
My luck's almost frighteningly good today.
And I don't feel like losing!
Something's appeared-coco!
I really am lucky today.
I just happened to come across
a prince of the Palmier Kingdom...
...right after getting my hands on
this little fellow!
A Pinky!
Golem...
This kills two birds with one stone.
What're you doing?! This thing's mine!
Nuts-san!
I just burned a lot of energy there.
If only I could've gotten
the Dream Collet at the same time!
Let's try this "taking" thing again.
Hold it!!
Nuts-sama!
Komachi, are you all right?
Yes.
A wild Nightmare appears!
Don't treat people like monsters!
Though I guess I am  kind of monstrous...
But that doesn't matter!
Whether there's one or five of you...
I, Hadenya, will knock you all down!
Let's...
...do this!
Today, I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
I'm no fledgling chick like you girls, so don't-
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Listen to people until they finish their boastful ranting!
Anyone who can't do what they're told
is in for some punishment!
The Pinky's...!
Conflicted about fighting a Pinky, are we?
We have to break that mask!
This is really starting to tick me off!
Go, Kowainaa!
So that's its fighting style?
Lemonade! Rouge!
Thanks...
Here it comes again!
This is getting ridiculous!
Ah, nobody's going anywhere,
not until you give me the Dream Collet!
Nuts-san!
Run for it! I'll hold her off!
No good will come of protecting those losers!
It's because of them that the
Palmier Kingdom was destroyed!
You're all headed for the same destiny: failure!
It wasn't Nuts-sama's fault-mil!
Nuts was tricked-coco! Quit raking him
over the coals for it-coco!
Stop making Nuts relive those painful memories!
There's no time for petty quibbles!
Mint!
Aqua!
There's nothing else I can do!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Nice try.
It's impossible for me.
I can't protect Nuts-san...
Am I useless?
I can't do anything for him...
Mint...
Knock off the nice girl act already.
You're doing all this,
just for their worthless dreams?
It's not just for Nuts and Coco!
Reviving the Palmier Kingdom is a dream for all of us!
We all promised to make that dream come true!
Plus, I decided that it was my dream, too!
That's why it's for my sake!
I've got no time to listen to
your mindless drivel!
As of today, you girls are finished!
Yes, this is for all our sakes.
And we won't regret it, will we?
This is the end!!
Dream!
I decided!
That's why it's for my sake!
And we won't regret it, will we?
Lemonade!
I won't let you!
Where did you have that much
power stored away?
Lemonade, hurry up!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Today... I'm getting that Dream Collet today...
We'd never let a fiend like you
have the Dream Collet!
Nuts-san, hold on tight to it!
Don't ever let it go!
Yes...
It's time to live up to the expectations of everyone I know.
Whatever future lies in store, I can take it!
Yes, this is for me!
What do you mean, "future"?
What do you mean, "dreams"?
I'll blow them all away!!
Mint!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Stop kidding yourselves!
We won't let your company have its way anymore!
Just you wait!
No more...
Komachi, are things going any better?
You don't have any paper out today.
No, I decided to shelve it for now.
There're lots of books to process today.
I see.
But I'll be fine. Don't worry.
I'll be sure to find...
...a last scene that suits me.
All right.
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Milk's been asking around...
What do you think an ideal caregiver is like?
Kind, athletic, smart...
Yeah, yeah.
Eats, sleeps, and laughs a whole bunch!
Yeah...
And then, she does ALL your homework,
and takes you out to
all kinds of fun places!
I don't think caregivers do that.
They don't?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
What Kind of Person is a Caregiver?
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?