I overslept-mil!!
Good morning-miaiewuh!
Good morning-coco.
Good morning-nuts.
I'm so sorry-mil!
I'll get things ready right away,
so please wait a moment-mil!
We already had breakfast-coco.
It's time to open the store.
And I need to get to school.
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama...
...can do everything themselves,
without Milk's help-mil.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Timing, QC: Force Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Translation, etc.: Zalis
Not for Sale, Rent, Auction or Streaming
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
Has there still  been no word from her?
Uhh, no, she hasn't contacted us.
How troublesome.
You're telling me.
Where the heck did she go?!
Ah, do you think Hadenya-san's planning to quit?
I won't allow such an irresponsible act!
I'll keep that in mind.
I'm hoping that she can at least be useful at the very end.
With a mask?
I've had about enough of this.
It's over for you, Pretty Cure!
What Kind of Person is a Caregiver?
What're you doing out here?
It's dangerous to be alone outside.
Why don't you come back to Natts House with me?
No-mil.
Milk?
Milk?!
Milk is... Milk isn't needed anymore-mil!
So that's what happened.
Milk has always admired
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama-mil.
That's why I wanted stay
with them as their caregiver
and be useful to them-mil.
I see.
But even if Milk doesn't take care of them...
...it seems like Coco-sama and Nuts-sama will be fine-mil.
Milk doesn't know what she should do-mil!
A caregiver, huh?
Washio-san's always taking care of me while I'm on the job.
He never fails to keep
my best interests in mind.
So is that what a caregiver is to you-mil?
I guess so.
And I really do appreciate him.
But...
I'm still not too sure what a caregiver is.
Even if they're not with you all the time,
they're always there...
to scold you or praise you during the really important moments.
That's how I think they should be.
A caregiver?
Yes-mil. They scold you, praise you...
...and always have the
right words for you-mil.
Do you mean...?
Someone like you-mil!
Rin, you're always blunt about anything you say-mil.
Something about the description doesn't sit well with me.
But you've got the wrong person.
Why is that-mil?
You're always helping at the store,
taking care of your siblings,
saying exactly what's on your mind,
and looking out for everyone-mil.
That's technically true,
but it's not the right answer.
There's somebody else who's as multi-talented as you?
Yeah.
No, she's a MAJOR screwup.
A screwup-mil?
Does she have any talents to make up for that?
Not a one. Her mind is like a sieve,
she's got zero coordination,
and she's always misplacing things.
Though she does  have a knack for tripping over nothing.
She sounds completely incompetent-mil.
Yeah, she's completely incompetent.
But she's always willing to get mad, cry,
smile, and worry for everyone's sake.
That's just how amazing she is.
I'm thankful to have her around.
So I consider myself to be in her care.
But it's hard to put into words.
Maybe Komachi-san can
explain it better than I can.
Nuts, have you seen Milk?
Don't tell me she's not here...
That's a difficult question. But...
But what?
I think it's important that they...
...believe from the bottom of their hearts in what they do and what they are.
Milk certainly feels that
she wants to be useful-mil.
But I don't know what I should do-mil.
That's right. It can be hard to turn your thoughts into action.
But there is somebody who can do that with ease.
She's a very strong-willed person.
Someone that incredible exists-mil?!
Yes.
And I know who that is-mil!
And that's why you've come to me?
Komachi mentioned a strong-willed person,
and I knew it HAD to be you-mil!
You know, I don't think I'm the one
that Komachi had in mind.
If it's not you, then who is  it-mil?
It seemed like Urara and Rin were also thinking of someone in particular-mil.
Milk is envious of this one person...
...that everybody needs-mil.
Yes, when I look at her,
I feel envious, too.
You do too-mil?
No matter what adversity she faces,
she never loses her radiance.
She's the kind of girl who
never forgets to believe.
Never forgets to believe-mil?
Milk wants to meet that person-mil!
You already know her very well.
It's Nozomi.
Time to eat!
You're not eating, Milk?
I'm not hungry-mil.
Oh, really?
So good...
Nozomi, I don't think you're all that special-mil.
There has got  to be some mistake-mil!
I don't really know what you're saying...
...but I bet it's something bad about me!
Then let me ask you-mil!
What's your ideal caregiver like-mil?
Hmm, let's see...
Someone who eats a lot, plays a lot,
sleeps a lot, is always healthy...
...and is full of happiness!
That's not an answer-mil.
Milk wants to be useful to
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama-mil!
You love Coco and Nuts, don't you?
Of course-mil!
Isn't that enough?
You've lost me-mil.
I never should've asked you
in the first place-mil.
What was that?!
Oh boy, another day, another fight.
By the way, where are
Coco-san and Nuts-san?
It doesn't seem like they're around here.
I saw them leaving Natts House as I was heading towards it.
They seemed to be in a rush.
Milk, did you actually tell  Coco and Nuts
that you were going out?
You left without saying anything?!
Did you find her?
No. Did you?
It's going to be dark soon.
Where could Milk have gone?
Were you looking for something?
Nightmare!
Playtime is now over.
Hand over the Dream Collet, on the double!
You really think we will?!
Coco! Nuts!
Are you all right-mil?
You all...!
Nightmare!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future...
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cure...!
Milk! I'm so glad you're okay-coco!
Were you looking for Milk-mil?
We sure were-coco!
You had us worried-nuts!
I'm not just useless,
I even make them worried-mil...
Didn't I tell you that playtime is over?!
Was she  the one you boys were looking for?
Why would you even bother?
You don't need someone like her.
That's not...
...true-nuts!
Either way, since you've been out wandering around...
...I've been able to get the Dream Collet.
Thank you so much!
It's Milk's fault...
Milk really is a failure as a caregiver-mil!
Just let me handle things from here.
I'll take REAL good care of you!
Thanks, but...
...no thanks!
Coco and Nuts' caregiver...
...can only be Milk!
Caregiving is a job where
you can just do whatever!
Someone like you could never understand...
...Milk's feelings!
I-I'm not through yet.
You mustn't push yourself.
Kawarino?
I'm here to deliver something
you'd forgotten, Hadenya-san.
Didn't I say I didn't need it?!
Yes, but I believe you very much do  need it.
I don't want it!
Just watch, I can win against Pretty Cure
without something like that!
Hadenya-san?
I'm telling you, I don't need it!
I can still beat them!
I thought you were
wise enough to understand...
...that to defeat Pretty Cure, this  is a necessary item!
He forced the mask onto her-mil!
Isn't she your ally-coco?
Ally? I've neither seen
nor heard of such a thing.
Get the job done, will you?
I won't give it up-mil!
Milk!
I won't hand over the Dream Collet-mil!
That's a noble thing to say,
for the sake of a nonexistent kingdom.
And once again, you two have failed to protect the Dream Collet.
Truly pathetic.
Useless people such as yourselves...
...are truly unnecessary, aren't you?
Be quiet-mil.
What's this? Did you say something?
I said to be quiet-mil!
Oh?
Milk!
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama are absolutely essential to the Palmier Kingdom-mil!
But they're no longer "essential,"
now that the kingdom's been destroyed.
The Palmier Kingdom WILL rise again-mil!
And when it does, Milk will definitely serve Coco-sama and Nuts-sama-mil!
Milk!
Your kingdom will never be revived.
Why, you ask?
Because I'll be taking the Dream Collet!
Milk!
There's no use running away!
I'll never let you have it-mil!
Because that's Milk's duty-mil!
To Milk, Coco and Nuts...
...are very precious!
She's taken very... good care of them!
We won't forgive you for
mocking Milk's feelings!
We all love Milk!
She's there by our side when it matters the most...
She gets mad for all our sakes...
She's very strong-willed...
She never forgets to believe...
Milk's the best caregiver ever,
and for her sake, we'll never let you
have the Dream Collet!
You girls...
Milk will  be Coco-sama and Nuts-sama's caregiver-mil!
Together with the powers of Dreams and Hope...
O Five Lights, right here and now...
Pretty Cure Five Explosion!!
How could things have
degenerated this much?
Milk sure is enjoying herself.
It's like she's been totally refreshed.
Her usual smile has returned.
Are you all right now, Milk?
My problems are behind me-mil!
That's great-coco!
Drop it-mil!
Coco-sama, you mustn't eat
any more cream puffs today-mil!
Milk knows all-mil! She told  you to eat a proper breakfast,
but you've eaten nothing but cream puffs-mil!
And then there's you, Nuts-sama!
Yesterday, you were so engrossed in your book
that you stayed up all night-mil!
I know  you couldn't have read that far
without an all-nighter-mil!
Milk sees right through you-mil!
The jig is up-coco...
For quite a while now,
Milk has had plenty of things...
...she's wanted to say-mil!
First off, Coco-sama, you can't always...
Looks like the lecturing has started.
If she keeps up this level of work,
Milk will be an excellent caregiver someday.
I can't wait!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
Merry Christmas!
The Pinky collecting is coming along fine,
and our dreams are about to come true.
Nozomi?
But once they do, Coco and Nuts will
go back to the Palmier Kingdom, right?
I suppose so. They are  princes and stuff.
I'd never even thought about that.
How much longer can we stay together?
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Nozomi and Coco's Christmas Vows
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?