Caught it!
You've done it!
Wow!
Now we've collected 54 Pinkies.
Yeah. There's just one more out there.
Huh?
This place was...
It's where Miku-san got married.
Miku-san sure looked pretty, didn't she?
Yeah.
That aside, this sure is one big tree.
I bet it looks so beautiful
when they light it up at night.
I bet you're right!
It's snowing! All right!
Why're you so happy about that-mil?
Because tomorrow's Christmas Eve.
If it keeps snowing,
we'll have a white Christmas!
The weather forecast calls for accumulation.
Really?!
Oh yeah! White Christmas, here we come!
Just one more Pinky and we'll have all 55-nuts.
We'll only be in this world a little while longer-coco!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Timing, QC: Force_Gaia Encode: K.o.R  Translation, etc.: Zalis
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Our dreams are about to come true.
I bet you're excited, Coco.
Once the kingdom is restored,
I wonder who'll become king: Coco-sama or Nuts-sama-mil?
The previous king retired
before Nightmare appeared-mil.
So a new king has to be chosen-mil!
I see. Kings are normally succeeded by princes...
So which prince will it be?
The king should be
someone who can listen to
the subjects' problems
and give good advice-nuts.
The king has to be strong-willed-coco.
Someone like you, Nuts, who doesn't
lose his cool in front of anybody-coco!
Someone who's beloved by the whole kingdom shouldn't be talking such nonsense-nuts!
Any way I see it,
you're the next in line-nuts!
You're always working behind the scenes for the good of the kingdom.
Everybody knows that-coco!
Everybody loves you more, Nuts-coco!
I'll be happy no matter which one of you becomes king-mil!
The king is elected
by everyone in the kingdom-mil.
A king, huh? That's so awesome!
Kings are pretty important, aren't they?
They're not just "pretty" important,
they're the most  important!
Be sure to come visit us,
even after you've become king.
That's impossible-nuts-
We might not be able to come
all that often-coco.
Really? Don't kings get vacations, too?
Didn't you say you went on trips all the time?
It's fine to do that as a prince,
but not so much when you're King-nuts.
Kings and princes are always needed in their countries.
Coco-sama and Nuts-sama serve as
moral support for their subjects-mil.
I suppose so.
I guess we'll really have to say goodbye.
I always knew that, but it's still sad.
But they'll be happiest living with
their own people in their homeland.
L-Let's not be hasty-coco!
The Kingdom still hasn't been revived-coco.
We've almost got all the Pinkies gathered.
H-Hold on!
Um, well... Once our dreams come true,
does that mean we won't see
Coco and the others anymore?
Nozomi and Coco's Christmas Vows
Once the Palmier Kingdom gets restored,
we have to say goodbye to you guys?
Nozomi?
That makes sense. Going back home
is the natural thing to do.
That's what we've been working so hard for.
Your tea has been cooled.
Hadenya-san has met with an unfortunate end.
This department expected so much from her,
but she disappointed us, Bloody-san.
Why did you force Hadenya to put that mask on?
We never would've used
something like that in the old days.
Nightmare hasn't been the same ever since you become Despariah's personal aide.
Just what is your angle
in all of this, Kawarino?
You think I would have an objective
beyond toiling for Despariah-sama's sake?
All I can say is, good luck, Bloody-san...
I'll get results, with my own methods.
What, you were still here, Bunbee-san?
W-What do you mean, "still"?
If you think there's still a place for those...
...who can't be useful to Despariah-sama,
you've got another think coming.
Then what am I supposed to do?
What're you looking at?!
Don't act like it's someone else's problem!
Any one of you could be next!
You'll see!
Talking to people who're in despair
is like talking to a wall.
Good luck, me...
Welcome!
Nozomi...
Rin-chan, this arrived for you.
Thanks a bunch!
Is Nozomi-san all right?
She's really forcing herself to act cheerful.
She's been jolted by a pretty big shock.
After working so hard
to realize everyone's dreams,
she has to confront
what'll happen afterward.
We'll all be sad to part with Coco, Nuts, and Milk...
...but Nozomi will be hit the hardest.
That's right.
Nozomi-san's and Coco's meeting was the beginning of everything.
I understand Nozomi's feelings-mil.
But Coco-sama and Nuts-sama
are needed in the kingdom-mil.
And I think Nozomi-san understands that very well.
Thanks a bunch!
Okay, is this good enough?
Yeah.
You think Nozomi's okay?
She looked pretty shocked.
Yeah, but I think she's fine.
Nozomi's got a strong spirit.
And you?
Are you okay with separating from Nozomi?
On cake: "Thank you"
Amazing!
What's this for?
The three of us made
this Christmas cake-coco.
It's a present to all of you-coco!
We hadn't expressed our thanks,
so this is a token of gratitude-nuts.
You all must eat this delicious cake.
It'll taste even better-mil!
Sure thing! And I've got the drinks.
Everything's ready!
Let's have a toast.
Okay! Here I go!
Nozomi?
Huh? Um, well, let's see...
Here's to the Pinky hunt! Merry Christmas!
Cheers!
Cheers.
Cheers-nuts!       Cheers-coco!       Cheers-mil!
Whoa, it's really good!
Milk did these decorations-mil.
They're lovely.
Thank you-mil!
Nozomi, what do you think-coco?
You're always the first to finish eating...
It doesn't taste good to you-mil?
No, it's delicious.
But for some reason, I can't get
the cake down my throat too well...
It's strange...
When I saw the words "thank you", I couldn't help thinking...
How much longer can we stay here,
like this, with Coco and the others...
This is the last time.
Nightmare!
Enjoying the party, are we?
I'd like to invite you to the Nightmare Banquet!
Everybody get outside-nuts!
Coco! Nuts! Milk!
Now, let's begin the final feast,
legendary warriors Pretty Cure!
Okay girls, let's go.
Yeah.
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Lemonade!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future...
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
I know that in our previous fights,
you five formed an unrivaled team.
However, I've found your crippling weakness!
If I take out the central supporting pillar,
the rest of you will collapse!
Dream!
Girls-!
This is no time to be worrying about your teammates.
It's like you're just going through the motions.
You can't defeat me like that!
Yes we can! If we all combine our powers, we'll find a way!
There is hesitation in your heart.
"What will happen after this?"
"Is this the right thing to do?"
Your dream is at odds with itself.
No, it's not!
Your movements are hesitant.
You've discovered that fulfilling your dreams
means separation from
the one you hold dear.
Wouldn't you have been better off not
knowing, and not fulfilling your dream?
That's not what I think!
You don't want to lose your dream
or your beloved.
You're worried, lost,
tired of thinking,
and likely to reject everything.
That's what it means to despair!
Dream!!
Farewell to you.
Of course we'd hesitate!
What's so wrong with standing still?
We might not find the answer right away, but...
...we're always here to back Dream up!
Everyone...
You're too late. Soon,
she won't even have the strength to stand.
Dream won't give up-nuts!
She won't lose to Nightmare-mil!
Dream!!
Coco?
Thanks, you guys. It's true; I was  lost.
But...
You guys ruined Coco's precious country,
and I won't lose to you!
I promised Coco that I'd get
the Palmier Kingdom restored.
So I believe that's the best thing I can do for him!
Dream!
I want to make Coco's dreams come true.
And no matter what happens,
that's what I'll do!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Despariah-sama, I have a report.
Only one Pinky has yet to be gathered.
It is only a matter of time before the Dream Collet becomes usable.
Good work today.
See you tomorrow!
It's late, so we'll drive you all home.
Good night.
Yeah. Bye-bye.
Nozomi!
Ah, well...
Coco, walk Nozomi home.
Here.
Ah, t-thanks.
Get going.
Go along with him, Nozomi.
It's cold, so wear this.
Nuts...
Shall we go?
Yeah.
Nobody else has been down this path.
And a one, two-
Once the snow melts, these footprints will disappear, won't they?
Question: when snow melts, what gets left behind?
What is it?
The answer is: memories.
I won't forget walking with you like this.
Even when the snow is gone.
Not ever.
Yeah. I won't forget, either.
That's right. This road leads to...
Isn't it gorgeous?
Yeah.
Say, do they decorate trees in the Palmier Kingdom, too?
I bet it's fun to get together
with everyone and deck the halls!
I imagine so. I'll have to try it; I'm sure they'd all like it.
N-Nozomi?
Huh? Oh no! Why am I crying?
I'm... happy, you know.
I want to fulfill your dream.
We've all worked towards that goal,
and it's just about to happen...
I'm really, I'm really... happy...
The Palmier Kingdom, where I was born,
is truly an incredible place.
Nuts and all the friends I loved were there, and I was happy.
However, I lost everything,
and wound up all alone.
I was without dreams, without hope...
It was a real nightmare.
Nozomi, you were the one who saved me
when I was in that state.
Your smile gave me
the courage to try again.
I did...?
Since then,
your smile has always been
shining on inside of me, along with
your strong affection for your friends,
and your great courage that
sees your dreams through.
Nozomi, thank you so much.
I was able to make it this far
because of you.
I... actually...
The truth is, I want you to stay here forever!
I feel the same way.
I want to stay with you forever.
But, you have to go home...
The people of the Palmier Kingdom need you...
Nuts and I are princes.
And princes of the Palmier Kingdom have to work their hardest for the people's sake.
Someday, we'll have to go our separate ways.
That's why I want to treasure the time we have together now, Nozomi.
Yeah!
I also love this time
we have together, Coco.
Thank you.
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
At last, there's only one Pinky left
before we have all 55!
Hey, isn't that thing on your head a Pinky?!
Woah, we've caught them all!
This is no time to celebrate!
Nightmare's here!
I won't give it up.
I'll never let you guys have it!
No! We mustn't fall for their trap!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Kawarino's Heartless Scheme!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?