Doing New Year's shrine visits in a group is kind of... refreshing.
That's for sure.
It's so great that we can all do this together.
I agree.
I'm sure...
I'm sure it'll be a great year.
So, doing shrine visits are all about wishes for the new year-mil.
That's right. Milk, did you wish for anything?
Milk wants the Palmier Kingdom to be resurrected as soon as possible-mil.
That's what I wished for!
What about you, Nozomi?
Oh, you know  I wished for the same thing.
It's everyone's dream, after all.
Oh, really-mil? The Nozomi I  know would've made a wish like
"I wanna eat a TON of fried eggs"
or something like that-mil.
Oh, come on, I totally know you wished you could eat a bunch of chocolates, Milk.
That's not true-mil!
You can't handle the truth!
Rin, what did you wish for?
M-Me?
You were the first one I was planning to tell, Karen-san.
The truth is, I...
Milk's being mean to me!
Nozomi's being mean to me-mil!
Just shut up already.
It looks we're in for another "busy" year.
We sure are.
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Translated & Timed by Zalis    Encode: K.o.R
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Hadenya-san put on that black mask,
and isn't around anymore...
And Bloody-san isn't coming back, either.
First one, then another... we're losing personnel left and right here.
It won't be long before this department is completely unstaffed!
So my turn has to be coming up...
What say you, voiceless peanut gallery?
Now is the time for decisive action!
"Letter of Resignation"
Should I submit one of these, or...?!
Or should I just run away?
What's the right course of action?!
Just once, I wish they'd answer me...
May I see this a moment?
Go ahead... Wha-?
K-K-K-K-Kawarino-san!?
Hmm, does this letter of resignation mean...
Well you see, this is...
...that you're thinking of quitting Nightmare?
Ah, yeah, well, actually...
I thought I'd go on a trip to find myself.
Bunbee-san?
Y-Yes?
Aren't you making some form of mistake here?
Huh?
The option of leaving Nightmare...
...is no longer available to you.
W-Why am I on the roof?!?
If you aren't going to work for Despariah-sama's sake,
your existence has no value.
I guess this is it, I'm pretty screwed.
Game over, man, game over!
Those who are not useful to Despariah-sama should vanish immediately.
I-Is this what you call "aggressive downsizing"?
Are you trying to criticize me?
Y-Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
You've just been using us!
We're not your tools!
Ah, sorry-!
I deeply  regret that you feel that way.
This is the worst exit interview ever!!
In the end, he wasn't able to be of any use at all.
Kawarino's Heartless Scheme!
We've almost got all 55 Pinkies.
There's just one more to go.
Gotta catch 'em all!
Yeah!
We're pretty much
Pinky Masters at this point.
Even so, finding the last Pinky...
...might not be that simple.
But we can't stop until
we find that last Pinky.
If we all work together,
we're sure to find it-mil.
Right.
All righty! No matter how hard it is,
I'll find it or die trying!
It's decided!
But still, our dreams won't come true that easily...
That's right. It's not like it'll be resting on top of our heads.
I can't believe something like that would happen.
Neither can I.
What? What is it?
There it is!
Look up!
Hurry and catch it-coco!
Caught it!
This is  the last one, right?
Yes-mil.
We really...
...gathered...
...them all...
...perfectly, didn't we?
This really and truly is all of them-mil!
We caught 'em all!
Our dreams will come true-coco!
The Palmier Kingdom will be restored-nuts!
Isn't this great?
Sure is.
And it didn't even take all that long.
Congratulations.
So you've gathered all of them, have you?
I should be grateful.
Thank you so much for doing all this for me.
Nightmare!
Girls...
Lock'n'load!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the power of hope...
...and the light of the future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
And now, to make you
turn over the final Pinky.
We won't give them up!
We worked too hard to collect them!
Each and every last one of the Pinkies
belongs in our hands.
There's meaning to our having them.
You guys-!
Leave this to us.
Dream, protect the last Pinky with everything you have.
Let's go!
Rouge!
You take care of that Pinky!
What's wrong? Your movements have been altered.
It seems that your attempt to protect
the final Pinky has disrupted your rhythm.
I-It has not!
Humans fear the loss of
the things they've obtained.
Don't they?
I'm not...
I'm not afraid!
Dream!
Look at the sky, and you will see
the truth of my words.
Your "protect at all costs" instincts have cost you dearly.
Behold! Now, the last Pinky
is as good as mine.
Let's all go and help Dream!
Yes!
Thanks, you guys!
I had already expected
something of this nature.
Hear this: the real fight begins now!
Retreat is not an option for me today!
Dream!
What?
Honestly, this is most vexing...
Dream!
Just when everyone's dreams were about to come true...!
Now, it's time to put an end to all of this
by giving me the Dream Collet
and that Pinky.
We won't do it.
Huh?
Everybody's desires and hard work
has brought us this far.
Dream...
That's why... That's why,
no matter what happens...
...we won't hand over the Collet OR the Pinky!
That's right-mil!
Our dream... is right before our eyes-mil!
Along with the powers of dreams and hope...
Five lights, right here and now!
Pretty Cure... Five Explosion!!
I'll get you next time,
Pretty Cure! Next time...
You're still thinking
there'll be  a "next time"?
Surely you had one of those black masks -
why didn't you use it?
I believe you could've won, had you used it.
I'll never use this piece of junk!
I never wanted to say something like this
to a former superior, but...
Bloody-san, don't you think your judgment isn't what it used to be?
Are you saying you find fault
with my methods?!
I didn't exactly say that. However...
...it's just that the times have changed.
The old ways can't prevail forever.
Kawarino,
Nightmare's been going downhill ever since you arrived.
You only prioritize your own objectives,
and never stop to think,
"Is this good for the company?"
The present Nightmare has no unity at all!
But isn't achieving our goals all that matters in the end?
Despariah-sama is also in agreement...
Lowlifes like you should never
utter that name!
I don't think Despariah-sama
would approve of your methods!
We'll know what Despariah-sama does or does not approve of
once we've obtained the Collet, now won't we?
I'll be sure to win next time.
Now that they've gathered all the Pinkies...
...I will  obtain the Collet,
regardless of any sacrifice I have to make!
What did you just say?
That they've gathered all  the Pinkies?
Yes. I personally witnessed them catching the final one.
Is that right? Now I see what this all means.
Bloody-san,
it means that your services are no longer required!
The end of your era is fast approaching.
Please step down from center stage
and take it easy.
Ah, I know! Why not embark on
a self-searching journey?
Please wander through the darkness of despair... forever.
Kawarino...!
Kawarino!!
KAWARINOOOOOO!!!!
Despariah-sama...
...it's right before our eyes.
The moment has...
...finally come-mil.
It's time for us to put the last Pinky
in the Dream Collet-mil.
Now, we'll be able to revive the Palmier Kingdom-mil!
Milk has...
Milk has been waiting so long for this day to arrive-mil!
Don't cry, Milk.
He's right. Who would cry on a day this joyous?
Coco-sama! Nuts-sama!
You shouldn't cry, Milk.
Because if you do, I'll want to cry too.
It's amazing to think
we've come this far.
Don't tell me you guys
are going to start crying now.
Let's put the last Pinky in the Collet.
Nozomi-san?
Okay!
A customer?
Shoot. I forgot to close the store.
I'll go check it out.
How strange...
You're-!
Everything okay?
Ah, sorry. It appears the customer has left.
They did?
Now, hurry and put the Pinky in the Collet!
Okay.
Where's the last Pinky?
Ah, hold on a sec!
Make haste!
Do it now!
Coco?
Coco, what's with you?
Coco-sama's right-mil!
I can't relax until that last Pinky's
in the Collet-mil!
Hurry up and put it in before "they" show up again-mil!
She's right! Quickly, quickly!
S-Sure...
And now, all 55 Pinkies are gathered.
Show it to me.
C'mon, do it now!
M-Milk!
Coco-sama, this is the
"Complete Collection" Collet-mil!
Wait a moment!
Thank you.
Who... are you?!
I just can't thank you all enough...
...for being tricked so many times.
I never knew you were this  gullible.
You're-!
Return the Collet!
Nuts-san!
Give us back the Collet!
Now, if you'll excuse me...
The Collet...
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming* Hey!
*happy coming*
yes!
What'll we do? The Dream Collet's
been stolen!
Milk's been depressed ever since.
It's not Milk's fault! It's Nightmare's fault!
We have to get it back.
But, how?
I've got a great plan!
Nightmare! Give the
Dream Collet back to us!
Nozomi, that's not exactly a plan...
It was worth a shot!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Take Back the Dream Collet!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?