I guess this is it, I'm pretty screwed.
Game over, man, game over!
This is the worst exit interview ever!!
Caught it!
This really and truly is all of them-mil!
Our dreams will come true-coco!
The Palmier Kingdom will be restored-nuts!
Congratulations.
So you've gathered all of them, have you?
Nightmare!
Dream!
Pretty Cure... Five Explosion!!
Please wander through the darkness of despair... forever.
KAWARINOOOOOO!!!!
And now, all 55 Pinkies are gathered.
Show it to me.
C'mon, do it now!
M-Milk!
Coco-sama, this is the
“Complete Collection” Collet-mil!
Thank you.
Who... are you?!
I just can't thank you all enough
for being tricked so many times.
You're—!
Now, if you'll excuse me...
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Despariah-sama, I have returned, Dream Collet in hand.
Bring it here.
Yes.
This is... This is the object of my desires...
I can... I can feel it.
An immense power, capable of
shrouding this world in darkness...
The time to make that vision a reality has finally arrived.
Kawarino!
Yes?
You've done well.
Yes, ma'am.
Despariah-sama...
From the outset,
I alone was more than enough.
Take Back the Dream Collet!
Coco...
Nightmare's here!
Nuts, where's the Dream Collet?!
It can't be!
The entire world will submit to despair.
With the power of this Dream Collet,
I will be eternally young!
I will be the only one
to have their wish granted.
All others will be left behind
in eternal despair.
Yes.
However...
Huh?
If only I hadn't given away
the Dream Collet back then...
Once again, this is my fault-nuts.
Nuts-sama...
We couldn't...
...do anything, either.
We let our guard down
after we found the last Pinky.
If anything, that should've
made us more  cautious.
You're all wrong-mil.
Milk's to blame-mil.
If Milk hadn't handed over the Dream Collet...
Milk...
It's not anybody's fault.
What's important is
what we do from now on.
Isn't that right, Coco?
Nozomi...
Haven't we already been through loads of trouble?
Even so, we never gave up.
So, shall we get going?
Um, where to?
To get the Dream Collet back!
But, Despariah...
...must've already used the Dream Collet-nuts.
The Collet can only be used once-nuts.
No...
We've still got time.
She hasn't used the Collet yet.
After all, the sky is still
sooo clear and pretty!
There are those who won't submit to despair.
Despite having lost the Dream Collet,
they have not yet abandoned hope.
I understand. Allow me
to wrap up those loose ends.
I will sink them into the depths of despair.
Any luck?
No clues here.
But we have to keep looking.
Yeah.
It's Milk's fault-mil...
Don't fret about it.
We'll get through somehow!
Hey! Nightmare!
Give us back the Dream Collet!!
C'mon, Rin-chan, you try it too.
Me?!
G-G-Give it back!!
See? Doesn't that get you all fired up?
Now you three try it.
Okay.
Give back the Collet!!
I cannot give it back.
You're—!
H-He really appeared!
Return the Dream Collet!
You want it back that badly?
That door...
Now, if you'd please just follow me...
This place is...
Welcome, young ladies.
No doubt you remember this place.
At that time, Girinma-kun suffered defeat,
but this time, it's your  turn.
Despariah!!
The Dream Collet!
It's okay-nuts. She hasn't used it yet-nuts.
Give us back the Dream Collet!
Go ahead and take it back.
Here we go, everyone.
Right!
Pretty Cure Metamorphose!
The Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!
The Red Flame of Passion, Cure Rouge!
The Effervescent Scent of Lemon,
Cure Lemonade!
The Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!
The Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!
With the Power of Hope...
...and the Light of the Future!
Our five beautiful hearts will soar!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Now, it's finally come down to this.
Can you defeat me,
and retake the Dream Collet?
No matter who we're up against...
...we'll see this through to the end!
Very well.
Now then, shall we begin?
Let's go!
Yes!
Is that all you've got?!
Please, entertain me at least a little!
The powerful flame of a young girl's
pure heart... Take this!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Did we get 'em?
Not yet!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Oh, you're using that?
It's meaningless.
No it's not!
The great potential of a young girl's dreams... Take this!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Dream!!
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
I knew from the beginning that things would turn out this way.
Even so,
it's almost a pity to say farewell under these circumstances.
Wait, that's right!
If you don't mind, why don't you become my subordinates?
I think you'll do a far better job than my previous underlings.
Don't toy with us!
Who'd ever work for you?!
I thought it was a good offer.
I'd be much better than these fools whom I managed to trick twice.
And I have to thank you
for that one time...
...when you opened the gate for me!!
So that was you -nuts?
What, you just now realized that?
Mint!
No!
We'll make you pay for this-nuts!
What're you doing to Nuts-coco?!
Nuts-san!
So, how're you feeling now?
Aren't you battered badly enough
to admit defeat?
I'll tell you exactly what this is.
This is what's called “despair”!
You should all accept despair as well.
Yes, just like all of them  have done.
We...
We won't ever... fall into despair!
That's right. We'll...
...never let despair bring us down!
Ah, but one of your companions has already accepted despair.
Huh?!
Milk...
You have to help them-coco!
R-Right-mil!
Milk!!
I can't let you do that.
I'd say despair is quite “fitting” for you.
Milk!
No-mil!
Milk lives for Coco-sama and Nuts-sama!
Thank you so much...
...for giving me the Dream Collet!
Milk!
Coco-sama, this is the
“Complete Collection” Collet-mil!
Nozomi...
Everyone...
Milk!!
Outstanding.
Such daunting despair.
The moment when all beings submit to despair...
...is before my eyes!
The time has come!
My wish will be granted now, in this instant!
Grant me eternal life!!
T-The Dream Collet has...
...been activated-coco!
No way...
Those're...
T-The Pinkies-coco!!
Let’s dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You’ll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let’s go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
“Hey, what’s with that?”
“dondakee!?” tte
It’s okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let’s turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you’ll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let’s go!
It’s your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you’re worried
nayandemo
Even if you’re tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you’re stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming*
*happy coming*
yes!
Despariah's used the Dream Collet.
Will we have to accept despair now?
Like heck we will! Don't we all have dreams?
Don't we all have hopes?
We won't fall into despair,
and we'll never, EVER give up!
That light... Milk-san's mask is...!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
Hope vs. Despair: The Final Showdown!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?