1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Original release by
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshishaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
Yes!
I can feel the power overflowing within me.
This is eternal youth, eternal life?
How exquisite it is.
T-The Dream Collet has...
...had its one and only wish used-nuts.
The Dream Collet no longer has the
power to revive the Palmier Kingdom.
You have lost your companion,
and Despariah-sama is eternally young.
There is absolutely nothing left for you...
...except despair.
I'll never... despair!
It's no use acting tough!
Dream...
Legendary warriors, Pretty Cure...
Savor this despair as much as you wish.
We do  have all the time in the world.
Hope vs. Despair: The Final Showdown!
Don't you understand it by now?
Your powers cannot hope to match mine.
Well, on the extreme off chance that you defeated me, what could you do?
You won't have any way to revive the Palmier Kingdom.
Pretty Cure!
Now that you've lost the hope that fuels your powers,
you don't stand a chance against me!
Hope fades away,
and is stained with despair.
How beautiful it is...
Huh?
Isn't this enough-coco?
I don't want to see them
hurt any more-coco!
They've really given their all-nuts.
Thank you-coco!
Don't make me laugh!
Coco!
Nuts-san!
Well, shall I apply the finishing touches?
This is the Darkness of Despair, which draws in
and engulfs those who have lost all hope.
Anyone who is swallowed by this darkness...
will wander eternally in an unending night.
And sure enough, it's picked up
the scent of despair on the five of you!
Huh?
D-Dream!
You would still keep standing,
after all you've been through?
I never  want to go through that again.
I don't want to feel the sadness I felt when I lost my friends.
But how do you plan to prevent that?
W-We've been through
all kinds of hardships so far.
And by combining all our powers,
we've always pulled through!
And we'll... get through this... too...
Where can you find hope
under these circumstances?
Let the Darkness of Despair consume you.
What's that?
Beads?
I finally found the right beads.
They'd go great with
the accessory I'm making.
I know I made a promise with you, Karen-san...
...that as soon as I found what I wanted to do, I'd tell you first.
Yes.
When we visited that shrine at New Year's,
I wished I could get better
at making accessories.
Back then...
It made me happy to see
how much people liked...
...what I made.
I thought I wanted to make
even more people happy.
So...
I was hoping I could get a job
making accessories someday.
Rin-chan...
Karen-san, it looks like I found what I wanted to do first.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Actually, during that shrine visit,
I wanted to tell you...
about what I want to do.
What is it? What do you want to do, Karen-san?
Back when I met you all...
Deep within me, I felt like I wanted to help everyone.
I felt the same thing
when I took care of Milk.
When I saw Milk's smile, after she got better...
...I realized I wanted to help the sick and the wounded.
I want to make them all smile.
So you want to be a doctor, Karen-san?
Yeah.
Why are they laughing?
I'm grateful to all of you.
When I had my singing debut, even while I was trying to make it as an actress...
I worried that it wasn't
the right thing to do.
But because you all gave me
a push in the right direction,
I realized how much fun singing could be.
After that, I found another goal for myself.
Right, Komachi-san?
I also had something I wanted to tell you.
The story I submitted to that contest awhile back,
"Pirate Hurricane," won an award for effort.
Everybody's advice and
encouragement made it possible,
so I feel like that prize
went to all of us.
And in order to live up to that prize,
I want to put all my effort into writing a story
that Urara-san can act out,
once she's become a wonderful actress.
The Darkness of Despair is...!
We just talked about our dreams for the future, right?
Yeah.
That means...
We haven't given up on the future.
That's right. There're still
lots of things we want to do.
We can't let ourselves be dragged down now.
If we put all our power together...
...and all our hearts become one,
we can do anything!
Impossible! How can they stand back up?
We won't fall into despair,
and we won't give up on our dreams!
And one of those precious dreams is...
...to restore the Palmier Kingdom!
You say you'll revive the kingdom?!
You can't use the Dream Collet anymore!
Be consumed by the darkness!
They dispersed the Darkness of Despair?!
Why? Why won't you despair?
Does this mean you won't
follow in their footsteps?
"Their"?
Yes. Take a good look.
They've lost their country,
abandoned all hope,
and are without a future.
They are the inhabitants of the Palmier Kingdom!
You lack the Dream Collet,
and the kingdom's subjects are like this.
You have nothing left to do but to fall into despair!
I'm so glad-coco.
Everyone's here-nuts!
I'm so happy they're all here-coco!
You say you're "happy"?
I'm so sorry, everybody-coco! If we'd been a little stronger,
we would've been able to protect the Palmier Kingdom and all of you-coco!
He's wrong-nuts. I'm the one at fault-nuts.
It's... It's all because I
opened the kingdom's gates,
It's my fault you all had to experience such pain and sadness-nuts.
I'm so sorry-nuts!
Everybody disappeared,
...and Nuts was wounded and asleep inside the Dream Collet.
I was all alone,
searching for the Dream Collet...
There were so, so, many times when I wanted to give up-coco!
But...
They showed me the light-coco.
Pretty Cure taught me that
I should never give up-coco!
In my case, after Nightmare tricked me...
I couldn't trust anybody-nuts.
But Pretty Cure helped me remember
how to trust my friends,
and believe in people-nuts!
Pretty Cure never gave up,
no matter how bad things got-coco!
And then, they put their powers together
to overcome any and all obstacles-nuts!
You all mustn't give up,
not when Pretty Cure's working so hard
for the sake of the Palmier Kingdom-coco!
You can't lose to despair-coco!
I'm sure you can all shake off this despair-nuts!
After all, you've all bathed in...
...the light of Pretty Cure's hope,
and felt the brightness and warmth of hope-coco!
If you're all with us, we won't...
...we won't need the Dream Collet anymore-nuts!
If you're all with us,
we can restore the kingdom-coco!
All of our dreams and hopes are built around you-coco!
So let's...
Let's make a new Palmier Kingdom together-coco!
Let's make a new Palmier Kingdom together-nuts!!
W-What?
Milk!
Coco-sama... Nuts-sama...
Your words have touched Milk deep inside-mil!
Milk!
How could they shatter the Masks of Despair?
Why is it?
Why won't you all fall into despair?
I was so careful, so thorough in leading you into despair...
Why won't you lose hope?!
Fine, whatever.
Your dreams, your hopes,
everything you hold dear...
I'LL ERASE IT ALL!!!
Everyone...
Yes!
It's useless!
You can't hope to match my power!
Everyone, listen to me-mil!
Having been near Coco-sama and Nuts-sama,
Milk understands this very well-mil!
They've been worried about
all of you this whole time-mil!
And the ones who supported and
encouraged them were Pretty Cure-mil!
And now's the time for their and
Pretty Cure's feelings to be rewarded-mil.
Join Pretty Cure...
...in turning despair into hope-mil!!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
Pretty Cure Rouge Burning!
Pretty Cure Lemonade Shining!
Pretty Cure Crystal Shoot!
Send all your power to Pretty Cure...
...and shine alongside them-mil!!
T-This is... the light of hope!?
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!!
Along with the powers of dreams and hope...
Five lights, right here and now!
Pretty Cure... Five Explosion!!
This power is nothing to me!
Des...pariah...-sa...ma...
We did it-coco!
Everyone!
You're okay-nuts!
Thank you all-mil!
We can't relax just yet.
You've shattered the masks, and defeated Kawarino.
You possess fearsome power.
Very well. I shall show you all...
...the true meaning of despair!
Get your subjects to a safe place!
Okay-nuts!
This way, everybody-coco!
Taste true despair...
...to your heart's content!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming*
*happy coming*
yes!
A lot's happened to us, huh?
We became Pretty Cure, and met everyone else...
We never could've come this far on our own.
That's right. If the five of us are together...
We'll be just fine from now on.
Yeah. Let's get through this together!
Yes!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5:
With Dreams and Hope, Pretty Cure 5!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?