Taste true despair...
...to your heart's content!
1, 2, 3, 4, Pretty Cure 5!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
Pu-ri-ti kyu kyu kyu kyu-a
Yes!
Everybody yes, fight!
eburibadi Yes, faito!
Yes!
Be excited, laugh like crazy!
dokidoki paatto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
Pretty Cure!
Pretty Cure Splash Subs (pcssubs.wordpress.com)
Timing, QC: Force_Gaia    Encode: K.o.R    Translation, Etc.: Zalis
Special Thanks: Silvania, Magenta, Rika_chama, Cure_Gecko
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Yes! Purikyua 5!
When you grow up, what do you want to be?
ookikunattara nani ni naritai?
Wha-t, what, what do you?
na-ni naru naru no
I want to do everything, hold it all in my hands!
ryoute ni ippai zenbu yaritai!
Do it all!
i-pai yaritai!
These tears that just won't go away,
mondai ga tokenai namida wa
let's wipe them out with the eraser of my heart!
kokoro no keshigomu de keshichaou
Metamorphose!
metamorufouze!
Go!
We're born to dream.
yume miru tame umareta
1, 2, 3 4 5!
Soar! Girls, give it your all.
toberuyo ganbaru onna no ko
5, 4, 3 2 1!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
kachimake dake janai mirai e
Carve out a new future tomorrow!
asu wo nurikaeteku
When in a pinch, there's your chance! Transform and be tough!
pinchi kara chansu e tafu ni henshin!
Go!
Go-go!
Go-go-go-go!
Yes!
Pretty Cu-cu-cu-cure
puriti kyu-kyu-kyu-kyua
Yes!
Everybody yes, hustle!
eburibadi Yes, hassuru!
Yes!
Be excited, smile and laugh!
dokidoki nitto waratte
Smile and go! Go!
sumairu gogo!
One, two, three-four, Pretty Cure (Five!)
1, 2, 3-4 Purikyua (5!)
Go!
With Dreams and Hope, Pretty Cure 5!
Bow down before the might of despair!
Okay girls, let's go!
Yes!
Are you okay-coco?
Is everyone all right-nuts?
Yes-papa. And we're all glad to see the two of you unharmed-papa.
Milk, you've also done very well-papa.
That's not quite true, Papaya-sama.
Pretty Cure did most of the protecting-mil.
We just have to separate them from the ground, right?
Looks that way!
Pretty Cure Aqua Tornado!
They didn't explode, even when we broke their links to the surface.
Then how?
There is nothing that any of you can do.
Abandon all hope, and fall into despair!
No way! We won't give up!
I know  we'll find a way out of this!
Dream!
Once you fall into despair,
this will all be over.
Allow me to remove
the source of your hope.
Behold reality!
No matter what you do,
you have no chance of winning!
I don't think so!
We'll just have to change reality!
As soon as you cease this resistance,
you'll be at peace.
Which is exactly what they  did.
You guys-!
Pretty Cure Mint Shield!
I won't let you lay a finger on Coco-sama and Nuts-sama's precious subjects!
Dream!
Everyone!
No challenge at all.
However, that was also inevitable.
Because the source of all your powers...
...lay in this thing.
Dream... Dream!
Coco...
I don't want to see your face
get scarred any further.
You've done enough.
Dream...
Dream, that's not Coco-nuts!
Open your eyes-mil!
Don't worry-coco!
Dream...
Dream will...
...be just fine-coco!!
You're not Coco!
The Coco I know worked...
...for everyone's sakes,
to revive the Palmier Kingdom.
He always put others ahead of himself
and always encouraged me!
Dream is always optimistic,
regardless of the situation.
She's an incredible person who's striving for a better future-coco!
Your kindness, and the way you treasured everybody...
...gave me the strength
to keep moving forward.
That's why I...
...love you, Coco.
Dream!!
And I'll be sure to make
Coco's dream come true!
Silence!
I had my wish granted,
while your wishes went unfulfilled.
So why won't you despair!?
Why is it? Aren't you people scared?
Doesn't the thought of aging frighten you?
Aren't you afraid that
your power will wane away?
Even though I've attained eternal life, I'm...
Why?!
Dream!
S-Stay away!
None may approach me!
Her transformation wore off-nuts!
No, she undid it herself-coco!
Nozomi-san!
Are you insane?!
W-Why...
I thought I'd be able
to talk to you this way.
Talk to me?
Yes.
I thought I was the same as you.
So I wanted to talk.
We are not  the same!
But you feel scared and anxious too, right?
It's because you have a heart,
just like everyone else does.
They disappeared?
Nozomi-san neutralized the power of despair!
You never gave up at any time, and always retained hope.
Didn't you ever feel afraid?
I was.
And I'm scared now, too.
But I'm fine.
W-Why?
You guys...
It's true; you've always plunged ahead without caring about the consequences.
But we felt like we had to
go along for the ride.
You're always full of surprises, but...
...we've come this far with you,
so we have to see this through to the end.
Thanks, girls.
I'm just doing my best...
...along with all my friends.
Having friends nearby reduces the fear...
...and allows you to remain hopeful?
Let's talk this over.
Okay?
You insolent fool!
Despariah-sama is far
too important a figure...
...to be pawed at by the likes of you!!
Nozomi-san!
Nozomi!
Get out of my sight!!
D-Despariah-sama...?
W-Why? Why treat me this way...?
I wish to hear more of
what these girls have to say.
There's no need to pay any attention to Pretty Cure's meaningless babble!
Despariah-sama!!
I wish to know how hope can be maintained.
What're you talking about?
You've become ageless and deathless!
You were going to shroud
the world in despair,
and become its one and only ruler!
What more could you desire?!
Obtaining eternal life
has not brought me peace.
Even if I shroud the world in despair,
won't it amount to nothing in the end?
Despariah-sama? Then all
the things I've done so far...
...were pointless?!
Curse you, Kawarino!!!
You're.. Bloody!??
DESPARIAH-SAMA!!!!
What's wrong?
I can't control the power anymore!
Huh?
The power of despair is running amok.
At this rate...
I have a request.
Use your powers to seal away this world, with me in it.
We can't! If we did that, then you'd be...
If this goes on, my powers
will obliterate the entire world.
But...!
This is my final wish. Please!
I understand.
I don't know what should be said
at a time like this.
I deeply regret this.
I'm in your debt.
They sure can eat.
What do you expect? We've got
the whole Palmier Kingdom in here.
Too bad Jiiya-san's on vacation.
He could've helped us out.
No, he couldn't have.
What'll you all do now?
The Palmier Kingdom's territory is still a wasteland-coco.
With everyone's hard work,
we'll build a new Palmier Kingdom-nuts.
Who will become king:
Coco-sama or Nuts-sama?
We all must decide together-papa!
Please listen to me-mil!
Milk has always been at Coco-sama
and Nuts-sama's side in this world-mil.
They both had a hard time adjusting to this unfamiliar world-mil.
Even so, they always cooperated...
...for the good of the kingdom and everyone in it-mil.
As long as they're together,
they can do anything-mil.
Therefore, I think Coco-sama and Nuts-sama...
...should both become kings together-mil!
We agree!
A prize for effort, huh?
Does this mean you can be a novelist?
No, it just means they
acknowledged my efforts.
I've still got a long ways to go.
But getting this effort prize
has filled me with confidence.
Nuts-san, thanks for
everything you've done for me.
I  should be thanking you.
I was always dwelling on my past failures,
and regretting them.
But...
You rewrote your story over and over,
and seeing how you kept on writing
without getting disheartened taught me...
...to move forward.
Nuts-san...
Here.
But this is...!
I want you to have it, Komachi.
So that we can continue onward.
Yes.
They were all really happy, huh?
I never imagined we'd both  become king.
In the past, having two kings
was unheard-of.
Still, I think two is better than one.
You can support each other, and combine your strengths to overcome anything.
Yeah, I think so too.
Hey, do you remember our promise from summer vacation?
Of course I do. Once we restore the Palmier Kingdom,
I'll invite you to visit.
I'll...
...be waiting.
Waiting for the time when
the Palmier Kingdom is restored,
and for you to call me there.
I'll look forward to it.
Yeah. I'll be sure to build a kingdom
worthy of showing off to you, Nozomi.
Bet on it.
Ah, a shooting star!
Everyone, thank you so very much-coco!
You're very welcome.
It was fun.
We'll never forget you-nuts.
Don't overdo it, Nuts-san.
Stay positive and do your best.
Karen, I'm sure you'll become
a great doctor-mil.
And Milk, I think you'll be a fine caregiver.
Well then, it's time to get going-coco.
Rin-san, didn't you say we should see them off with a smile?
Y-Yeah, but...
This isn't farewell, you guys.
As long as our hearts are connected,
we're sure to meet again.
we're sure to meet again-coco.
By the way, Coco,
I found my dream for the future.
Your dream-coco?
I want to be a teacher.
You once told me that my potential would fill up like a balloon.
I want to inflate my own potential to the max!
You and everyone else have taught me
all kinds of things,
and given me the true courage I needed to fulfill my dreams.
I was able to feel confident about myself.
That's why I want to become a teacher like you were,
and help somebody else in the same way.
We'll also work hard to become
kings that can fill everyone with hope,
just like you do-coco.
Girls?
Yeah.
Those butterflies are the Five Lights of Hope that protect the Palmier Kingdom-coco!
They'll open the way
to the kingdom for us-nuts!
Stay healthy and work hard, okay?
Yes!
They're gone.
Yeah.
I'm sure Coco and Nuts are trying to be
the best kings they can be.
So I'll do my best to work towards my dream of becoming a teacher.
However, these test scores aren't
exactly cooperating with my vision.
But it's all good!
CamHeart 10th Audition
If I don't do my job well,
or don't pass an audition,
I'll probably feel down.
But since everyone's with me,
I can keep going!
I sometimes get stuck
when I'm writing a story.
When that happens, I always come here.
I can't always decide
which design to go with.
That's why I get everybody's opinions!
I sometimes feel unsure about being suited to work in the medical field.
But when I come here,
everyone's smiles cheer me right up.
Let's eat!
Rin, you brought orange juice?
Yeah, and I assume you brought grape juice?
Yes, I did.
Nozomi-san, have some sweet fried eggs!
Huh? You didn't put ketchup on it?
Sometimes I leave it out.
Everyone's here.
Friends that I can talk to about anything.
People who'll keep an eye on me.
Precious companions.
Best friends.
Yes! Pretty Cure 5!
Let's dance!
te no hira taiyou mukete
Put your palms up towards the sun
(Go go go go!)
furifuri karada yusureba
and swing your body from side to side
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Take a shower in the light
hikari no shawaa o abite
(Go go go go!)
kyou mo ichinichi pikapika
You'll sparkle all day
all right!
All right!
Work it, to the limit, hold your head up a a a oh!
ganbatte, harikitte, ganbaransu de ei ei o~
Yes!
When you run up against a wall
kabe ni butsukatte
Let's go!
Your eyes will narrow
me ga ten ni naru
"Hey, what's with that?"
"dondakee!?" tte
It's okay to start from way down
mainasu kara demo OK!
OK!
Let's turn it around!
gyakuten shiyou!
All at once, yo yo!
ikki! YO YO
Let out a yawn and stretch your back
akubito senobide
and you'll feel at ease
raku ni naru
Let's go!
It's your source of energy
genki no minamoto
Even if you're worried
nayandemo
Even if you're tired
nemukutemo
Powerful Smiling♪!
pawafuru sumairin♪!
1 2 3 4 5!
And then hold your head high and dance (Go! Go!)
soshite ganbaransu de dansu
(Go go go go!)
If you're stressed it will make you refreshed
sondemotte sutoresu mo > rifuresshu
(Pretty Cure 5!)
Everyone is a glittering gem
minna wa hikaru houseki
(Go go go go!)
that shines with the light of life~
kagayaku inochi sono mono~
Oh yes!
oh! yes
Dreaming is a miracle
yumemiru kiseki
Now jump with your whole body
banji janpu suru~
Ooh go!
The magic of Pretty Cure
purikyua no mahou
*Happy coming*
*happy coming*
yes!
We'd gone back to being normal girls...
...until we got a mysterious letter from someone named Flora,
inviting us to the Cure Rose Garden!
Let's go and have Syrup
the delivery boy help us out!
It's decided!
But it looks like it won't be so easy,
'cause we get attacked by some weirdo!
Time to transform, everybody!
Yes! Pretty Cure 5 Go Go!
Resurrection! Pretty Cure 5!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, 'kay?
This has been Zalis's 47th and likely final Pretty Cure episode translation.  I hope you enjoyed this series and Splash Star, despite how long it took me to finish translating their 2nd halves.
But stay tuned for more of Yes! Pretty Cure 5 from PCSS, including the movie and the earlier episodes. And possibly other re-releases from the Pretty Cure franchise, and/or other undisclosed projects.
Force_Gaia: It feels weird that the first series I help sub ends before I've finished subbing it. However I'm thankful to Zalis for accepting my help, for teaching everything to me from scratch, and for his monumental patience while I've had many mishaps this year
that caused the huge delays. But most of all it just feels good to know
I've played a part in finishing this long-overdue series.